<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Video Dubbing on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/video-dubbing/</link><description>Recent content in Video Dubbing on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/video-dubbing/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flag Monkey Goes Swedish!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/flag-monkey-goes-swedish/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/flag-monkey-goes-swedish/</guid><description>A good friend of ours, Flag Monkey, has been experimenting with AI video translation. Lets have a look at his use case, why he is using our product and what he hopes will work based on the content!
Meet Kevin and Jay! Flag Monkey is a flags and bunting sales business, which relies on social media to create an ecosystem of flag enthusiasts.
So who is Kevin?
Kevin is a puppet, and is the star of the Flag Monkey channel!</description></item><item><title>Reviewing Vixer Video Editor On iPhone</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/reviewing-vixer-video-editor-on-iphone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/reviewing-vixer-video-editor-on-iphone/</guid><description>Hello, fam!
Last month, we made a review about Splice video editor.
The app was, in fact, really good and we rated it a 4 out of 5.
We are still in search of another phone video editor and this time we are going to make a review about Vixer Video Editor!
What Is Vixer Video Editor? Vixer is a video editor that allows you to:
• Trim, Speed, Crop videos</description></item><item><title>Why Should You Translate Video Content: A Client Perspective</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-translate-video-content-a-client-perspective/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-translate-video-content-a-client-perspective/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we do a lot of work in the Internationalization And Localization industry.
But we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.
Sometimes however, the most useful thing we can do is just have a conversation.</description></item><item><title>AI Dubbing: What Different Dialects Of English Sound Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</guid><description>Today we are going to look AI dubbing and look at a few different samples of what an AI can sound like in English. We are going to do something pretty simple, we will use the quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog for our seed text.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what this sentence is, quoting from Wikipedia, &amp;ldquo;The quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog&amp;rdquo; is an English-language pangram—a sentence that contains all of the letters of the alphabet.</description></item></channel></rss>