<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Weekly Roundup on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/weekly-roundup/</link><description>Recent content in Weekly Roundup on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/weekly-roundup/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Girls and Women Revitalising Canada's Indigenous Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-girls-and-women-revitalising-canadas-indigenous-languages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-girls-and-women-revitalising-canadas-indigenous-languages/</guid><description>It was International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day this past Sunday 8 March and in honour of the day we&amp;rsquo;re looking at some incredible females who are doing all they can for their native languages.
The Girls and Women Revitalising Canada&amp;#39;s Indigenous Languages
Celebrating Indigenous Women Who Are Reclaiming and Revitalising Their Languages Image courtesy of Marion Konwanénhon Delaronde and Karihwiióstha Callie Montour In light of International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day which was this past Sunday, March 8, CBC News in Canada put together an article celebrating a number of Indigenous women and their plight to preserve and revitalise their traditional languages.</description></item><item><title>Fighting the Coronavirus and E. Coli with Machine Learning</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/fighting-the-coronavirus-and-e-coli-with-machine-learning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/fighting-the-coronavirus-and-e-coli-with-machine-learning/</guid><description>When it comes to combating superbugs and viruses, the human raced needs all the help it can get. Artificial Intelligence is being implemented to find treatments to fight bacteria that was formally resistant to all forms of antibiotics. China is also using AI to quickly determine if a person is showing symptoms of the coronavirus, which could be a great win against getting a handle on the respiratory disease.
Fighting The Coronavirus And E-Coli With Machine Learning</description></item><item><title>AI &amp; Wildlife Preservation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-and-wildlife-preservation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-and-wildlife-preservation/</guid><description>If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing most of us can agree on, it&amp;rsquo;s that wildlife preservation is important. The animals on this planet have been suffering a lot since we humans came on the scene. Luckily, there are amazing people out there trying to right the wrongs. Using Artificial Intelligence, researchers are able to continue this quest all the more and we&amp;rsquo;re looking into just how that&amp;rsquo;s being done.
How Artificial Intelligence Is Changing Wildlife Research Giraffe populations are rapidly declining but AI is here to help Researcher Jenna Stacy-Dawes and her team at San Diego Zoo&amp;rsquo;s Institute for Conservation Research are being assisted in their work in giraffe conservation with the AI software program, Wildbook.</description></item><item><title>Speaking In The Mother Tongue: AI Indian Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</guid><description>We recently came across an article with the exciting news that the Indian government is planning on making its Internet content available in regional languages &amp;ldquo;to remove the language barrier among Indians.&amp;quot;
Currently websites are available in English and Hindi but that leaves out the remaining 20 regional languages that are spoken across the country.
&amp;ldquo;We need a method through which any Indian using his or her language should be able to converse with any user in any other Indian language without the impediment of English as a link language.</description></item><item><title>On The Brink Of Extinction: Nearly Dead Languages And The Dedicated Linguists Bringing Them Back To Life</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</guid><description>Thousands of kilometres apart, and in incredibly different cultures; three linguists are doing their part to save the culture of their people through language.
Masahiro Yamada and Natsuko Nakagawa in Japan and Kenny Pheasant in the United States are all passionate about ensuring almost lost languages are preserved and continue to be taught; and a lot of it comes down to teaching the languages to children.
Linguists Work To Preserve Ryukyu Dialects Now Dying Out Image courtesy of Nobuaki Tanaka Professors at the National Institute for Japanese Language and Linguistics made an alarming discovery when they found that many dialects in the Okinawa Prefecture are on the verge of dying out.</description></item><item><title>Sign Languages: Their past, present and future</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/sign-languages-their-past-present-and-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/sign-languages-their-past-present-and-future/</guid><description>For something that is used by an estimated 70 million people worldwide, there is still a lot we don&amp;rsquo;t know when it comes to the origin of sign language - luckily research is being done to change that. Going from the past to the future, Google Translate is developing a way to translate sign language into speech and we are excited about the possibilities that this brings for, well, everyone!</description></item><item><title>One place, many languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-place-many-languages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-place-many-languages/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re talking language today and how diverse it can be even in the same country, or city! Germany is still a country divided when it comes to what a pancake should be called - maybe they should be called egg-cakes? Also Mandarin is now Melbourne and Sydney&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;most widely spoken community language.&amp;rdquo;
Language matters, it&amp;rsquo;s important culturally and on a deeper level to help us identify with ourselves and others.</description></item><item><title>Where are we heading with AI computing in the 2020s? And how human can they really become?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/where-are-we-heading-with-ai-computing-in-the-2020s-and-how-human-can-they-really-become/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/where-are-we-heading-with-ai-computing-in-the-2020s-and-how-human-can-they-really-become/</guid><description>We now well and truly know that Artificial Intelligence is here to stay (and in fact has been for quite some time), but what will become of it, and us, in the future? One author has some very interesting thoughts on how AI computing will reach beyond just recognising how to act like a human but rather see the world the way we do and have a form of common sense.</description></item><item><title>Real life Dr Dolittle: We are on our way to talking to the animals and AI may make happen sooner than you think!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-jan-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-jan-2020/</guid><description>Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be fantastic if we could understand what our pets were trying to tell us? Having them be able to communicate if they like the food we give them, when they&amp;rsquo;re not feeling well and when they want to be pet, would take out so much of the guess work. (Although hearing dogs constantly asking to have a ball thrown might get a bit old after a while). Researchers are looking into decoding animal languages and we are here for it!</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: For the Love of Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-17-dec-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-17-dec-2019/</guid><description>Language. It's something we're passionate about here at Video Translator, we can't get enough of it. And, judging by the news that&amp;rsquo;s come out in the past week, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of folks out there who share our passion. We&amp;rsquo;re delving into language from all across the globe this week; NLP research engineers working with pidgin English, YouTube India is branching out into local and regional Indian languages, Navajo is getting it&amp;rsquo;s own version of one of the most popular (read: annoying for adults) songs amongst toddlers and we see the effects on the brain from being bilingual from an early age.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Exciting developments for Epilepsy patients, Amazon has added 22 new languages to Amazon Translate and has Microsoft given children the ability to speak to reindeer?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-10-dec-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-10-dec-2019/</guid><description>It seems like every week there are exciting new developments with artificial intelligence being used in the health, medicine and science fields; and that&amp;rsquo;s because, well, there is. There is often quite a negative attitude amongst the public in relation to AI, &amp;ldquo;they&amp;rsquo;re going to take our jobs!&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s the end of the human race!&amp;rdquo; But it&amp;rsquo;s not all doom and gloom. Really good, positive, and not to mention lifesaving advances in medicine, are taking place all with AI and proving that our new robot overlords are not planning on taking over the world just quite yet&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Hello baby! Machine learning helping to understand placental health, did Shakespeare have help? And advances in health and medicine thanks to AI.</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-26-nov-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-26-nov-2019/</guid><description>Considering it is something that keeps the human race going, maternal and placental health is still not properly understood, which proves extremely detrimental to the health of mother and baby during pregnancy. Thanks to a new development in AI technology, that will begin to change. We&amp;rsquo;re also looking at how educators in the US are frantically searching for a better solution to interpretations services that help communicate with non-English speaking families and we look at the leaps and bounds being made in medicine thanks to machine learning.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: AI to the rescue! Using machine learning for the greater good; advances in medicine, agriculture and saving lives, is there anything we can't do with the help of artificial intelligence?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-12-nov-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-12-nov-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another AI focused week and with so much going on in the world of Artificial Intelligence, can you blame us? The field of medicine and science have long been advocates of using AI for the greater good and it appears there are some incredible trail blazers helping to make that happen.
1. A Star Professor—And Her Radical, AI-Powered Plan To Discover New Drugs Using AI to discover new medicine One woman is using her incredible skills and mind to advance the way in which drugs can be discovered and created with the help of artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Foreign signs installed to save lives, when seeing isn't believing; learning about deepfake videos, content creators coming together to save the planet and hilarious movie translations</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-05-nov-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-05-nov-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s the start of a new month and news from around the globe keeps on rolling in. This week we&amp;rsquo;ve learnt the power of YouTube, its content creators and their followers and how they&amp;rsquo;re working together for the greater good. We also focus on the Western Australian Government&amp;rsquo;s foreign language road signs initiative that aims to save lives and we delve into the world of deepfake videos. Are they as dangerous as they seem?</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Google's latest Pixel 4 app impresses, praise for Nobel Prize winner and a feel-good video to brighten your week</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-29-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-29-oct-2019/</guid><description>Exciting news for content creators this week at Instagram&amp;rsquo;s IGTV releases features that will allow videos to viewed as a series. Google is releasing an on-device transcribing app that may be a game-changer, plus just because we loved it so; a video showing a deaf father signing to his newborn daughter, that has really hit us with all the feels.
1. Pixel 4’s live transcription goes up against “real-life” challenges Image courtesy of The Wall Street Journal Google is a releasing a new built in app in their Pixel 4 and honestly, it&amp;rsquo;s very impressive.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Travelling back in time with AI, learning the love of translation and why it is imperative to get more interpreters in courthouses to aid domestic violence cases</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-22-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-22-oct-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another big week in AI news, from assisting in search and rescue methods to aiding doctors in detecting brain bleeds, it&amp;rsquo;s being proven time and time again how Artificial Intelligence can help humanity in meaningful ways. We also see that AI is helping historians create a portal into the past of Europe and creating virtual worlds that we can experience. In other news, one woman is advocating for more support and resources for translators in domestic violence cases and one author and translator explains her love for language and translation.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Translation devices changing the business game, machine learning aiding scientific research and the world's first ever AI concert</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-oct-2019/</guid><description>The art of translation has been a skilled required by humans for over 2000 years, we&amp;rsquo;ve got a few interesting articles that highlight just how important it is and one translator shares with us what she&amp;rsquo;s learnt after being in the business for 20 years. We&amp;rsquo;re also looking at how machine learning is aiding scientists in researching plants, AI writers writing as well as humans can, and we celebrate as Armenia hosts the first ever AI concert.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: AI is here to help; translation at the tip of your ears; and Google's ALBERT is receiving top ranks</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-01-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-01-oct-2019/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s been a lot going on with AI in particular this week. Read on to get up to date on some of the most interesting things coming out of the world of Artificial Intelligence. There&amp;rsquo;s also top ranking machine learning systems and earbuds that can translate languages as you&amp;rsquo;re hearing them.
1. Yes Bank creates &amp;lsquo;Yes Robot&amp;rsquo; using Microsoft Cognitive Services Yes Robot A bank in India has created AI assistant, &amp;lsquo;Yes Robot&amp;rsquo; to provide 24 hour customer service to its patrons.</description></item></channel></rss>