<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dialects on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/dialects/</link><description>Recent content in Dialects on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/dialects/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>5 Countries With The Most Official Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/countries-with-the-most-official-languages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/countries-with-the-most-official-languages/</guid><description>Did you know that there are over 7,000 languages in the world?
Yes, 7000!
Although there are so many languages out there, there are only a few countries that have three or more languages as their official languages.
So, what are the top 5 countries with the most official languages and what languages are they? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out in this article!
What Are Official Languages? Definition of official language</description></item><item><title>Transcribing A Video: How Do I Know Which Dialect To Choose?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/which-dialect-to-choose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/which-dialect-to-choose/</guid><description>Here at Video Translator, we love your questions. Receiving your questions mean that you are interested in the services we are offering.
Not long ago, we received an enquiry from a customer.
How do you know which dialect would work when transcribing videos
&amp;ldquo;Hello, there are YouTube videos in Arabic News. I would like to have them transcribed, translated and dubbed into the English language so that I can understand them.</description></item><item><title>The Importance Of Learning A Foreign Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-importance-of-learning-a-foreign-language/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-importance-of-learning-a-foreign-language/</guid><description>I was born in Indonesia, a country with over 250 million population scattered across its 17,000 islands. When I came to Australia four years ago, I noticed that most Australians with Indonesian background or mixed raced Indonesians do not know how to speak Indonesian.
Indonesia, the land with 17,000 islands
So, I began to question myself: how important it is to learn a foreign language? I came up with few answers…</description></item><item><title>How AI Dubbing Will Change Everything: Building A Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</guid><description>There is a very interesting piece of content we are looking at today. A team from IIIT-H (Indian Institute of Information Technology - Hyderabad) has build an AI which translates and lip-syncs a video from one language to another.
This originally came to our attention in this article from the folks at TNW. The paper this article is based on is here, and if you are interested in AI/Language you should absolutely have a look.</description></item><item><title>How AI Transcription Fails And What To Do About It</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</guid><description>AI Transcription has been all the rage recently. Several companies have been coming out with new products to meet this requirement.
What does it mean? Does it work? How to evaluate these products? We take a look and try to think behind the hype.
First we look at some of the incoming offerings. Then some issues with AI Transcription and Translation.
Incoming Offerings There is a very large number of AI products hitting the market place.</description></item><item><title>One Igbo Woman Trying To Save Her Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</guid><description>Oddly, its the feel-good stories which we think are the most important. This week we had a few stories come by which show much progress is being made in the popularity of regional languages.
Here at VideoTranslator we feel that most people are quite proud of where they come from - its totally natural.
Each one of us has a story of how we came to be, and the stories of those who came before are a vital part of any human identity.</description></item><item><title>How To Reach Gen Z Using AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we keep an eye on what everyone else is doing.
Well, we try to anyways. And one of the better resources out there is Social Media Today. This article, &amp;lsquo;What Gen Z is Watching Online - and What That Means for Marketers in 2020&amp;rsquo; is full of wonderful titbits about how to think about video.
How Gen Z Is Using YouTube The big takeaway from the article is that Vlogging and Informative Videos are the biggest draws.</description></item><item><title>Clients: Why You Make Me Blush!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:02 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we get lots of feedback from clients. Most of it is good, some of it not so much. Recently, as we have started to build out our retail client base it has become interesting.
The product challenge with retail is quite different from an enterprise offering or a managed service. Because the user is not being paid to use the product (or being told to by their manager) expectations for the product are totally different.</description></item><item><title>Accessibility: Why It Matters And How To Avoid Being Sued</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work with clients who are part of the healthcare ecosystem.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, voice over artists, or in this case, nurses/doctors. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing - we are technologists who are trying to service our clients to the best of our ability.
Every now and then a story turns up which brings a lot of our work into sharp focus.</description></item><item><title>Quick Transcribe: For When You Need To Get Transcription Done Quickly</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator.Ai, we work closely with the Internationalization And Localization industry. This industry has many different participants, and they use our technology in different ways.
As a software firm, the hardest thing is to really understand what our clients do and why they do these things. Sounds funny, but it is true.
We had a strong response to our previous article, 3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency, and a number of questions and suggestions.</description></item><item><title>Mr Sh*thole: What To Do When Your AI Misbehaves</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</guid><description>Today we look at a humorous articles which look at what happens when AI goes wrong. Here at video translator we like to keep abreast of the latest news in the intersection of Artificial Intelligence, Natural Language Programming, Human Languages and Culture.
Read on to find out how Facebook&amp;rsquo;s AI got in trouble, and why Oracle thinks replacing your manager with a robot is likely, and a good thing to boot!</description></item><item><title>What Arabic Voices are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</guid><description>Previously we&amp;rsquo;ve gone through the list of our English speaking AI and the different dialects they speak. You can see them all here.
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re looking at our Arabic speaking AI and the different dialects and voices available.
If you need a reminder as to how to select the appropriate AI language and dialect, check out our article here.
Now, on to the voices! We&amp;rsquo;ve used the phrase birds of a feather, flock together or الطيور على أشكالها تقع for our AI to say each time for the examples.</description></item><item><title>Extra! Extra! Read all about it!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/extra-extra-read-all-about-it/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/extra-extra-read-all-about-it/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of exciting developments at VideoTranslator, which means exciting things for you! This means that you&amp;rsquo;ll be hearing more from us going forward in the form of a weekly email.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t subscribed to our mailing list or signed up for a free trial yet, please do so here.
The email will be featuring the latest articles we&amp;rsquo;ve posted which will be like the following:
What English Dialects are Available?</description></item><item><title>3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work in what is called the Internationalization And Localization industry.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
When do we do this work for our clients? Generally when a client needs a managed service. This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.</description></item><item><title>What English Dialects are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-english-dialects-are-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-english-dialects-are-available/</guid><description>Did you know that our AI can speak in over 180 languages and more than 120 differing dialects and different genders? It&amp;rsquo;s true! That&amp;rsquo;s one smart robot ;)
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re focusing on English and the four different dialects that you can choose from when using our app.
For those that have you used the app before, you will notice that we have renamed the &amp;ldquo;voices&amp;rdquo;. Previously we had them named as EN-IN-P-M1, or UK-S4-M which didn&amp;rsquo;t make a lot of sense for those who were unfamiliar with the technology.</description></item><item><title>What A Hindi Speaking AI Sounds Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</guid><description>A few posts ago we transcribed an Indian English video using a Speech-To-Text Indian English transcription Artificial Intelligence (AI). Today we are going to take the same idea forward, and now going to translate the video into Hindi.
To recap, we used a sample clip from Rajya Sabha TV which as (a) transcribed using a speech-to-text AI, and (b) cleaned up by a human. We will now clean it up a little bit more, and then translate the content into Hindi.</description></item><item><title>Samples From A Voice Over Robot: French, German and Dutch</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</guid><description>Following on from last week&amp;rsquo;s blog post, where we looked at different English dialects, we are going to do much the same today in Dutch, French and German.
Do you like the below examples? Let us know - we are super keen to hear what you think?
To try other languages (for FREE!) sign up to the free trial and give it a go!
Steps First, as per our usual create a new item using the English language template.</description></item><item><title>AI Dubbing: What Different Dialects Of English Sound Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</guid><description>Today we are going to look AI dubbing and look at a few different samples of what an AI can sound like in English. We are going to do something pretty simple, we will use the quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog for our seed text.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what this sentence is, quoting from Wikipedia, &amp;ldquo;The quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog&amp;rdquo; is an English-language pangram—a sentence that contains all of the letters of the alphabet.</description></item><item><title>How To Use Auto Overlay To Simplify Transcription</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-auto-overlay-to-simplify-transcription/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-auto-overlay-to-simplify-transcription/</guid><description>We got this video from OSL Brokerage&amp;rsquo;s LinkedIn page. We are not suggesting that we have any relationship with OSL, and largely, we are using this content to demonstrate the process by which video content can be translated.
This specific video already has captions, so we don&amp;rsquo;t need these per se. However, we will be adding Chinese captions as an overlay, as opposed to captions.
The final output is shown below.</description></item><item><title>How To Reach Refugees, And Combat People Smugglers, With AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-refugees-and-combat-people-smugglers-with-ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-refugees-and-combat-people-smugglers-with-ai/</guid><description>Video translation is all the rage in Sydney currently. It sounds hard to believe, but this is honestly the case at the moment. The controversy revolves around a secret video, which the current Australian Prime Minister, Scott Morrison has (apparently) recorded.
The gist of the news is that the Australian Prime Minister has recorded a video, which will be translated into a number of languages. Once translated, the video will be broadcast in the media in different countries including Indonesia, Malaysia, Thailand, Pakistan, Bangladesh, Sri Lanka, Afghanistan and Iraq.</description></item><item><title>How To Use AI To Save Lions, In Afrikaans</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-ai-to-save-lions-in-afrikaans/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-ai-to-save-lions-in-afrikaans/</guid><description>As part of our process for testing the platform prior to go live, one of the things we look to do is test a large number of different languages. Part of it is good fun, the other objective is to try to change things around to see if we can break the platform and find bugs.
Realistically, this means looking for cool videos, and then trying things out with the videos.</description></item><item><title>How To Transcribe Lots of Different Accents Accurately</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-lots-of-different-accents-accurately/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-lots-of-different-accents-accurately/</guid><description>Today, we will look at how to transcribe many different accents correctly. First off, what does this question even mean in terms of AI?
The video we are working with is from Institute for Communication in Health Care (ICH) at the Australian National University (ANU).
Looking at the ICH&amp;rsquo;s mission statement, &amp;ldquo;The ICH’s mission is to build an international, collaborative research and training hub in healthcare communication to improve patient safety and quality of healthcare practice around the world&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;</description></item></channel></rss>