<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Transcription on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/transcription/</link><description>Recent content in Transcription on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:00:01 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/transcription/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Implications Of AI Adoption In Our Tools</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-implications-of-ai-adoption-in-our-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-implications-of-ai-adoption-in-our-tools/</guid><description>AI is everywhere in the news these days. But something critical has changed recently.
In the near past, AI has gone from being super fancy to being, well... pedestrian.
Say what now?
Well - AI is becoming ordinary. And turning up in our office/productivity toolkits.
In recent days, Google has expanded its offering using AI, as has Microsoft, and so has Amazon.
What does this mean for how we work, and how can you use this trend to advantage your business?</description></item><item><title>How NSW Health Is Using Video Translation To Empower Occupational Therapists</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</guid><description>One major challenge in diverse societies is the provision of healthcare services.
In western Sydney, this problem is directly tackled by the South-West Sydney Local Health District, which sits under New South Wales Health.
Ok - so obviously this is complicated stuff. But how does video translation help?
If you don't speak good English, specifically business English, finding information is very hard. The doctor is the only resource who can help, but what happens when they don't speak your language?</description></item><item><title>Why YouTube Stopped Community Caption Contributions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</guid><description>Community captions are a function in YouTube. This function allows a YouTube content creator to crowd source captions for their video content.
YouTube is shutting this down. Here is how it will affect you!
Change To Community Contributions On YouTube Notice about an upcoming change to community contributions on YouTube Both creators and viewers have reported problems with the community contributions feature, including spam, abuse, and low quality submissions.</description></item><item><title>How Vyasa University Is Fighting Covid With Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</guid><description>Vivekananda Yoga Anusandhana Samsthana or VYASA is a registered charitable institution (1986) working to make Yoga a socially relevant field of study.
Based on the teachings of Swami Vivekananda, Vyasa University combines the four streams of Yoga with unity in their diversity, the key essence of Indian culture, applications of Yoga to bring health, harmony, peace the world over are now spread across the globe in nearly 30 countries.
Vyasa University: Using scientific research to bring Yoga into the modern world!</description></item><item><title>How QAChef Is Reaching Clients In A Tough Market</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</guid><description>The hospitality business is in a hard place right now because of Covid 19.
QAChef is a technology company which digitizes food safety compliance processes through a single handheld device, thus enabling unprecedented ingredient-to-customer food traceability and greater efficiency and productivity.
QAChef&amp;#39;s handheld device being used to measure temperature during cooking So QAChef is in a fantastic position, a ready for market product which enhances traceability across large scale food production - perfect given the focus on food safety and associated health implications in the wake of the Covid-19 pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Video Translation And Its Implications For FireTech</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</guid><description>A recent interview with FireTech Connect was really good fun, with Leigh Kelson hosting a free-wheeling discussion about crisis, technology and the future of AI in the internationalization and localization space.
FireTech Connect The FireTech 2020 program is an initiative of the Peregian Digital Hub, a leading technology incubator based in Noosa on Queensland&amp;rsquo;s Sunshine Coast.
FireTech Connect is funded by the Department of Industry, Science, Energy and Resources through the AusIndustry Entrepreneurs’ Programme; The Queensland State Government&amp;rsquo;s Advance Queensland Program; and Noosa Shire Council.</description></item><item><title>How Subtitling Can Boost ROI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</guid><description>Today we look at how to boost ROI or ROAS across your video production lifecycle, and how to make structural decisions which will pay off over a long time frame.
ROI or ROAS: Which One Should I Use? It&amp;rsquo;s actually a pretty messy question, but here are the basics.
ROI: Return on Investment Getting a definition is the starting point, and according to the smart folks at Investopia:
Return on Investment (ROI) is a performance measure used to evaluate the efficiency of an investment or compare the efficiency of a number of different investments.</description></item><item><title>AI Localisation: Help Me Help You</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-localisation-help-me-help-you/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-localisation-help-me-help-you/</guid><description>Today we look at AI localisation. Essentially, how to use AI to reach a broader market at scale.
Its a really simple question. Does AI Localisation work at scale?
As always, the answer is yes and no, but mostly it depends on what you are trying to do.
The context is this: localisation project managers often burn themselves out by performing tons of routine operations every single day.
So the question becomes, how to use AI localisation at scale, and then, how to best use AI in localisation efforts at the process level?</description></item><item><title>Video SEO: Keywords, Titles, Descriptions And The Transcript</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-seo-keywords-titles-descriptions-and-the-transcript/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-seo-keywords-titles-descriptions-and-the-transcript/</guid><description>This post is dedicated to simple rules to maximise your SEO (Search Engine Optimisation) impact with video content.
There are 4 things you need to do to maximise your video content&amp;rsquo;s SEO impact. They are, title, description, keywords and the transcript, we will look at each one of these in detail.
Why Do Video SEO? From this DeepCrawl article, search engines cannot index video content. This is because search engines can only index text content.</description></item><item><title>How To Do Video SEO Right</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-do-video-seo-right/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-do-video-seo-right/</guid><description>There are a large number of reasons as to why people create content. Here is the one thing all content creators have in common.
They need to market their content. And step one is thinking about Search Engine Optimisation (SEO).
This blog post covers what you need to know about making video content indexable, and hence searchable.
Read on to understand what you need to do to make your video SEO friendly!</description></item><item><title>Video Series: How to Quickly Transcribe Your Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-series-how-to-quickly-transcribe-your-video/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-series-how-to-quickly-transcribe-your-video/</guid><description>The QuickTranscribe feature is our most used feature in the video transcription and translation process.
Our easy how-to guide on using the Quick Transcribe feature. For more information on Quick Transcribe visit our written guide here.
How to quickly transcribe your video
We are very grateful for your support!
Please connect with us on LinkedIn, YouTube or Facebook for any comments, questions, or just to keep up to date with the work we do!</description></item><item><title>A Step by Step Guide to Translating Your First Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-step-by-step-guide-to-translating-your-first-video/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-step-by-step-guide-to-translating-your-first-video/</guid><description>Having the ability to translate your video into a number of different languages and dialects puts your business a step ahead of the rest in means of reaching a larger audience and in turn, customers.
But getting your content translated and transcribed into another language seems expensive and time consuming, right?
Good news, friend. You&amp;rsquo;re wrong!
Dubbing and/or subtitling your video is a quick and easy process if you&amp;rsquo;re using our app and we hope that&amp;rsquo;s why you&amp;rsquo;re here&amp;hellip; to find out how to do it.</description></item><item><title>What Is The Best Subtitling Software Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-is-the-best-subtitling-software-available/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-is-the-best-subtitling-software-available/</guid><description>Are you a content creator? Or Are you a court reporter looking for an easy way to caption lots of content? This blog post might be for you.
Having captions is very useful these days. Its really good for engagement, and its also really good for accessibility - specifically hearing impaired folk.
However, and there is no getting around this, it is painful to do.
Manual audio or video transcription takes ages.</description></item><item><title>How Safe Is AI Transcription: What You Need To Know</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-safe-is-ai-transcription-what-you-need-to-know/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-safe-is-ai-transcription-what-you-need-to-know/</guid><description>You are a content creator who uses AI.
But how safe is the AI you use, whether for transcription, translation or dubbing. Also some tips on how to use AI better in your journey into expanding your market.
There was a great article on this recently at How-To-Geek.
Ok - so why do you use AI? As a content creator you care about engagement. AI Transcription combined with Open Captions is fantastic for engagement.</description></item><item><title>Translate Your English Video Into Filipino And Chinese</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</guid><description>Business today relies on content creation. How do you expand your market? We show you how to add open captions for accessibility wins, and translate your video content into Tagalog and Chinese to expand your target client base!
Matija Squire is a LinkedIn coach, all round nice person plus a good friend. And she is doing something really cool!
We all know Covid-19 has distrupted all our lives. Some of us are lucky enough to be able to earn an income by working from home online.</description></item><item><title>How To Translate YouTube Videos And Dominate SEO</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</guid><description>The basic steps to translate a YouTube video are:
Download the video to your computer. Upload the video into an AI transcription service. Get the transcript in an .srt file. Translate the transcript using an AI translation service. Embed the translation into your video. You should only translate videos that you expect a good Return On Investment from - so you have a good feeling this video will work in a different language.</description></item><item><title>Clipping Chinese App: How To Translate Video Into Mandarin Chinese With AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</guid><description>One very common use case of video translator is as a Chinese clipping app. What is a Chinese clipping app?
This term is used by content creators to mean how to translate a video from English to Chinese, and they generally mean a short video for various social media channels.
In this blog post we are going to look at how to translate a small video from English to Mandarin (Simplified Chinese).</description></item><item><title>How AI Dubbing Will Change Everything: Building A Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</guid><description>There is a very interesting piece of content we are looking at today. A team from IIIT-H (Indian Institute of Information Technology - Hyderabad) has build an AI which translates and lip-syncs a video from one language to another.
This originally came to our attention in this article from the folks at TNW. The paper this article is based on is here, and if you are interested in AI/Language you should absolutely have a look.</description></item><item><title>How AI Transcription Fails And What To Do About It</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</guid><description>AI Transcription has been all the rage recently. Several companies have been coming out with new products to meet this requirement.
What does it mean? Does it work? How to evaluate these products? We take a look and try to think behind the hype.
First we look at some of the incoming offerings. Then some issues with AI Transcription and Translation.
Incoming Offerings There is a very large number of AI products hitting the market place.</description></item><item><title>One Igbo Woman Trying To Save Her Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</guid><description>Oddly, its the feel-good stories which we think are the most important. This week we had a few stories come by which show much progress is being made in the popularity of regional languages.
Here at VideoTranslator we feel that most people are quite proud of where they come from - its totally natural.
Each one of us has a story of how we came to be, and the stories of those who came before are a vital part of any human identity.</description></item><item><title>How To Reach Gen Z Using AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we keep an eye on what everyone else is doing.
Well, we try to anyways. And one of the better resources out there is Social Media Today. This article, &amp;lsquo;What Gen Z is Watching Online - and What That Means for Marketers in 2020&amp;rsquo; is full of wonderful titbits about how to think about video.
How Gen Z Is Using YouTube The big takeaway from the article is that Vlogging and Informative Videos are the biggest draws.</description></item><item><title>Clients: Why You Make Me Blush!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:02 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we get lots of feedback from clients. Most of it is good, some of it not so much. Recently, as we have started to build out our retail client base it has become interesting.
The product challenge with retail is quite different from an enterprise offering or a managed service. Because the user is not being paid to use the product (or being told to by their manager) expectations for the product are totally different.</description></item><item><title>Accessibility: Why It Matters And How To Avoid Being Sued</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work with clients who are part of the healthcare ecosystem.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, voice over artists, or in this case, nurses/doctors. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing - we are technologists who are trying to service our clients to the best of our ability.
Every now and then a story turns up which brings a lot of our work into sharp focus.</description></item><item><title>Quick Transcribe: For When You Need To Get Transcription Done Quickly</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator.Ai, we work closely with the Internationalization And Localization industry. This industry has many different participants, and they use our technology in different ways.
As a software firm, the hardest thing is to really understand what our clients do and why they do these things. Sounds funny, but it is true.
We had a strong response to our previous article, 3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency, and a number of questions and suggestions.</description></item><item><title>Mr Sh*thole: What To Do When Your AI Misbehaves</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</guid><description>Today we look at a humorous articles which look at what happens when AI goes wrong. Here at video translator we like to keep abreast of the latest news in the intersection of Artificial Intelligence, Natural Language Programming, Human Languages and Culture.
Read on to find out how Facebook&amp;rsquo;s AI got in trouble, and why Oracle thinks replacing your manager with a robot is likely, and a good thing to boot!</description></item><item><title>What Arabic Voices are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</guid><description>Previously we&amp;rsquo;ve gone through the list of our English speaking AI and the different dialects they speak. You can see them all here.
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re looking at our Arabic speaking AI and the different dialects and voices available.
If you need a reminder as to how to select the appropriate AI language and dialect, check out our article here.
Now, on to the voices! We&amp;rsquo;ve used the phrase birds of a feather, flock together or الطيور على أشكالها تقع for our AI to say each time for the examples.</description></item><item><title>Extra! Extra! Read all about it!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/extra-extra-read-all-about-it/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/extra-extra-read-all-about-it/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of exciting developments at VideoTranslator, which means exciting things for you! This means that you&amp;rsquo;ll be hearing more from us going forward in the form of a weekly email.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t subscribed to our mailing list or signed up for a free trial yet, please do so here.
The email will be featuring the latest articles we&amp;rsquo;ve posted which will be like the following:
What English Dialects are Available?</description></item><item><title>Where are we heading with AI computing in the 2020s? And how human can they really become?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/where-are-we-heading-with-ai-computing-in-the-2020s-and-how-human-can-they-really-become/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/where-are-we-heading-with-ai-computing-in-the-2020s-and-how-human-can-they-really-become/</guid><description>We now well and truly know that Artificial Intelligence is here to stay (and in fact has been for quite some time), but what will become of it, and us, in the future? One author has some very interesting thoughts on how AI computing will reach beyond just recognising how to act like a human but rather see the world the way we do and have a form of common sense.</description></item><item><title>3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work in what is called the Internationalization And Localization industry.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
When do we do this work for our clients? Generally when a client needs a managed service. This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays from VideoTranslator!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-hoidays-from-videotranslator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-hoidays-from-videotranslator/</guid><description>What a year it&amp;rsquo;s been! From our launch in May we would not have believed we&amp;rsquo;d come so far in such a short amount of time.
Thank You Thank you everyone for all your support! We want to wish you and yours a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year. We hope you have a brilliant 2020!
Everyone who engaged with us, others that offered feedback, and folks who made a purchasing decision - thank you very much.</description></item><item><title>What English Dialects are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-english-dialects-are-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-english-dialects-are-available/</guid><description>Did you know that our AI can speak in over 180 languages and more than 120 differing dialects and different genders? It&amp;rsquo;s true! That&amp;rsquo;s one smart robot ;)
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re focusing on English and the four different dialects that you can choose from when using our app.
For those that have you used the app before, you will notice that we have renamed the &amp;ldquo;voices&amp;rdquo;. Previously we had them named as EN-IN-P-M1, or UK-S4-M which didn&amp;rsquo;t make a lot of sense for those who were unfamiliar with the technology.</description></item><item><title>Open Captions: Enhancements November 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/open-captions-enhancements-november-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/open-captions-enhancements-november-2019/</guid><description>Working with a prospect, we added a number of enhancements to our open captions workflow. If you are interested in what open captions are and what its use cases are please have a look at this blog post.
Very simply open captions are generally used as an accessibility tool focused on people who have hearing impairments. More recently due to the rise of streaming services, open captions have been making a come back.</description></item><item><title>Transcribing Indian English: A Simple Guide To Using AI To Speed Up Transcription And Add Open Captions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcribing-indian-english-a-simple-guide-to-using-ai-to-speed-up-transcription-and-add-open-captions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcribing-indian-english-a-simple-guide-to-using-ai-to-speed-up-transcription-and-add-open-captions/</guid><description>Today we are going to look at how to transcribe Indian English. Firstly of course, what is Indian English, and what does it sound like? How many such dialects exist? Have a look.
Now that we know what Indian English sounds like, we are going to use a short clip from Rajya Sabha TV, an Indian government content creator. We use our AI to transcribe this clip.
Lastly, we add an Auto-Overlay so that we can show you the video.</description></item><item><title>Samples From A Voice Over Robot: French, German and Dutch</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</guid><description>Following on from last week&amp;rsquo;s blog post, where we looked at different English dialects, we are going to do much the same today in Dutch, French and German.
Do you like the below examples? Let us know - we are super keen to hear what you think?
To try other languages (for FREE!) sign up to the free trial and give it a go!
Steps First, as per our usual create a new item using the English language template.</description></item><item><title>AI Dubbing: What Different Dialects Of English Sound Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</guid><description>Today we are going to look AI dubbing and look at a few different samples of what an AI can sound like in English. We are going to do something pretty simple, we will use the quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog for our seed text.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what this sentence is, quoting from Wikipedia, &amp;ldquo;The quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog&amp;rdquo; is an English-language pangram—a sentence that contains all of the letters of the alphabet.</description></item><item><title>AI Transcription, Translation And Dubbing: How To Think About Accuracy</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-transcription-translation-and-dubbing-how-to-think-about-accuracy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-transcription-translation-and-dubbing-how-to-think-about-accuracy/</guid><description>We get a number of questions around AI Accuracy, and depending on the context, the question can refer to a number of things.
Wanted to put down a note describing the various iterations of what Accuracy in Artificial Intelligence refers to, and where it is going from my point of view.
Is the AI accurate? Is AI accurate when it comes to Transcription? Is AI accurate when it comes to Translation?</description></item><item><title>Text-To-Speech: AI Dubbing And What You Can Do With It</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/text-to-speech-ai-dubbing-and-what-you-can-do-with-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/text-to-speech-ai-dubbing-and-what-you-can-do-with-it/</guid><description>Today we are going to look AI dubbing and its various use cases. If you are wondering, is my content suitable for AI dubbing, or AI localisation? In simple terms:
What is dubbing or dub localisation? Should I use a human, or a machine for my dubbing? How do I use a video translator to dub my video? Rules of thumb, or heuristics, to achieve a superior outcome with AI dubbing?</description></item><item><title>Transcripción y Traducción de Videos de Español a Inglés</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcripci%C3%B3n-y-traducci%C3%B3n-de-videos-de-espa%C3%B1ol-a-ingl%C3%A9s/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcripci%C3%B3n-y-traducci%C3%B3n-de-videos-de-espa%C3%B1ol-a-ingl%C3%A9s/</guid><description>Este video pertenece al canal de YouTube Mariel de Viaje.
El video ofrece consejos básicos para afrontar con facilidad, comodidad y familiaridad cualquier viaje en plan turístico a la República Dominicana, e incluye sugerencias para visitar lugares emblemáticos como Punta Cana y Santo Domingo.
La República Dominicana es el segundo país más grande y diverso del Caribe. Cuenta con vuelos directos desde las principales ciudades de Latinoamérica, Estados Unidos, Canadá y Europa, es un país que se destaca por la calidez de su clima y la hospitalidad de su gente.</description></item><item><title>Transcripción y Traducción de Videos de Inglés a Español</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcripci%C3%B3n-y-traducci%C3%B3n-de-videos-de-ingl%C3%A9s-a-espa%C3%B1ol/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcripci%C3%B3n-y-traducci%C3%B3n-de-videos-de-ingl%C3%A9s-a-espa%C3%B1ol/</guid><description>Este video pertenece al canal de YouTube History Matters. El video habla sobre el personaje histórico ruso con repercusiones en la historia universal, Ivan El Terrible.
Iván IV Vasílievich, llamado Iván el Terrible, fue un gran príncipe de Moscú y de toda Rusia, además de ser el primer monarca ruso en adoptar el título de Zar. Es considerado como uno de los creadores del Estado Ruso.
Pasos A Seguir Abre tu navegador y dirígete a videotranslator.</description></item><item><title>Translating Your Video From English To French: A Step By Step Guide</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translating-your-video-from-english-to-french-a-step-by-step-guide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translating-your-video-from-english-to-french-a-step-by-step-guide/</guid><description>The Sydney Opera House is one of the most well known landmarks in the world. With over 10.9 million people visiting it each year, it&amp;rsquo;s obviously one of Australia&amp;rsquo;s hottest tourist spots.
When searching online, the official videos for the Opera House are all in English, which is great for English speakers, but what about those who aren&amp;rsquo;t?
Using the videotranslator.ai app and creating translated videos would be a great way to reach millions of people worldwide who aren&amp;rsquo;t native English speakers.</description></item><item><title>Why Post Video To Social Media: 3 Tips</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-post-video-to-social-media-3-tips/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-post-video-to-social-media-3-tips/</guid><description>Several recent reports show that video content outperforms every other type of post on social media. In other words, using video content in social media marketing is a very good strategy. In this post we look at some numbers, and try to work out what this means for content creators and marketers.
Renderforest put together an insightful report on social video marketing. Here are some of their statistics:
100 million hours of video per day is watched on Facebook.</description></item><item><title>How Video Transcription Works Explainer</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-video-transcription-works-explainer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-video-transcription-works-explainer/</guid><description>We have been working really hard making a number of changes to our underlying application. Specifically we have (i) added a new architecture to our video processing, (ii) added a few more languages, (iii) large number of changes to the look/feel of the product.
All in all, we felt it was time for a new explainer video which covered how to use the platform.
Here it is&amp;hellip; enjoy!
How To Transcribe A Video Using AI Explainer: How to Transcribe A Video Using AI</description></item><item><title>Subtitling For The Win</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/subtitling-for-the-win/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/subtitling-for-the-win/</guid><description>It started with a Tweet, which was then picked up by the Guardian, re-Tweeted and the rest is history. The post got re-tweeted 70K+ times, and liked 74K+ times. That is clearly something which struck a cord. Why?
Who is using subtitles or captions, why are they using it, and how can you also use subtitles or captions. For a technical discussion on subtitles or captions, see this. This post is more about the value in subtitles or captions.</description></item><item><title>The Growing Pains Of Diversity And A Possible Solution</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-growing-pains-of-diversity-and-a-possible-solution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-growing-pains-of-diversity-and-a-possible-solution/</guid><description>This post is not really about diversity. It is about the granular challenges around governance in an increasingly complex world, and operational solutions which may work going forward.
We look at three events which took place in this week. What the problem is, and what a solution might be. These events are:
Trump Administration’s Deregulation Drive Begins to Impact Language Industry Sometimes Lost In Translation, With Dialects Context Is Key Translating verdicts will help all litigants Trump Administration’s Deregulation Drive Begins to Impact Language Industry US federal regulations have generally favored the language services industry.</description></item><item><title>How We Used SEO To Come Up With A New Name</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-we-used-seo-to-come-up-with-a-new-name/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-we-used-seo-to-come-up-with-a-new-name/</guid><description>Our original name was QBL Media, and our new name is videotranslator.ai. The original name did not really work, and was always a temporary name.
This post covers some of the context of where our platform came from, and what changes happened in the course of getting this app to market, including a pivot.
We used SEO to determine a new name. Read on to understand why this was done, how it was done, and what benefits we expect to get from the name change.</description></item><item><title>How Do I Make Subtitles And Closed Captions?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-do-i-make-subtitles-and-closed-captions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-do-i-make-subtitles-and-closed-captions/</guid><description>Many clients ask how us about subtitles. Generally, this is the first question a prospect asks us about our platform. In practise, they mean a few different things.
We want subtitles for our audio/video content. We have subtitles, but want to make changes to the timing. We want to embed our subtitles into our video file, for use in Social Media. Let us look at these questions in detail.</description></item><item><title>मोम का हाथ बनाने की कला: अंग्रेजी से हिंदी मे वीडियो अनुवादित</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A5-%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%A8%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%A4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A5-%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%A8%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%A4/</guid><description>यह वीडियो मैडम तुसाद सिडनी यूट्यूब पृष्ठ से है और यह मैडम तुसाद सिडनी में मोम के हाथ बनाने के बारे में है, जहां वे तरल मोम से लोगों के हाथ के नक्से, कुछ सरल चरणों का पालन करके बनाते है।
प्रक्रिया के अनुसार ठंडे पानी में लोगों के हाथों को डुबोना, और फिर तरल मोम में उनके हाथ डुबोने शामिल है । यह करीब 5 बार दोहराया जाता है, हाथों का सांचा बनाने के लिए ।</description></item><item><title>The Art Of Making Wax Hands: English To Hindi Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-art-of-making-wax-hands-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-art-of-making-wax-hands-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</guid><description>This video is from Madame Tussauds Sydney&amp;rsquo;s Youtube page and it is about making wax hands at Madame Tussauds Sydney, where they make moulds of people hands out of liquid wax, by following a few simple steps.
The process involves dipping people hands into cold water, and then dipping their hands in liquid wax. This is repeated about 5 times, to make a mould of the hands.
The Art Of Making Wax Hands: English Video Translation From English To Hindi</description></item><item><title>एक प्रकृति की कला बंगू यिलबारा संग्रह: अंग्रेजी से हिंदी वीडियो प्रतिलेखन और अनुवाद</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%83%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%82-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%B9-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%83%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%82-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%B9-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</guid><description>हमें यह वीडियो म्यूजियम ऑफ कंटेम्पररी आर्ट् ऑस्ट्रेलिया के वेबसाइट के यूट्यूब पृष्ठ से मिला है ।
यह वीडियो एमसीए कलेक्शन के बंगू यिलबारा कला के बारे में है । बंगू यिलबारा शब्द अपने आप में कला के प्रयास का वर्णन है, और उस काम को बनाने का इरादा के लिए , प्रदर्शनी के लिए काम का वर्णन करने पर ज्यादा ध्यान केंद्रित नहीं करना है।
प्रदर्शनी कुछ अतिरिक्त लेबल के बिना जीवन की वास्तविकता के साथ संपर्क में लाने के लिए, प्रयास और दृष्टि के लिए कलाकार अभ्यास से संबंधित कला को प्रदर्शित करने पर केंद्रित है।</description></item><item><title>A Nature Of Art Bangu Yilbara Collection: English To Hindi Video Transcription And Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-nature-of-art-bangu-yilbara-collection-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-nature-of-art-bangu-yilbara-collection-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</guid><description>We got this video from Museum of Contemporary Art Australia&amp;rsquo;s Youtube page This video is about Bangu Yilbara collection at the MCA. The collection is focused on art produced by the Aboriginal and Torres Straits Islander cultures.
The exhibition focuses on the diversity of Aboriginal and Torres Straits Islander culture, primarily by looking to the artists to define their work, as opposed to labelling the work &amp;lsquo;Aboriginal&amp;rsquo; and boxing it into any particular style.</description></item><item><title>A Journey Through Australian Fashion: English To Hindi Video Transcription And Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-journey-through-australian-fashion-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-journey-through-australian-fashion-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</guid><description>This video is from Museum of Applied Arts and Sciences Youtube channel. This video is about the garments and design collection at the Museum of Applied Arts and Sciences (MAAS).
The garment collection covers pieces from the 18th century to present day examples. These are shown at the new Centre For Fashion at MAAS. There are around 30,000 amazing pieces in total, which MAAS hopes will impact and inspire future generations of fashion designers.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guide: Audio To Text</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-audio-to-text/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-audio-to-text/</guid><description>This post covers how to transcribe audio content. We will use a podcast as our sample audio content, and assume you are on a free trial. This post covers:
Sign into the application. Create an audio specific template. Create a new item, with our audio specific template as parent. Upload our podcast, and then use an Artificial Intelligence (AI) to transcribe our content. On reviewing this visual guide, you will be able to upload your own audio content, and transcribe using an AI.</description></item><item><title>वीडियो अनुवाद किया गया अंग्रेजी से हिंदी में: एक कोन्विक्ट हेरिटेज</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%97%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%97%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C/</guid><description>आज का वीडियो हयडे पार्क बैरक्स म्यूजियमस से है। यूटूब पेज, विशेष रूप से यह वीडियो है । हम इस वीडियो को अंग्रेजी से हिंदी में बदल देंगे ।
हाइडल पार्क बैरक्स म्यूजियम नवीनीकरण के दौर से गुजर रहा है । इस 2019 के अंत तक पूरा होने की उम्मीद है । क्यूरेटर और शोधकर्ताओं द्वारा नए शोध की एक बड़ी मात्रा हाइड पार्क बैरक में स्थित संग्रहालय को फिर से खोलने के बाद दिखाए जाने की उम्मीद है। यह नया प्रदर्शन ऑस्ट्रेलिया की सिद्धदोष विरासत के बारे में है । प्रारंभिक औपनिवेशिक ऑस्ट्रेलिया में अपराधियों के प्रभाव का दस्तावेजीकरण किया गया है, आंखों के माध्यम से देखा स्थानीय आदिवासी लोगों, और बसने वाले दोनों ने।</description></item><item><title>Video Translation From English To Hindi: A Convict Heritage</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-from-english-to-hindi-a-convict-heritage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-from-english-to-hindi-a-convict-heritage/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s video is from the Hyde Park Barracks Museum&amp;rsquo;s Youtube page, specifically this video. We will convert this video from English to Hindi.
Hyde Park Barracks Museum is undergoing a refurbishment. This is expected to be complete late 2019. A large amount of new research by curators and researchers based at Hyde Park Barracks is also expected to be shown once the museum is reopened.
This new exhibit is about Australia&amp;rsquo;s convict heritage.</description></item><item><title>How To Reach Refugees, And Combat People Smugglers, With AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-refugees-and-combat-people-smugglers-with-ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-refugees-and-combat-people-smugglers-with-ai/</guid><description>Video translation is all the rage in Sydney currently. It sounds hard to believe, but this is honestly the case at the moment. The controversy revolves around a secret video, which the current Australian Prime Minister, Scott Morrison has (apparently) recorded.
The gist of the news is that the Australian Prime Minister has recorded a video, which will be translated into a number of languages. Once translated, the video will be broadcast in the media in different countries including Indonesia, Malaysia, Thailand, Pakistan, Bangladesh, Sri Lanka, Afghanistan and Iraq.</description></item><item><title>How To Use AI To Save Lions, In Afrikaans</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-ai-to-save-lions-in-afrikaans/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-ai-to-save-lions-in-afrikaans/</guid><description>As part of our process for testing the platform prior to go live, one of the things we look to do is test a large number of different languages. Part of it is good fun, the other objective is to try to change things around to see if we can break the platform and find bugs.
Realistically, this means looking for cool videos, and then trying things out with the videos.</description></item><item><title>How To Transcribe Lots of Different Accents Accurately</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-lots-of-different-accents-accurately/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-lots-of-different-accents-accurately/</guid><description>Today, we will look at how to transcribe many different accents correctly. First off, what does this question even mean in terms of AI?
The video we are working with is from Institute for Communication in Health Care (ICH) at the Australian National University (ANU).
Looking at the ICH&amp;rsquo;s mission statement, &amp;ldquo;The ICH’s mission is to build an international, collaborative research and training hub in healthcare communication to improve patient safety and quality of healthcare practice around the world&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>How To Get The Most Out Of Your AI: English To Hindi Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-get-the-most-out-of-your-ai-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-get-the-most-out-of-your-ai-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</guid><description>Today, we will cover simple heuristics to get the most out of your AI. As always, use the AI to do the heavy lifting, and use a human subject matter expert to finesse the results, producing a superior outcome with less time/effort.
The process followed is:
Transcribe the Gram Marg (literally, &amp;lsquo;road map&amp;rsquo; in Hindi) video using Indian English. Clean up the transcribed Gram Marg video, and present simple heuristics to the the most out of your AI.</description></item><item><title>How To Transcribe English Into Hebrew: ChangePlan</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-english-into-hebrew-changeplan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-english-into-hebrew-changeplan/</guid><description>Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here. Today, we will be using the video translation platform on a video from our friends at ChangePlan. We will do the following:
Transcribe ChangePlan&amp;rsquo;s video using Australian English. Fix up spelling/grammar in our captions. Translate ChangePlan&amp;rsquo;s video from English -&amp;gt; Hebrew. If you are looking to replicate this process, please note, after the translation step, it is highly recommended that you have a Hebrew qualified subject-matter expert finesse the captions.</description></item><item><title>How To Transcribe A Foreign Language Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-a-foreign-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-a-foreign-language/</guid><description>Today we are going to look at how to transcribe a foreign language video. But how does this work when we live in a globalised world where people are from many different places - exactly what is foreign?
Well, Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here.
What we are looking at today, is how to transcribe a video in an language you do not know.</description></item><item><title>English To German Video Translation: What is a Babybündel?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/english-to-german-video-translation-what-is-a-babyb%C3%BCndel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/english-to-german-video-translation-what-is-a-babyb%C3%BCndel/</guid><description>Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here. What we are going to do today is transcribe content to a different language, and use a practical example to demonstrate the technology.
We will be using this video, from the team at NSWHealth. The video is a simple, but effective solution for young mothers, where NSWHealth provide a useful box of household items aimed at first time mothers.</description></item><item><title>More Text-To-Speech Transcription!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/more-text-to-speech-transcription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/more-text-to-speech-transcription/</guid><description>Our platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here. Recently, we added a number of additional languages specific to Text-To-Speech transcription. These are, (a) French (Canadian), (b) Portuguese (Brazilian), (c) Spanish, (d) Swedish, and (e) Turkish.
In total, Text-To-Speech transcription now has the below set of languages available. Please note each language has multiple dialects, and gender specific voices are available.</description></item><item><title>What Languages Are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-languages-are-available/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-languages-are-available/</guid><description>We look at the number of languages which you can use with your content. Remember, each languages is potentially a new market, and care needs to be taken to properly target your preferred leads.
There are two kinds of transcription, the first is Speech-To-Text Transcription, the second is a Text-To-Speech Transcription. In both cases, speech is involved, hence these are referred to as transcription AI&amp;rsquo;s. Similarly, with translation, what we are actually using is a Text-To-Text Translation AI.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Transcribe a Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-transcribe-a-video/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 16:45:05 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-transcribe-a-video/</guid><description>We look at how to transcribe video content. From Wikipedia, &amp;lsquo;Transcription in the linguistic sense is the systematic representation of language in written form. The source can either be utterances (speech or sign language) or pre-existing text in another writing system.&amp;rsquo;
In brief, we will (i) upload our content, (ii) trigger transcription, and (iii) download a video with our embedded transcript. To transcribe your existing video content, please follow the below steps.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/welcome-to-video-translator/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 11:16:52 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/welcome-to-video-translator/</guid><description>Welcome to the Video Translator. We are a Sydney based, media focused technology platform provider, looking to make the world a more accessible place. Our primary value proposition is a translation platform, with a focus on video translation.
Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s translation platform (&amp;ldquo;the application&amp;rdquo;) is an Internet-enabled SaaS (Software as a Service) platform which assists content creators (&amp;ldquo;the client&amp;rdquo;) to engage with stakeholders (&amp;ldquo;the audience&amp;rdquo;) from different linguistic backgrounds. The application is used to convert hypermedia content from one language to another, using an Artificial Intelligence (AI) assisted process.</description></item></channel></rss>