<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Video transcription on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/video-transcription/</link><description>Recent content in Video transcription on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/video-transcription/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Different Ways To Reduce Audio Background Noise</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/reduce-background-noise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/reduce-background-noise/</guid><description>We all know how annoying it can be to listen to noisy audio.
Professionals who do speech-to-text transcription on a daily basis sure can relate to this matter.
Your audio quality matters when you are doing the transcription process, especially if what you are trying to transcribe is an important matter, such as a legal case.
If your audio is filled with loud background noises, not only that it will be hard for the AI to automatically transcribe your audio but also for a human to manually transcribe it.</description></item><item><title>Cara Menambahkan Subtitle Ke Video YouTube, Facebook dan LinkedIn</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tambah-subtitle-youtube-facebook-linkedin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tambah-subtitle-youtube-facebook-linkedin/</guid><description>Hello semuanya!
Kembali lagi bersama Video Translator dimana kami akan memberikan tips and tricks tentang dunia media dan terjemahan.
Di artikel sebelumnya, kami sudah membahas cara agar kalian bisa membuat file SRT.
Kali ini, kami akan membahas gimana caranya kalian bisa menambahkan subtitle ke video kalian di YouTube, Facebook maupun LinkedIn.
Ayo, kita mulai!
Menambahkan Subtitle Ke YouTube Kalian pernah nggak lagi nonton video YouTube di tempat umum dan suara videonya nggak kedengeran gara-gara suara di sekitar kalian lebih kenceng dari pada suara videonya?</description></item><item><title>How To Add Subtitles To YouTube, Facebook and LinkedIn Videos</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-add-subtitle-youtube-facebook-linkedin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-add-subtitle-youtube-facebook-linkedin/</guid><description>Hello lovely people!
Welcome back to VideoTranslator support where we will be telling you the tips and tricks regarding the media and translation world.
In the previous post, we have written about how you can create, import, and edit SRT files.
This time, we will be explaining how you can add subtitles to your YouTube, Facebook, and LinkedIn video.
So, without further ado, let&amp;rsquo;s begin!
Adding Subtitles To YouTube Videos Have you ever been on noisy public transport rides and struggled to watch your favorite YouTuber&amp;rsquo;s video?</description></item><item><title>How To Import And Edit SRT File To Adobe Premiere Pro</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/import-and-edit-srt-file-to-adobe-premiere-pro-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/import-and-edit-srt-file-to-adobe-premiere-pro-/</guid><description>Hello, fam!
Welcome back again to VideoTranslator support where we will be telling you the tips and tricks regarding the media and translation world.
This time, we will be explaining how you can import and edit SRT files to Adobe Premiere Pro.
Before we begin, let&amp;rsquo;s explain what an SRT file is first&amp;hellip;
What Is SRT? SRT is a plain-text file that contains critical information regarding subtitles, including the start and end timecodes of your text to ensure your subtitles match your audio, and the sequential number of subtitles.</description></item><item><title>Review Aplikasi Splice Untuk Mengedit Video Di Iphone</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/review-aplikasi-splice-untuk-mengedit-video-di-iphone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/review-aplikasi-splice-untuk-mengedit-video-di-iphone/</guid><description>Halo, semuanya!
Beberapa minggu yang lalu, kita baru aja ngeupload artikel tentang 9 video editor terbaik untuk iOS.
Nah, salah satu aplikasi yang kita tampilkan adalah Splice.
Kali ini, kita bakalan memberikan review jujur tentang aplikasi editor video Splice!
Apa Itu Splice Splice adalah aplikasi pengeditan video gratis dari pencipta GoPro.
Aplikasi ini mengklaim bahwa mereka memungkinkan pengguna untuk:
Memotong klip video Menyesuaikan kecepatan video Menghapus latar belakang video Menambahkan filter dan efek pada video Menambahkan judul, overlay teks, dan outro Membuat tayangan slide video Apa Yang Akan Kami Ulaskan Di artikel kali ini, kami akan mengulas tentang seberapa bagus Splice dalam:</description></item><item><title>Reviewing Splice Video Editor on iPhone</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/reviewing-splice-video-editor-on-iphone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/reviewing-splice-video-editor-on-iphone/</guid><description>Hello, fam!
A few weeks back, we have just released an article about the 9 of iOS top video editing apps.
One of the apps that we mentioned in that article is Splice.
So, today, we are going to give you our honest review of the video editing app Splice!
What Is Splice Splice is a free video editing app from the creators of GoPro.
The app claims that it will allow users to:</description></item><item><title>10 TikTok Content Ideas</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/10-tiktok-content-ideas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/10-tiktok-content-ideas/</guid><description>We know that you&amp;rsquo;ve been guilty of spending hours and hours scrolling through your ForYou page on TikTok.
The microblogging app called Tik Tok is the trend these days. Most of the viral videos online come from this platform.
You know as well as we do that TikTok can bring you a lot of traction. So, you also want to make TikTok videos. However, you don’t know what contents you should post.</description></item><item><title>Leaving A Long-Lasting Legacy: Curating Your Family’s History</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/leaving-a-long-lasting-legacy-by-curating-your-familys-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/leaving-a-long-lasting-legacy-by-curating-your-familys-history/</guid><description>I believe everyone wants to leave a legacy.
Many people choose to pass on their homes, investments and possessions.
For Jeff Dormish, leaving a legacy means so much more than that. He does not just want to leave possessions; he wants to pass on his history.
For many Americans, most of their ancestors came from Europe in the great emigration wave before the First World War. Jeff Dormish’s ancestors also came from Europe, Slovenia, to be exact.</description></item><item><title>How To Conveniently Translate Your Videos</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-conveniently-translate-your-videos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-conveniently-translate-your-videos/</guid><description>Many of you would have heard about translation. According to Kristen Malmkjær, translation is an activity that aims to convey meaning or meanings of a given linguistic discourse from one language to another.
What are the difficulties in translation? As a multilingual speaker, I have frequently asked to translate different languages. My family would ask me to translate files such as reports, articles and legal documents. However, translation also comes with its challenges.</description></item><item><title>Why Should You Translate Video Content: A Client Perspective</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-translate-video-content-a-client-perspective/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-translate-video-content-a-client-perspective/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we do a lot of work in the Internationalization And Localization industry.
But we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.
Sometimes however, the most useful thing we can do is just have a conversation.</description></item><item><title>The Implications Of AI Adoption In Our Tools</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-implications-of-ai-adoption-in-our-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-implications-of-ai-adoption-in-our-tools/</guid><description>AI is everywhere in the news these days. But something critical has changed recently.
In the near past, AI has gone from being super fancy to being, well... pedestrian.
Say what now?
Well - AI is becoming ordinary. And turning up in our office/productivity toolkits.
In recent days, Google has expanded its offering using AI, as has Microsoft, and so has Amazon.
What does this mean for how we work, and how can you use this trend to advantage your business?</description></item><item><title>How NSW Health Is Using Video Translation To Empower Occupational Therapists</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</guid><description>One major challenge in diverse societies is the provision of healthcare services.
In western Sydney, this problem is directly tackled by the South-West Sydney Local Health District, which sits under New South Wales Health.
Ok - so obviously this is complicated stuff. But how does video translation help?
If you don't speak good English, specifically business English, finding information is very hard. The doctor is the only resource who can help, but what happens when they don't speak your language?</description></item><item><title>Why YouTube Stopped Community Caption Contributions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</guid><description>Community captions are a function in YouTube. This function allows a YouTube content creator to crowd source captions for their video content.
YouTube is shutting this down. Here is how it will affect you!
Change To Community Contributions On YouTube Notice about an upcoming change to community contributions on YouTube Both creators and viewers have reported problems with the community contributions feature, including spam, abuse, and low quality submissions.</description></item><item><title>How Vyasa University Is Fighting Covid With Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</guid><description>Vivekananda Yoga Anusandhana Samsthana or VYASA is a registered charitable institution (1986) working to make Yoga a socially relevant field of study.
Based on the teachings of Swami Vivekananda, Vyasa University combines the four streams of Yoga with unity in their diversity, the key essence of Indian culture, applications of Yoga to bring health, harmony, peace the world over are now spread across the globe in nearly 30 countries.
Vyasa University: Using scientific research to bring Yoga into the modern world!</description></item><item><title>How QAChef Is Reaching Clients In A Tough Market</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</guid><description>The hospitality business is in a hard place right now because of Covid 19.
QAChef is a technology company which digitizes food safety compliance processes through a single handheld device, thus enabling unprecedented ingredient-to-customer food traceability and greater efficiency and productivity.
QAChef&amp;#39;s handheld device being used to measure temperature during cooking So QAChef is in a fantastic position, a ready for market product which enhances traceability across large scale food production - perfect given the focus on food safety and associated health implications in the wake of the Covid-19 pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Video Translation And Its Implications For FireTech</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</guid><description>A recent interview with FireTech Connect was really good fun, with Leigh Kelson hosting a free-wheeling discussion about crisis, technology and the future of AI in the internationalization and localization space.
FireTech Connect The FireTech 2020 program is an initiative of the Peregian Digital Hub, a leading technology incubator based in Noosa on Queensland&amp;rsquo;s Sunshine Coast.
FireTech Connect is funded by the Department of Industry, Science, Energy and Resources through the AusIndustry Entrepreneurs’ Programme; The Queensland State Government&amp;rsquo;s Advance Queensland Program; and Noosa Shire Council.</description></item><item><title>How Subtitling Can Boost ROI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</guid><description>Today we look at how to boost ROI or ROAS across your video production lifecycle, and how to make structural decisions which will pay off over a long time frame.
ROI or ROAS: Which One Should I Use? It&amp;rsquo;s actually a pretty messy question, but here are the basics.
ROI: Return on Investment Getting a definition is the starting point, and according to the smart folks at Investopia:
Return on Investment (ROI) is a performance measure used to evaluate the efficiency of an investment or compare the efficiency of a number of different investments.</description></item><item><title>ऑस्ट्रेलियाई फैशन के माध्यम से एक यात्रा: अंग्रेजी से हिंदी में वीडियो प्रतिलेख और अनुवाद</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%91%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%88-%E0%A4%AB%E0%A5%88%E0%A4%B6%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A7%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A4%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%91%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%88-%E0%A4%AB%E0%A5%88%E0%A4%B6%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A7%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A4%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</guid><description>ये वीडियो है म्यूजियम ऑफ एप्लाइड आर्ट्स एंड साइंसेज यूट्यूब चैनल। यह वीडियो म्यूजियम ऑफ एप्लाइड आर्ट्स एंड साइंसेज (मॉस) के परिधान और डिजाइन संग्रह के बारे में है।
परिधान संग्रह 18 वीं सदी से वर्तमान उदाहरण के टुकड़े को दर्शाता है। इन्हें मॉस के नए सेंटर फॉर फैशन में दिखाया गया है । कुल मिलाकर लगभग 30,000 अद्भुत टुकड़े हैं, जो मॉस, आशा करता हैं कि भविष्य की पीढ़ियों के फैशन डिजाइनरों को प्रभावित और प्रेरित करेंगे।</description></item></channel></rss>