<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Engineering on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/engineering/</link><description>Recent content in Engineering on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 23:00:00 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/engineering/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Little Positivity: To Brighten Your Day, Week And Month!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-little-positivity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-little-positivity/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m not going to sugarcoat it, this pandemic sucks big time and if you&amp;rsquo;re anything like me, you&amp;rsquo;re overwhelmed with the horrifying statistics and negative news that surrounds this whole thing.
So we&amp;rsquo;re focusing on the good news today. As Fred Rogers famously said, &amp;ldquo;When I was a boy and I would see scary things in the news, my mother would say to me, &amp;lsquo;Look for the helpers. You will always find people who are helping.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: January 2020</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-january-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-january-2020/</guid><description>There are a number of bug fixes and patches, which may affect your experience. In fact, we hope it will affect your experience for the better!
Images below are from our UAT environment. Please contact your relationship manager for more information or access.
Fixes include the below. If you have any questions please contact us at hello@videotranslator.ai.
Spaces In FileTemplate And FileItem Names Transcription Without Time-Coding Transcription Copy Function Edit/Exit Modals Removed/Modified Fixes To Locking Cosmetic Fixes To Billing January 2020: Spaces In FileTemplate And FileItem Names Previously, it was not possible to have spaces in fileTemplate and fileItem names.</description></item><item><title>Babies teaching us how best to teach AI, glasses made for translation and keeping an eye on our giant fishy friends with AI!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-15-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-15-oct-2019/</guid><description>More than just cute little stinkers, babies are exceptional learners, so good in fact that we&amp;rsquo;re trying to simulate their learning process to assist AI in becoming evermore smarter. Our first article details just how babies learn and what they&amp;rsquo;re doing to make AI do the same. Plus, machine learning is helping us prepare and respond to natural disasters and an app is now available to help content creators reach their target market, with the click of a button.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: September 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-september-2019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-september-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy month for us so far. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of new and exciting features we&amp;rsquo;re still developing so watch this space! In the meantime, there are a couple of updates and patches to tell you about.
Embedding Captions Previously, to embed captions onto your video it was possible to do so from the captions tab. This tab is now only used to make edits to the captions. To embed captions, it is now done by using the Audio Overlay tab.</description></item><item><title>AI tools are transforming Indian healthcare, growth in the Translations Market and more</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-24-sept-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-24-sept-2019/</guid><description>Welcome to the Weekly Roundup!
Each week we put together a list of articles featuring some of the most interesting ideas and news in the field. This week we take a look at how AI tools are helping to transform Indian healthcare, machine learning is being used to create new music, plus much more.
Read on to find out what&amp;rsquo;s been going on in the past week.
1. Why one media buyer is embracing programmatic linear TV Linear television can be a tough nut to crack when it comes to advertising and brand reach, but Global director of media strategy at PHD Media, Nick Vernola believes new technology can hold the solution.</description></item><item><title>Product Update: May 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/product-update-may-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/product-update-may-2019/</guid><description>We have been putting in for a number of grant applications in the innovation space. One of the applications needed a small video as part of the application process.
The video covers the basic use cases, and we added the captions to the asset.
May 2019: Product update Product Update: May 2019 (English)
Conclusion Please connect with us on LinkedIn, YouTube or Facebook for any comments, questions, or just to keep up to date with the work we do!</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: May 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-may-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-may-2019/</guid><description>There are a number of bug fixes and patches, which may affect your user experience. Fixes include (a) and upload bug, (b) a naming convention enhancement, (c) a UI timing bug, (d) UI help bug, and (e) UI folder bug.
May 2019: Upload Bug Previously, if you uploaded certain files, and exceeded certain file sizes, the application would error without notifying the user.
Specifically, on the operational side, we setup all client with file and size permissions at enrolment.</description></item><item><title>Bleeding Edge AI: How A DeepMind Just Beat Team Liquid At StarCraft II</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-deepmind-just-beat-team-liquid-at-starcraft-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-deepmind-just-beat-team-liquid-at-starcraft-ii/</guid><description>If you didn&amp;rsquo;t catch it, last Thursday January 24, 2019 DeepMind&amp;rsquo;s new AI, AlphaStar beat a Team Liquid player Grzegorz Komincz, also known as MaNa in a professional game of StarCraft II.
What are we talking about? StarCraft II is a real-time strategy game by Blizzard Entertainment, which has become a staple of the eSports community. Professional play has been ongoing since the game&amp;rsquo;s initial release in 2010, following on the success of StartCraft and StarCraft: Brood Wars, both of which had substantial eSports fan bases.</description></item><item><title>How To Add A Forum To Your Website</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-add-a-forum-to-your-website/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-add-a-forum-to-your-website/</guid><description>Given we are getting super close to launch, there are a lot of conversations with prospects who are keen to use our product. We get many (welcome) questions from prospects/clients on how to use the platform. Additionally, because we are a new start up, we don't have great documentation. How to solve this problem with limited bandwidth?
The requirement is pretty simple, an easy way to communicate with prospects and clients, which stacks.</description></item></channel></rss>