<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/feed.xml</link><description>Recent content on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:00:01 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Implications Of AI Adoption In Our Tools</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-implications-of-ai-adoption-in-our-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-implications-of-ai-adoption-in-our-tools/</guid><description>AI is everywhere in the news these days. But something critical has changed recently.
In the near past, AI has gone from being super fancy to being, well... pedestrian.
Say what now?
Well - AI is becoming ordinary. And turning up in our office/productivity toolkits.
In recent days, Google has expanded its offering using AI, as has Microsoft, and so has Amazon.
What does this mean for how we work, and how can you use this trend to advantage your business?</description></item><item><title>How NSW Health Is Using Video Translation To Empower Occupational Therapists</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</guid><description>One major challenge in diverse societies is the provision of healthcare services.
In western Sydney, this problem is directly tackled by the South-West Sydney Local Health District, which sits under New South Wales Health.
Ok - so obviously this is complicated stuff. But how does video translation help?
If you don't speak good English, specifically business English, finding information is very hard. The doctor is the only resource who can help, but what happens when they don't speak your language?</description></item><item><title>Why YouTube Stopped Community Caption Contributions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</guid><description>Community captions are a function in YouTube. This function allows a YouTube content creator to crowd source captions for their video content.
YouTube is shutting this down. Here is how it will affect you!
Change To Community Contributions On YouTube Notice about an upcoming change to community contributions on YouTube Both creators and viewers have reported problems with the community contributions feature, including spam, abuse, and low quality submissions.</description></item><item><title>How Vyasa University Is Fighting Covid With Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</guid><description>Vivekananda Yoga Anusandhana Samsthana or VYASA is a registered charitable institution (1986) working to make Yoga a socially relevant field of study.
Based on the teachings of Swami Vivekananda, Vyasa University combines the four streams of Yoga with unity in their diversity, the key essence of Indian culture, applications of Yoga to bring health, harmony, peace the world over are now spread across the globe in nearly 30 countries.
Vyasa University: Using scientific research to bring Yoga into the modern world!</description></item><item><title>How QAChef Is Reaching Clients In A Tough Market</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</guid><description>The hospitality business is in a hard place right now because of Covid 19.
QAChef is a technology company which digitizes food safety compliance processes through a single handheld device, thus enabling unprecedented ingredient-to-customer food traceability and greater efficiency and productivity.
QAChef&amp;#39;s handheld device being used to measure temperature during cooking So QAChef is in a fantastic position, a ready for market product which enhances traceability across large scale food production - perfect given the focus on food safety and associated health implications in the wake of the Covid-19 pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Video Translation And Its Implications For FireTech</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</guid><description>A recent interview with FireTech Connect was really good fun, with Leigh Kelson hosting a free-wheeling discussion about crisis, technology and the future of AI in the internationalization and localization space.
FireTech Connect The FireTech 2020 program is an initiative of the Peregian Digital Hub, a leading technology incubator based in Noosa on Queensland&amp;rsquo;s Sunshine Coast.
FireTech Connect is funded by the Department of Industry, Science, Energy and Resources through the AusIndustry Entrepreneurs’ Programme; The Queensland State Government&amp;rsquo;s Advance Queensland Program; and Noosa Shire Council.</description></item><item><title>How Subtitling Can Boost ROI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</guid><description>Today we look at how to boost ROI or ROAS across your video production lifecycle, and how to make structural decisions which will pay off over a long time frame.
ROI or ROAS: Which One Should I Use? It&amp;rsquo;s actually a pretty messy question, but here are the basics.
ROI: Return on Investment Getting a definition is the starting point, and according to the smart folks at Investopia:
Return on Investment (ROI) is a performance measure used to evaluate the efficiency of an investment or compare the efficiency of a number of different investments.</description></item><item><title>AI Localisation: Help Me Help You</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-localisation-help-me-help-you/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-localisation-help-me-help-you/</guid><description>Today we look at AI localisation. Essentially, how to use AI to reach a broader market at scale.
Its a really simple question. Does AI Localisation work at scale?
As always, the answer is yes and no, but mostly it depends on what you are trying to do.
The context is this: localisation project managers often burn themselves out by performing tons of routine operations every single day.
So the question becomes, how to use AI localisation at scale, and then, how to best use AI in localisation efforts at the process level?</description></item><item><title>Video SEO: Keywords, Titles, Descriptions And The Transcript</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-seo-keywords-titles-descriptions-and-the-transcript/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-seo-keywords-titles-descriptions-and-the-transcript/</guid><description>This post is dedicated to simple rules to maximise your SEO (Search Engine Optimisation) impact with video content.
There are 4 things you need to do to maximise your video content&amp;rsquo;s SEO impact. They are, title, description, keywords and the transcript, we will look at each one of these in detail.
Why Do Video SEO? From this DeepCrawl article, search engines cannot index video content. This is because search engines can only index text content.</description></item><item><title>How To Do Video SEO Right</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-do-video-seo-right/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-do-video-seo-right/</guid><description>There are a large number of reasons as to why people create content. Here is the one thing all content creators have in common.
They need to market their content. And step one is thinking about Search Engine Optimisation (SEO).
This blog post covers what you need to know about making video content indexable, and hence searchable.
Read on to understand what you need to do to make your video SEO friendly!</description></item><item><title>Video Series: How to Quickly Transcribe Your Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-series-how-to-quickly-transcribe-your-video/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-series-how-to-quickly-transcribe-your-video/</guid><description>The QuickTranscribe feature is our most used feature in the video transcription and translation process.
Our easy how-to guide on using the Quick Transcribe feature. For more information on Quick Transcribe visit our written guide here.
How to quickly transcribe your video
We are very grateful for your support!
Please connect with us on LinkedIn, YouTube or Facebook for any comments, questions, or just to keep up to date with the work we do!</description></item><item><title>A Step by Step Guide to Translating Your First Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-step-by-step-guide-to-translating-your-first-video/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-step-by-step-guide-to-translating-your-first-video/</guid><description>Having the ability to translate your video into a number of different languages and dialects puts your business a step ahead of the rest in means of reaching a larger audience and in turn, customers.
But getting your content translated and transcribed into another language seems expensive and time consuming, right?
Good news, friend. You&amp;rsquo;re wrong!
Dubbing and/or subtitling your video is a quick and easy process if you&amp;rsquo;re using our app and we hope that&amp;rsquo;s why you&amp;rsquo;re here&amp;hellip; to find out how to do it.</description></item><item><title>A Little Positivity: To Brighten Your Day, Week And Month!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-little-positivity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-little-positivity/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m not going to sugarcoat it, this pandemic sucks big time and if you&amp;rsquo;re anything like me, you&amp;rsquo;re overwhelmed with the horrifying statistics and negative news that surrounds this whole thing.
So we&amp;rsquo;re focusing on the good news today. As Fred Rogers famously said, &amp;ldquo;When I was a boy and I would see scary things in the news, my mother would say to me, &amp;lsquo;Look for the helpers. You will always find people who are helping.</description></item><item><title>What Is The Best Subtitling Software Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-is-the-best-subtitling-software-available/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-is-the-best-subtitling-software-available/</guid><description>Are you a content creator? Or Are you a court reporter looking for an easy way to caption lots of content? This blog post might be for you.
Having captions is very useful these days. Its really good for engagement, and its also really good for accessibility - specifically hearing impaired folk.
However, and there is no getting around this, it is painful to do.
Manual audio or video transcription takes ages.</description></item><item><title>How Safe Is AI Transcription: What You Need To Know</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-safe-is-ai-transcription-what-you-need-to-know/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-safe-is-ai-transcription-what-you-need-to-know/</guid><description>You are a content creator who uses AI.
But how safe is the AI you use, whether for transcription, translation or dubbing. Also some tips on how to use AI better in your journey into expanding your market.
There was a great article on this recently at How-To-Geek.
Ok - so why do you use AI? As a content creator you care about engagement. AI Transcription combined with Open Captions is fantastic for engagement.</description></item><item><title>Translate Your English Video Into Filipino And Chinese</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</guid><description>Business today relies on content creation. How do you expand your market? We show you how to add open captions for accessibility wins, and translate your video content into Tagalog and Chinese to expand your target client base!
Matija Squire is a LinkedIn coach, all round nice person plus a good friend. And she is doing something really cool!
We all know Covid-19 has distrupted all our lives. Some of us are lucky enough to be able to earn an income by working from home online.</description></item><item><title>How To Translate YouTube Videos And Dominate SEO</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</guid><description>The basic steps to translate a YouTube video are:
Download the video to your computer. Upload the video into an AI transcription service. Get the transcript in an .srt file. Translate the transcript using an AI translation service. Embed the translation into your video. You should only translate videos that you expect a good Return On Investment from - so you have a good feeling this video will work in a different language.</description></item><item><title>The Girls and Women Revitalising Canada's Indigenous Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-girls-and-women-revitalising-canadas-indigenous-languages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-girls-and-women-revitalising-canadas-indigenous-languages/</guid><description>It was International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day this past Sunday 8 March and in honour of the day we&amp;rsquo;re looking at some incredible females who are doing all they can for their native languages.
The Girls and Women Revitalising Canada&amp;#39;s Indigenous Languages
Celebrating Indigenous Women Who Are Reclaiming and Revitalising Their Languages Image courtesy of Marion Konwanénhon Delaronde and Karihwiióstha Callie Montour In light of International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day which was this past Sunday, March 8, CBC News in Canada put together an article celebrating a number of Indigenous women and their plight to preserve and revitalise their traditional languages.</description></item><item><title>Clipping Chinese App: How To Translate Video Into Mandarin Chinese With AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</guid><description>One very common use case of video translator is as a Chinese clipping app. What is a Chinese clipping app?
This term is used by content creators to mean how to translate a video from English to Chinese, and they generally mean a short video for various social media channels.
In this blog post we are going to look at how to translate a small video from English to Mandarin (Simplified Chinese).</description></item><item><title>Fighting the Coronavirus and E. Coli with Machine Learning</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/fighting-the-coronavirus-and-e-coli-with-machine-learning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/fighting-the-coronavirus-and-e-coli-with-machine-learning/</guid><description>When it comes to combating superbugs and viruses, the human raced needs all the help it can get. Artificial Intelligence is being implemented to find treatments to fight bacteria that was formally resistant to all forms of antibiotics. China is also using AI to quickly determine if a person is showing symptoms of the coronavirus, which could be a great win against getting a handle on the respiratory disease.
Fighting The Coronavirus And E-Coli With Machine Learning</description></item><item><title>How AI Dubbing Will Change Everything: Building A Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</guid><description>There is a very interesting piece of content we are looking at today. A team from IIIT-H (Indian Institute of Information Technology - Hyderabad) has build an AI which translates and lip-syncs a video from one language to another.
This originally came to our attention in this article from the folks at TNW. The paper this article is based on is here, and if you are interested in AI/Language you should absolutely have a look.</description></item><item><title>How AI Transcription Fails And What To Do About It</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</guid><description>AI Transcription has been all the rage recently. Several companies have been coming out with new products to meet this requirement.
What does it mean? Does it work? How to evaluate these products? We take a look and try to think behind the hype.
First we look at some of the incoming offerings. Then some issues with AI Transcription and Translation.
Incoming Offerings There is a very large number of AI products hitting the market place.</description></item><item><title>One Igbo Woman Trying To Save Her Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</guid><description>Oddly, its the feel-good stories which we think are the most important. This week we had a few stories come by which show much progress is being made in the popularity of regional languages.
Here at VideoTranslator we feel that most people are quite proud of where they come from - its totally natural.
Each one of us has a story of how we came to be, and the stories of those who came before are a vital part of any human identity.</description></item><item><title>How To Reach Gen Z Using AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we keep an eye on what everyone else is doing.
Well, we try to anyways. And one of the better resources out there is Social Media Today. This article, &amp;lsquo;What Gen Z is Watching Online - and What That Means for Marketers in 2020&amp;rsquo; is full of wonderful titbits about how to think about video.
How Gen Z Is Using YouTube The big takeaway from the article is that Vlogging and Informative Videos are the biggest draws.</description></item><item><title>AI &amp; Wildlife Preservation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-and-wildlife-preservation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-and-wildlife-preservation/</guid><description>If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing most of us can agree on, it&amp;rsquo;s that wildlife preservation is important. The animals on this planet have been suffering a lot since we humans came on the scene. Luckily, there are amazing people out there trying to right the wrongs. Using Artificial Intelligence, researchers are able to continue this quest all the more and we&amp;rsquo;re looking into just how that&amp;rsquo;s being done.
How Artificial Intelligence Is Changing Wildlife Research Giraffe populations are rapidly declining but AI is here to help Researcher Jenna Stacy-Dawes and her team at San Diego Zoo&amp;rsquo;s Institute for Conservation Research are being assisted in their work in giraffe conservation with the AI software program, Wildbook.</description></item><item><title>Clients: Why You Make Me Blush!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:02 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we get lots of feedback from clients. Most of it is good, some of it not so much. Recently, as we have started to build out our retail client base it has become interesting.
The product challenge with retail is quite different from an enterprise offering or a managed service. Because the user is not being paid to use the product (or being told to by their manager) expectations for the product are totally different.</description></item><item><title>Speaking In The Mother Tongue: AI Indian Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</guid><description>We recently came across an article with the exciting news that the Indian government is planning on making its Internet content available in regional languages &amp;ldquo;to remove the language barrier among Indians.&amp;quot;
Currently websites are available in English and Hindi but that leaves out the remaining 20 regional languages that are spoken across the country.
&amp;ldquo;We need a method through which any Indian using his or her language should be able to converse with any user in any other Indian language without the impediment of English as a link language.</description></item><item><title>Accessibility: Why It Matters And How To Avoid Being Sued</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work with clients who are part of the healthcare ecosystem.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, voice over artists, or in this case, nurses/doctors. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing - we are technologists who are trying to service our clients to the best of our ability.
Every now and then a story turns up which brings a lot of our work into sharp focus.</description></item><item><title>On The Brink Of Extinction: Nearly Dead Languages And The Dedicated Linguists Bringing Them Back To Life</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</guid><description>Thousands of kilometres apart, and in incredibly different cultures; three linguists are doing their part to save the culture of their people through language.
Masahiro Yamada and Natsuko Nakagawa in Japan and Kenny Pheasant in the United States are all passionate about ensuring almost lost languages are preserved and continue to be taught; and a lot of it comes down to teaching the languages to children.
Linguists Work To Preserve Ryukyu Dialects Now Dying Out Image courtesy of Nobuaki Tanaka Professors at the National Institute for Japanese Language and Linguistics made an alarming discovery when they found that many dialects in the Okinawa Prefecture are on the verge of dying out.</description></item><item><title>Sign Languages: Their past, present and future</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/sign-languages-their-past-present-and-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/sign-languages-their-past-present-and-future/</guid><description>For something that is used by an estimated 70 million people worldwide, there is still a lot we don&amp;rsquo;t know when it comes to the origin of sign language - luckily research is being done to change that. Going from the past to the future, Google Translate is developing a way to translate sign language into speech and we are excited about the possibilities that this brings for, well, everyone!</description></item><item><title>Quick Transcribe: For When You Need To Get Transcription Done Quickly</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator.Ai, we work closely with the Internationalization And Localization industry. This industry has many different participants, and they use our technology in different ways.
As a software firm, the hardest thing is to really understand what our clients do and why they do these things. Sounds funny, but it is true.
We had a strong response to our previous article, 3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency, and a number of questions and suggestions.</description></item><item><title>Mr Sh*thole: What To Do When Your AI Misbehaves</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</guid><description>Today we look at a humorous articles which look at what happens when AI goes wrong. Here at video translator we like to keep abreast of the latest news in the intersection of Artificial Intelligence, Natural Language Programming, Human Languages and Culture.
Read on to find out how Facebook&amp;rsquo;s AI got in trouble, and why Oracle thinks replacing your manager with a robot is likely, and a good thing to boot!</description></item><item><title>One place, many languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-place-many-languages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-place-many-languages/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re talking language today and how diverse it can be even in the same country, or city! Germany is still a country divided when it comes to what a pancake should be called - maybe they should be called egg-cakes? Also Mandarin is now Melbourne and Sydney&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;most widely spoken community language.&amp;rdquo;
Language matters, it&amp;rsquo;s important culturally and on a deeper level to help us identify with ourselves and others.</description></item><item><title>What Arabic Voices are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</guid><description>Previously we&amp;rsquo;ve gone through the list of our English speaking AI and the different dialects they speak. You can see them all here.
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re looking at our Arabic speaking AI and the different dialects and voices available.
If you need a reminder as to how to select the appropriate AI language and dialect, check out our article here.
Now, on to the voices! We&amp;rsquo;ve used the phrase birds of a feather, flock together or الطيور على أشكالها تقع for our AI to say each time for the examples.</description></item><item><title>Extra! Extra! Read all about it!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/extra-extra-read-all-about-it/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/extra-extra-read-all-about-it/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of exciting developments at VideoTranslator, which means exciting things for you! This means that you&amp;rsquo;ll be hearing more from us going forward in the form of a weekly email.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t subscribed to our mailing list or signed up for a free trial yet, please do so here.
The email will be featuring the latest articles we&amp;rsquo;ve posted which will be like the following:
What English Dialects are Available?</description></item><item><title>Where are we heading with AI computing in the 2020s? And how human can they really become?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/where-are-we-heading-with-ai-computing-in-the-2020s-and-how-human-can-they-really-become/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/where-are-we-heading-with-ai-computing-in-the-2020s-and-how-human-can-they-really-become/</guid><description>We now well and truly know that Artificial Intelligence is here to stay (and in fact has been for quite some time), but what will become of it, and us, in the future? One author has some very interesting thoughts on how AI computing will reach beyond just recognising how to act like a human but rather see the world the way we do and have a form of common sense.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: January 2020</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-january-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-january-2020/</guid><description>There are a number of bug fixes and patches, which may affect your experience. In fact, we hope it will affect your experience for the better!
Images below are from our UAT environment. Please contact your relationship manager for more information or access.
Fixes include the below. If you have any questions please contact us at hello@videotranslator.ai.
Spaces In FileTemplate And FileItem Names Transcription Without Time-Coding Transcription Copy Function Edit/Exit Modals Removed/Modified Fixes To Locking Cosmetic Fixes To Billing January 2020: Spaces In FileTemplate And FileItem Names Previously, it was not possible to have spaces in fileTemplate and fileItem names.</description></item><item><title>Real life Dr Dolittle: We are on our way to talking to the animals and AI may make happen sooner than you think!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-jan-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-jan-2020/</guid><description>Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be fantastic if we could understand what our pets were trying to tell us? Having them be able to communicate if they like the food we give them, when they&amp;rsquo;re not feeling well and when they want to be pet, would take out so much of the guess work. (Although hearing dogs constantly asking to have a ball thrown might get a bit old after a while). Researchers are looking into decoding animal languages and we are here for it!</description></item><item><title>3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work in what is called the Internationalization And Localization industry.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
When do we do this work for our clients? Generally when a client needs a managed service. This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year 2020!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year-2020/</guid><description>Its the start of a new decade! This is a big deal, the only question is will this be the roaring 20&amp;rsquo;s all over again. Here at VideoTranslator we think it is going to be an exciting year.
Several amazing things happened last year, and this was mostly due to the kindness of strangers. Thank you very much to all the folks who took an interest in our work.
We started to get some traction, we found a niche where our tech was useful, and slowly slowly things started to come together.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays from VideoTranslator!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-hoidays-from-videotranslator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-hoidays-from-videotranslator/</guid><description>What a year it&amp;rsquo;s been! From our launch in May we would not have believed we&amp;rsquo;d come so far in such a short amount of time.
Thank You Thank you everyone for all your support! We want to wish you and yours a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year. We hope you have a brilliant 2020!
Everyone who engaged with us, others that offered feedback, and folks who made a purchasing decision - thank you very much.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: For the Love of Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-17-dec-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-17-dec-2019/</guid><description>Language. It's something we're passionate about here at Video Translator, we can't get enough of it. And, judging by the news that&amp;rsquo;s come out in the past week, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of folks out there who share our passion. We&amp;rsquo;re delving into language from all across the globe this week; NLP research engineers working with pidgin English, YouTube India is branching out into local and regional Indian languages, Navajo is getting it&amp;rsquo;s own version of one of the most popular (read: annoying for adults) songs amongst toddlers and we see the effects on the brain from being bilingual from an early age.</description></item><item><title>An Old Language Is Young Again...</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/an-old-language-feels-young-again/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/an-old-language-feels-young-again/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we are big fans of the work of Tim Brookes. Recently, his work has included a kickstarter to create art work in traditional Nepalese script known as Ranjana.
We look at a language he shone some light on today. We also look at work Comcast is doing to support hearing impaired clients. This is quite exciting from an operational perspective.
Lastly we look at a recent write up from the Latin Post which looks at how to interface with commercial translation firms for your localisation and internationalization requirements.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Exciting developments for Epilepsy patients, Amazon has added 22 new languages to Amazon Translate and has Microsoft given children the ability to speak to reindeer?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-10-dec-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-10-dec-2019/</guid><description>It seems like every week there are exciting new developments with artificial intelligence being used in the health, medicine and science fields; and that&amp;rsquo;s because, well, there is. There is often quite a negative attitude amongst the public in relation to AI, &amp;ldquo;they&amp;rsquo;re going to take our jobs!&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s the end of the human race!&amp;rdquo; But it&amp;rsquo;s not all doom and gloom. Really good, positive, and not to mention lifesaving advances in medicine, are taking place all with AI and proving that our new robot overlords are not planning on taking over the world just quite yet&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>What English Dialects are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-english-dialects-are-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-english-dialects-are-available/</guid><description>Did you know that our AI can speak in over 180 languages and more than 120 differing dialects and different genders? It&amp;rsquo;s true! That&amp;rsquo;s one smart robot ;)
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re focusing on English and the four different dialects that you can choose from when using our app.
For those that have you used the app before, you will notice that we have renamed the &amp;ldquo;voices&amp;rdquo;. Previously we had them named as EN-IN-P-M1, or UK-S4-M which didn&amp;rsquo;t make a lot of sense for those who were unfamiliar with the technology.</description></item><item><title>60% Of The Content Produced By US YouTubers Is Watched In Other Countries</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/60-of-the-content-produced-by-us-youtubers-is-watched-in-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/60-of-the-content-produced-by-us-youtubers-is-watched-in-other-countries/</guid><description>Google produces all sorts of very interesting research. I mean, all kinds! One of the specific bits of intel which is well worth tracking is Think With Google.
Today we are going to look at a set of remarkable trend lines which point the way in which the world is heading.
We look at a 3 behavior and cultural shifts inside YouTube.
2 Behavioural And Cultural Shifts You should really read the article yourself, but the below was what we found super useful.</description></item><item><title>Changes In The Internationalization And Localization Industry</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/changes-in-the-internationalization-and-localization-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/changes-in-the-internationalization-and-localization-industry/</guid><description>Rev.com, a online transcription platform, got in trouble last month. It picked up a negative profile last month by none other than the New York Times.
Even worse was that Rev managed to become the poster child of gig-economy companies who mistreat workers. This led to a lot of negative media coverage which is probably not what Rev is looking to do.
What Set Off Media Focus This article by the NYT set of this series of events.</description></item><item><title>What A Hindi Speaking AI Sounds Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</guid><description>A few posts ago we transcribed an Indian English video using a Speech-To-Text Indian English transcription Artificial Intelligence (AI). Today we are going to take the same idea forward, and now going to translate the video into Hindi.
To recap, we used a sample clip from Rajya Sabha TV which as (a) transcribed using a speech-to-text AI, and (b) cleaned up by a human. We will now clean it up a little bit more, and then translate the content into Hindi.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Hello baby! Machine learning helping to understand placental health, did Shakespeare have help? And advances in health and medicine thanks to AI.</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-26-nov-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-26-nov-2019/</guid><description>Considering it is something that keeps the human race going, maternal and placental health is still not properly understood, which proves extremely detrimental to the health of mother and baby during pregnancy. Thanks to a new development in AI technology, that will begin to change. We&amp;rsquo;re also looking at how educators in the US are frantically searching for a better solution to interpretations services that help communicate with non-English speaking families and we look at the leaps and bounds being made in medicine thanks to machine learning.</description></item><item><title>Winning: We Won The JobsForNSW MVP Grant! Before, During And After...</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/winning-how-we-won-a-jobsfornsw-mvp-grant/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/winning-how-we-won-a-jobsfornsw-mvp-grant/</guid><description>DISCLAIMER: This blog post was updated after having a conversation with JobsForNSW. [3 Dec 2019]
Please check the JobsForNSW website for updates. The process covered below changes regularly and DO NOT rely on the below to be correct going forward. It was correct at time of publication, but talking to the JobsForNSW staff it is LIKELY to change pretty soon.
Earlier this year we put in an application for a Minimum Viable Product Grant from JobsForNSW, a NSW Government initiative.</description></item><item><title>Open Captions: Enhancements November 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/open-captions-enhancements-november-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/open-captions-enhancements-november-2019/</guid><description>Working with a prospect, we added a number of enhancements to our open captions workflow. If you are interested in what open captions are and what its use cases are please have a look at this blog post.
Very simply open captions are generally used as an accessibility tool focused on people who have hearing impairments. More recently due to the rise of streaming services, open captions have been making a come back.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: AI to the rescue! Using machine learning for the greater good; advances in medicine, agriculture and saving lives, is there anything we can't do with the help of artificial intelligence?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-12-nov-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-12-nov-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another AI focused week and with so much going on in the world of Artificial Intelligence, can you blame us? The field of medicine and science have long been advocates of using AI for the greater good and it appears there are some incredible trail blazers helping to make that happen.
1. A Star Professor—And Her Radical, AI-Powered Plan To Discover New Drugs Using AI to discover new medicine One woman is using her incredible skills and mind to advance the way in which drugs can be discovered and created with the help of artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Transcribing Indian English: A Simple Guide To Using AI To Speed Up Transcription And Add Open Captions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcribing-indian-english-a-simple-guide-to-using-ai-to-speed-up-transcription-and-add-open-captions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcribing-indian-english-a-simple-guide-to-using-ai-to-speed-up-transcription-and-add-open-captions/</guid><description>Today we are going to look at how to transcribe Indian English. Firstly of course, what is Indian English, and what does it sound like? How many such dialects exist? Have a look.
Now that we know what Indian English sounds like, we are going to use a short clip from Rajya Sabha TV, an Indian government content creator. We use our AI to transcribe this clip.
Lastly, we add an Auto-Overlay so that we can show you the video.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Foreign signs installed to save lives, when seeing isn't believing; learning about deepfake videos, content creators coming together to save the planet and hilarious movie translations</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-05-nov-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-05-nov-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s the start of a new month and news from around the globe keeps on rolling in. This week we&amp;rsquo;ve learnt the power of YouTube, its content creators and their followers and how they&amp;rsquo;re working together for the greater good. We also focus on the Western Australian Government&amp;rsquo;s foreign language road signs initiative that aims to save lives and we delve into the world of deepfake videos. Are they as dangerous as they seem?</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Google's latest Pixel 4 app impresses, praise for Nobel Prize winner and a feel-good video to brighten your week</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-29-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-29-oct-2019/</guid><description>Exciting news for content creators this week at Instagram&amp;rsquo;s IGTV releases features that will allow videos to viewed as a series. Google is releasing an on-device transcribing app that may be a game-changer, plus just because we loved it so; a video showing a deaf father signing to his newborn daughter, that has really hit us with all the feels.
1. Pixel 4’s live transcription goes up against “real-life” challenges Image courtesy of The Wall Street Journal Google is a releasing a new built in app in their Pixel 4 and honestly, it&amp;rsquo;s very impressive.</description></item><item><title>Samples From A Voice Over Robot: French, German and Dutch</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</guid><description>Following on from last week&amp;rsquo;s blog post, where we looked at different English dialects, we are going to do much the same today in Dutch, French and German.
Do you like the below examples? Let us know - we are super keen to hear what you think?
To try other languages (for FREE!) sign up to the free trial and give it a go!
Steps First, as per our usual create a new item using the English language template.</description></item><item><title>AI Dubbing: What Different Dialects Of English Sound Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</guid><description>Today we are going to look AI dubbing and look at a few different samples of what an AI can sound like in English. We are going to do something pretty simple, we will use the quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog for our seed text.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what this sentence is, quoting from Wikipedia, &amp;ldquo;The quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog&amp;rdquo; is an English-language pangram—a sentence that contains all of the letters of the alphabet.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Travelling back in time with AI, learning the love of translation and why it is imperative to get more interpreters in courthouses to aid domestic violence cases</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-22-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-22-oct-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another big week in AI news, from assisting in search and rescue methods to aiding doctors in detecting brain bleeds, it&amp;rsquo;s being proven time and time again how Artificial Intelligence can help humanity in meaningful ways. We also see that AI is helping historians create a portal into the past of Europe and creating virtual worlds that we can experience. In other news, one woman is advocating for more support and resources for translators in domestic violence cases and one author and translator explains her love for language and translation.</description></item><item><title>AI Transcription, Translation And Dubbing: How To Think About Accuracy</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-transcription-translation-and-dubbing-how-to-think-about-accuracy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-transcription-translation-and-dubbing-how-to-think-about-accuracy/</guid><description>We get a number of questions around AI Accuracy, and depending on the context, the question can refer to a number of things.
Wanted to put down a note describing the various iterations of what Accuracy in Artificial Intelligence refers to, and where it is going from my point of view.
Is the AI accurate? Is AI accurate when it comes to Transcription? Is AI accurate when it comes to Translation?</description></item><item><title>Text-To-Speech: AI Dubbing And What You Can Do With It</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/text-to-speech-ai-dubbing-and-what-you-can-do-with-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/text-to-speech-ai-dubbing-and-what-you-can-do-with-it/</guid><description>Today we are going to look AI dubbing and its various use cases. If you are wondering, is my content suitable for AI dubbing, or AI localisation? In simple terms:
What is dubbing or dub localisation? Should I use a human, or a machine for my dubbing? How do I use a video translator to dub my video? Rules of thumb, or heuristics, to achieve a superior outcome with AI dubbing?</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Babies teaching us how best to teach AI, glasses made for translation and keeping an eye on our giant fishy friends with the help of Artificial Intelligence</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-15-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-15-oct-2019/</guid><description>More than just cute little stinkers, babies are exceptional learners, so good in fact that we&amp;rsquo;re trying to simulate their learning process to assist AI in becoming evermore smarter. Our first article details just how babies learn and what they&amp;rsquo;re doing to make AI do the same. Plus, machine learning is helping us prepare and respond to natural disasters and an app is now available to help content creators reach their target market, with the click of a button.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Open Captions for Deaf and Hard of Hearing People</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/importance-of-open-captions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/importance-of-open-captions/</guid><description>It comes as no surprise that for hard of hearing and deaf people, closed captions are a necessity for being able to watch TV, films and online videos. We&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned before the need for more captions and subtitles to be present in cinemas and as highlighted in this Washington Post article, &amp;ldquo;accessing online material&amp;hellip;can be a challenge for differently abled people.&amp;rdquo;
This is one of the reasons we believe it is so important to include open captions in online videos.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Translation devices changing the business game, machine learning aiding scientific research and the world's first ever AI concert</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-oct-2019/</guid><description>The art of translation has been a skilled required by humans for over 2000 years, we&amp;rsquo;ve got a few interesting articles that highlight just how important it is and one translator shares with us what she&amp;rsquo;s learnt after being in the business for 20 years. We&amp;rsquo;re also looking at how machine learning is aiding scientists in researching plants, AI writers writing as well as humans can, and we celebrate as Armenia hosts the first ever AI concert.</description></item><item><title>Transcripción y Traducción de Videos de Español a Inglés</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcripci%C3%B3n-y-traducci%C3%B3n-de-videos-de-espa%C3%B1ol-a-ingl%C3%A9s/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcripci%C3%B3n-y-traducci%C3%B3n-de-videos-de-espa%C3%B1ol-a-ingl%C3%A9s/</guid><description>Este video pertenece al canal de YouTube Mariel de Viaje.
El video ofrece consejos básicos para afrontar con facilidad, comodidad y familiaridad cualquier viaje en plan turístico a la República Dominicana, e incluye sugerencias para visitar lugares emblemáticos como Punta Cana y Santo Domingo.
La República Dominicana es el segundo país más grande y diverso del Caribe. Cuenta con vuelos directos desde las principales ciudades de Latinoamérica, Estados Unidos, Canadá y Europa, es un país que se destaca por la calidez de su clima y la hospitalidad de su gente.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: AI is here to help; translation at the tip of your ears; and Google's ALBERT is receiving top ranks</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-01-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-01-oct-2019/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s been a lot going on with AI in particular this week. Read on to get up to date on some of the most interesting things coming out of the world of Artificial Intelligence. There&amp;rsquo;s also top ranking machine learning systems and earbuds that can translate languages as you&amp;rsquo;re hearing them.
1. Yes Bank creates &amp;lsquo;Yes Robot&amp;rsquo; using Microsoft Cognitive Services Yes Robot A bank in India has created AI assistant, &amp;lsquo;Yes Robot&amp;rsquo; to provide 24 hour customer service to its patrons.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: September 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-september-2019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-september-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy month for us so far. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of new and exciting features we&amp;rsquo;re still developing so watch this space! In the meantime, there are a couple of updates and patches to tell you about.
Embedding Captions Previously, to embed captions onto your video it was possible to do so from the captions tab. This tab is now only used to make edits to the captions. To embed captions, it is now done by using the Audio Overlay tab.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: AI tools are transforming Indian healthcare, growth in the Translations Market and more</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-24-sept-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-24-sept-2019/</guid><description>Welcome to the Weekly Roundup!
Each week we put together a list of articles featuring some of the most interesting ideas and news in the field. This week we take a look at how AI tools are helping to transform Indian healthcare, machine learning is being used to create new music, plus much more.
Read on to find out what&amp;rsquo;s been going on in the past week.
1. Why one media buyer is embracing programmatic linear TV Linear television can be a tough nut to crack when it comes to advertising and brand reach, but Global director of media strategy at PHD Media, Nick Vernola believes new technology can hold the solution.</description></item><item><title>What's Hot in Short Video Apps for iOS</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/whats-hot-in-short-video-apps-for-ios/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/whats-hot-in-short-video-apps-for-ios/</guid><description>With the ever increasing popularity of short video apps amongst iOS users, more and more developers are trying to get their apps to the top. This has resulted in a plethora of short video apps being created with different features based on the users needs and wants. We&amp;rsquo;ve taken a look at the top ranking short video apps in the Apple App Store (as of August 2019) to see what these apps for iPhone have to offer.</description></item><item><title>9 of China's Best Short Video Apps</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/9-of-chinas-best-short-video-apps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/9-of-chinas-best-short-video-apps/</guid><description>Short video makers are an up and coming category of apps that are really hitting the ground running in China. Short video clips (even less than a second long) have been gaining in popularity along with social platforms like Instagram and Snapchat, and especially in China with Wechat and Weibo. The social component to online video broadcasting has changed how we consume short videos, and what we expect from them.</description></item><item><title>The 8 Best Short Video Apps for Android</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-8-best-short-video-apps-for-android/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-8-best-short-video-apps-for-android/</guid><description>Short video clips continue to gain in popularity along with social platforms like Instagram and Snapchap. As smartphone video technology has improved along with our access to video media online, there has been a growing need for short video apps on smartphones. TechloMedia recently published a report on trending social video apps. We’ve taken a look at these as well as the top performing video apps in the Google Play Store (as of August 2019).</description></item><item><title>Transcripción y Traducción de Videos de Inglés a Español</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcripci%C3%B3n-y-traducci%C3%B3n-de-videos-de-ingl%C3%A9s-a-espa%C3%B1ol/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcripci%C3%B3n-y-traducci%C3%B3n-de-videos-de-ingl%C3%A9s-a-espa%C3%B1ol/</guid><description>Este video pertenece al canal de YouTube History Matters. El video habla sobre el personaje histórico ruso con repercusiones en la historia universal, Ivan El Terrible.
Iván IV Vasílievich, llamado Iván el Terrible, fue un gran príncipe de Moscú y de toda Rusia, además de ser el primer monarca ruso en adoptar el título de Zar. Es considerado como uno de los creadores del Estado Ruso.
Pasos A Seguir Abre tu navegador y dirígete a videotranslator.</description></item><item><title>Translating Your Video From English To French: A Step By Step Guide</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translating-your-video-from-english-to-french-a-step-by-step-guide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translating-your-video-from-english-to-french-a-step-by-step-guide/</guid><description>The Sydney Opera House is one of the most well known landmarks in the world. With over 10.9 million people visiting it each year, it&amp;rsquo;s obviously one of Australia&amp;rsquo;s hottest tourist spots.
When searching online, the official videos for the Opera House are all in English, which is great for English speakers, but what about those who aren&amp;rsquo;t?
Using the videotranslator.ai app and creating translated videos would be a great way to reach millions of people worldwide who aren&amp;rsquo;t native English speakers.</description></item><item><title>Why Post Video To Social Media: 3 Tips</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-post-video-to-social-media-3-tips/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-post-video-to-social-media-3-tips/</guid><description>Several recent reports show that video content outperforms every other type of post on social media. In other words, using video content in social media marketing is a very good strategy. In this post we look at some numbers, and try to work out what this means for content creators and marketers.
Renderforest put together an insightful report on social video marketing. Here are some of their statistics:
100 million hours of video per day is watched on Facebook.</description></item><item><title>How Video Transcription Works Explainer</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-video-transcription-works-explainer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-video-transcription-works-explainer/</guid><description>We have been working really hard making a number of changes to our underlying application. Specifically we have (i) added a new architecture to our video processing, (ii) added a few more languages, (iii) large number of changes to the look/feel of the product.
All in all, we felt it was time for a new explainer video which covered how to use the platform.
Here it is&amp;hellip; enjoy!
How To Transcribe A Video Using AI Explainer: How to Transcribe A Video Using AI</description></item><item><title>Subtitling For The Win</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/subtitling-for-the-win/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/subtitling-for-the-win/</guid><description>It started with a Tweet, which was then picked up by the Guardian, re-Tweeted and the rest is history. The post got re-tweeted 70K+ times, and liked 74K+ times. That is clearly something which struck a cord. Why?
Who is using subtitles or captions, why are they using it, and how can you also use subtitles or captions. For a technical discussion on subtitles or captions, see this. This post is more about the value in subtitles or captions.</description></item><item><title>The Growing Pains Of Diversity And A Possible Solution</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-growing-pains-of-diversity-and-a-possible-solution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-growing-pains-of-diversity-and-a-possible-solution/</guid><description>This post is not really about diversity. It is about the granular challenges around governance in an increasingly complex world, and operational solutions which may work going forward.
We look at three events which took place in this week. What the problem is, and what a solution might be. These events are:
Trump Administration’s Deregulation Drive Begins to Impact Language Industry Sometimes Lost In Translation, With Dialects Context Is Key Translating verdicts will help all litigants Trump Administration’s Deregulation Drive Begins to Impact Language Industry US federal regulations have generally favored the language services industry.</description></item><item><title>How We Used SEO To Come Up With A New Name</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-we-used-seo-to-come-up-with-a-new-name/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-we-used-seo-to-come-up-with-a-new-name/</guid><description>Our original name was QBL Media, and our new name is videotranslator.ai. The original name did not really work, and was always a temporary name.
This post covers some of the context of where our platform came from, and what changes happened in the course of getting this app to market, including a pivot.
We used SEO to determine a new name. Read on to understand why this was done, how it was done, and what benefits we expect to get from the name change.</description></item><item><title>Comparison Between Rev.com And VideoTranslator.ai</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/comparison-between-rev-dot-com-and-videotranslator-dot-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/comparison-between-rev-dot-com-and-videotranslator-dot-ai/</guid><description>These days, there are a large number of video editing tools available. The majority of these can add captions, or add subtitles, to your video. However, to do this we first need a transcript of the audio or video content.
Given the number of video transcription services out there, which one should you choose?
Before you take on the monotonous task of transcribing audio to text, read this blog post to see the major differences between two transcription platforms, rev.</description></item><item><title>How Do I Make Subtitles And Closed Captions?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-do-i-make-subtitles-and-closed-captions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-do-i-make-subtitles-and-closed-captions/</guid><description>Many clients ask how us about subtitles. Generally, this is the first question a prospect asks us about our platform. In practise, they mean a few different things.
We want subtitles for our audio/video content. We have subtitles, but want to make changes to the timing. We want to embed our subtitles into our video file, for use in Social Media. Let us look at these questions in detail.</description></item><item><title>Product Update: May 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/product-update-may-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/product-update-may-2019/</guid><description>We have been putting in for a number of grant applications in the innovation space. One of the applications needed a small video as part of the application process.
The video covers the basic use cases, and we added the captions to the asset.
May 2019: Product update Product Update: May 2019 (English)
Conclusion Please connect with us on LinkedIn, YouTube or Facebook for any comments, questions, or just to keep up to date with the work we do!</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: May 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-may-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-may-2019/</guid><description>There are a number of bug fixes and patches, which may affect your user experience. Fixes include (a) and upload bug, (b) a naming convention enhancement, (c) a UI timing bug, (d) UI help bug, and (e) UI folder bug.
May 2019: Upload Bug Previously, if you uploaded certain files, and exceeded certain file sizes, the application would error without notifying the user.
Specifically, on the operational side, we setup all client with file and size permissions at enrolment.</description></item><item><title>मोम का हाथ बनाने की कला: अंग्रेजी से हिंदी मे वीडियो अनुवादित</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A5-%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%A8%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%A4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A5-%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%A8%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%A4/</guid><description>यह वीडियो मैडम तुसाद सिडनी यूट्यूब पृष्ठ से है और यह मैडम तुसाद सिडनी में मोम के हाथ बनाने के बारे में है, जहां वे तरल मोम से लोगों के हाथ के नक्से, कुछ सरल चरणों का पालन करके बनाते है।
प्रक्रिया के अनुसार ठंडे पानी में लोगों के हाथों को डुबोना, और फिर तरल मोम में उनके हाथ डुबोने शामिल है । यह करीब 5 बार दोहराया जाता है, हाथों का सांचा बनाने के लिए ।</description></item><item><title>The Art Of Making Wax Hands: English To Hindi Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-art-of-making-wax-hands-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-art-of-making-wax-hands-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</guid><description>This video is from Madame Tussauds Sydney&amp;rsquo;s Youtube page and it is about making wax hands at Madame Tussauds Sydney, where they make moulds of people hands out of liquid wax, by following a few simple steps.
The process involves dipping people hands into cold water, and then dipping their hands in liquid wax. This is repeated about 5 times, to make a mould of the hands.
The Art Of Making Wax Hands: English Video Translation From English To Hindi</description></item><item><title>एक प्रकृति की कला बंगू यिलबारा संग्रह: अंग्रेजी से हिंदी वीडियो प्रतिलेखन और अनुवाद</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%83%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%82-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%B9-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%83%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%82-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%B9-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</guid><description>हमें यह वीडियो म्यूजियम ऑफ कंटेम्पररी आर्ट् ऑस्ट्रेलिया के वेबसाइट के यूट्यूब पृष्ठ से मिला है ।
यह वीडियो एमसीए कलेक्शन के बंगू यिलबारा कला के बारे में है । बंगू यिलबारा शब्द अपने आप में कला के प्रयास का वर्णन है, और उस काम को बनाने का इरादा के लिए , प्रदर्शनी के लिए काम का वर्णन करने पर ज्यादा ध्यान केंद्रित नहीं करना है।
प्रदर्शनी कुछ अतिरिक्त लेबल के बिना जीवन की वास्तविकता के साथ संपर्क में लाने के लिए, प्रयास और दृष्टि के लिए कलाकार अभ्यास से संबंधित कला को प्रदर्शित करने पर केंद्रित है।</description></item><item><title>A Nature Of Art Bangu Yilbara Collection: English To Hindi Video Transcription And Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-nature-of-art-bangu-yilbara-collection-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-nature-of-art-bangu-yilbara-collection-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</guid><description>We got this video from Museum of Contemporary Art Australia&amp;rsquo;s Youtube page This video is about Bangu Yilbara collection at the MCA. The collection is focused on art produced by the Aboriginal and Torres Straits Islander cultures.
The exhibition focuses on the diversity of Aboriginal and Torres Straits Islander culture, primarily by looking to the artists to define their work, as opposed to labelling the work &amp;lsquo;Aboriginal&amp;rsquo; and boxing it into any particular style.</description></item><item><title>ऑस्ट्रेलियाई फैशन के माध्यम से एक यात्रा: अंग्रेजी से हिंदी में वीडियो प्रतिलेख और अनुवाद</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%91%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%88-%E0%A4%AB%E0%A5%88%E0%A4%B6%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A7%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A4%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%91%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%88-%E0%A4%AB%E0%A5%88%E0%A4%B6%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A7%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A4%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</guid><description>ये वीडियो है म्यूजियम ऑफ एप्लाइड आर्ट्स एंड साइंसेज यूट्यूब चैनल। यह वीडियो म्यूजियम ऑफ एप्लाइड आर्ट्स एंड साइंसेज (मॉस) के परिधान और डिजाइन संग्रह के बारे में है।
परिधान संग्रह 18 वीं सदी से वर्तमान उदाहरण के टुकड़े को दर्शाता है। इन्हें मॉस के नए सेंटर फॉर फैशन में दिखाया गया है । कुल मिलाकर लगभग 30,000 अद्भुत टुकड़े हैं, जो मॉस, आशा करता हैं कि भविष्य की पीढ़ियों के फैशन डिजाइनरों को प्रभावित और प्रेरित करेंगे।</description></item><item><title>A Journey Through Australian Fashion: English To Hindi Video Transcription And Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-journey-through-australian-fashion-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-journey-through-australian-fashion-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</guid><description>This video is from Museum of Applied Arts and Sciences Youtube channel. This video is about the garments and design collection at the Museum of Applied Arts and Sciences (MAAS).
The garment collection covers pieces from the 18th century to present day examples. These are shown at the new Centre For Fashion at MAAS. There are around 30,000 amazing pieces in total, which MAAS hopes will impact and inspire future generations of fashion designers.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guide: Audio To Text</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-audio-to-text/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-audio-to-text/</guid><description>This post covers how to transcribe audio content. We will use a podcast as our sample audio content, and assume you are on a free trial. This post covers:
Sign into the application. Create an audio specific template. Create a new item, with our audio specific template as parent. Upload our podcast, and then use an Artificial Intelligence (AI) to transcribe our content. On reviewing this visual guide, you will be able to upload your own audio content, and transcribe using an AI.</description></item><item><title>वीडियो अनुवाद किया गया अंग्रेजी से हिंदी में: एक कोन्विक्ट हेरिटेज</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%97%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%97%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C/</guid><description>आज का वीडियो हयडे पार्क बैरक्स म्यूजियमस से है। यूटूब पेज, विशेष रूप से यह वीडियो है । हम इस वीडियो को अंग्रेजी से हिंदी में बदल देंगे ।
हाइडल पार्क बैरक्स म्यूजियम नवीनीकरण के दौर से गुजर रहा है । इस 2019 के अंत तक पूरा होने की उम्मीद है । क्यूरेटर और शोधकर्ताओं द्वारा नए शोध की एक बड़ी मात्रा हाइड पार्क बैरक में स्थित संग्रहालय को फिर से खोलने के बाद दिखाए जाने की उम्मीद है। यह नया प्रदर्शन ऑस्ट्रेलिया की सिद्धदोष विरासत के बारे में है । प्रारंभिक औपनिवेशिक ऑस्ट्रेलिया में अपराधियों के प्रभाव का दस्तावेजीकरण किया गया है, आंखों के माध्यम से देखा स्थानीय आदिवासी लोगों, और बसने वाले दोनों ने।</description></item><item><title>Video Translation From English To Hindi: A Convict Heritage</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-from-english-to-hindi-a-convict-heritage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-from-english-to-hindi-a-convict-heritage/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s video is from the Hyde Park Barracks Museum&amp;rsquo;s Youtube page, specifically this video. We will convert this video from English to Hindi.
Hyde Park Barracks Museum is undergoing a refurbishment. This is expected to be complete late 2019. A large amount of new research by curators and researchers based at Hyde Park Barracks is also expected to be shown once the museum is reopened.
This new exhibit is about Australia&amp;rsquo;s convict heritage.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guide: Free Trial Registration</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-free-trial-registration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-free-trial-registration/</guid><description>Everyone likes to try before they buy. This post is a visual guide to how to sign up for the free trial, and logging into the Video Translator platform. This post covers:
Sign up for the free trial Select your preferred languages Verify your email address, and log into the application On reviewing this visual guide, you should be able to sign up to Video Translator platform for free, and transcribe and translate up to 20 minutes of video content.</description></item><item><title>How To Use Auto Overlay To Simplify Transcription</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-auto-overlay-to-simplify-transcription/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-auto-overlay-to-simplify-transcription/</guid><description>We got this video from OSL Brokerage&amp;rsquo;s LinkedIn page. We are not suggesting that we have any relationship with OSL, and largely, we are using this content to demonstrate the process by which video content can be translated.
This specific video already has captions, so we don&amp;rsquo;t need these per se. However, we will be adding Chinese captions as an overlay, as opposed to captions.
The final output is shown below.</description></item><item><title>We Just Launched And We Need Luck</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-just-launched-and-we-need-luck/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-just-launched-and-we-need-luck/</guid><description>For the last 2 years or so, we have been working on a new platform which we think will be super useful for content creators. This includes marketers for exporters, tourism concerns, media shops and everyday folks looking to build brands and businesses using tools like YouTube and LinkedIn.
Just for some background, we are a tiny software company, and think of ourselves as basically an independent studio, trying to craft the best tools we can.</description></item><item><title>We Have An Explainer Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-have-an-explainer-video/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-have-an-explainer-video/</guid><description>We are a Sydney based, media focused technology platform provider, looking to make the world a more accessible place. Our primary value proposition is a transcription and translation platform, with a focus on audio and video content.
Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s translation platform (&amp;ldquo;the application&amp;rdquo;) is an Internet-enabled SaaS (Software as a Service) platform which assists content creators (&amp;ldquo;the client&amp;rdquo;) to engage with stakeholders (&amp;ldquo;the audience&amp;rdquo;) from different linguistic backgrounds. The application is used to convert hypermedia content from one language to another, using an Artificial Intelligence (AI) assisted process.</description></item><item><title>How To Reach Refugees, And Combat People Smugglers, With AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-refugees-and-combat-people-smugglers-with-ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-refugees-and-combat-people-smugglers-with-ai/</guid><description>Video translation is all the rage in Sydney currently. It sounds hard to believe, but this is honestly the case at the moment. The controversy revolves around a secret video, which the current Australian Prime Minister, Scott Morrison has (apparently) recorded.
The gist of the news is that the Australian Prime Minister has recorded a video, which will be translated into a number of languages. Once translated, the video will be broadcast in the media in different countries including Indonesia, Malaysia, Thailand, Pakistan, Bangladesh, Sri Lanka, Afghanistan and Iraq.</description></item><item><title>How To Use AI To Save Lions, In Afrikaans</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-ai-to-save-lions-in-afrikaans/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-ai-to-save-lions-in-afrikaans/</guid><description>As part of our process for testing the platform prior to go live, one of the things we look to do is test a large number of different languages. Part of it is good fun, the other objective is to try to change things around to see if we can break the platform and find bugs.
Realistically, this means looking for cool videos, and then trying things out with the videos.</description></item><item><title>How To Transcribe Lots of Different Accents Accurately</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-lots-of-different-accents-accurately/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-lots-of-different-accents-accurately/</guid><description>Today, we will look at how to transcribe many different accents correctly. First off, what does this question even mean in terms of AI?
The video we are working with is from Institute for Communication in Health Care (ICH) at the Australian National University (ANU).
Looking at the ICH&amp;rsquo;s mission statement, &amp;ldquo;The ICH’s mission is to build an international, collaborative research and training hub in healthcare communication to improve patient safety and quality of healthcare practice around the world&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>How To Get The Most Out Of Your AI: English To Hindi Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-get-the-most-out-of-your-ai-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-get-the-most-out-of-your-ai-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</guid><description>Today, we will cover simple heuristics to get the most out of your AI. As always, use the AI to do the heavy lifting, and use a human subject matter expert to finesse the results, producing a superior outcome with less time/effort.
The process followed is:
Transcribe the Gram Marg (literally, &amp;lsquo;road map&amp;rsquo; in Hindi) video using Indian English. Clean up the transcribed Gram Marg video, and present simple heuristics to the the most out of your AI.</description></item><item><title>How To Transcribe English Into Hebrew: ChangePlan</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-english-into-hebrew-changeplan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-english-into-hebrew-changeplan/</guid><description>Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here. Today, we will be using the video translation platform on a video from our friends at ChangePlan. We will do the following:
Transcribe ChangePlan&amp;rsquo;s video using Australian English. Fix up spelling/grammar in our captions. Translate ChangePlan&amp;rsquo;s video from English -&amp;gt; Hebrew. If you are looking to replicate this process, please note, after the translation step, it is highly recommended that you have a Hebrew qualified subject-matter expert finesse the captions.</description></item><item><title>Available Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/available-languages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/available-languages/</guid><description>OVERVIEW We look at the number of languages which you can use with your content. Remember, each languages is potentially a new market, and care needs to be taken to properly target your preferred leads.
There are two kinds of transcription, listed below. In both cases, speech is involved, hence these are referred to as transcription AI&amp;rsquo;s.
Speech-To-Text Transcription AI Text-To-Speech Transcription AI Similarly, with translation, what we are actually using is a Text-To-Text Translation AI.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/frequently-asked-questions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/frequently-asked-questions/</guid><description>WHAT IS TRANSCRIPTION? Transcription is a process which converts speech (either live or recorded) into a written or electronic text document. Transcription services are often required for business, legal, or medical purposes.
The most common type of transcription is from a spoken-language source into text such as a computer file suitable for printing as a document such as a report.
WHO ARE TRANSCRIPTS FOR? Transcripts are very useful for people who are deaf, hard of hearing, or have some other hearing related disability.</description></item><item><title>Help And Documentation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/help-and-documentation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/help-and-documentation/</guid><description>GETTING STARTED HOW TO REGISTER / HOW TO REGISTER FOR A FREE TRIAL To register please use the Free-Trial option.
Navigate to videotranslator.ai/free-trial/ Fill out your email address and select up to 4 languages from the drop-down menu (you can add more later). Click Sign Up A dialogue box will appear with the Terms of Service. You must accept the Terms of Service before hitting Submit. You will be redirected to a page to fill out your name and password.</description></item><item><title>People</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/people/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Pricing</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/pricing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/pricing/</guid><description>OVERVIEW Video Translator uses a Business to Customer (B2C) subscription plan loosely modelled on a mobile phone contract.
Video Translator: Pricing: Subscription vs. Pay-As-You-Go
PRICING MODEL BASICS Note that $10 = 1000 credits, and charges are in USD.
sign up for the free-trial and get 100 credits, pay 30 cents/minute for AI usage with no commitments, alternately subscribe for a minimum of $10/month and pay 15 cents/minute for AI usage.</description></item><item><title>Services</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/services/</guid><description>BENEFITS OF MANAGED SERVICE Service Internationalization has three components, app, website and marketing Benefits Of A Managed Service Video Translator provides managed services to assist clients to localize/internationalize their value proposition.
We offer a managed service aimed at meeting custom requirements.
Shallow Use Cases The majority of governments, non-profits and businesses have what we think of as shallow use cases. That is, they require translation services as an adjunct to their core concerns.</description></item><item><title>Social Media Guide To Video 1</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/social-media-guide-to-video-facebook-twitter-instagram-igtv-twitter-youtube/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/social-media-guide-to-video-facebook-twitter-instagram-igtv-twitter-youtube/</guid><description>INTRODUCTION If you’re planning to post your video to social media, it’s important to make sure your video meets social channel specific formatting requirements.
Not doing this can affect your users experience, from looking distorted, to unreadable captioning, to simply not playing, the below simple tips and tricks will make your content convert faster!
Video Formats, Size And Recommendations Video Lengths, Preferred Quality And Resolution Ratio&amp;rsquo;s Subtitles And Caption Options - Open Or Closed Metadata Heuristics RECOMMENDATIONS If you are aiming for maximum exposure use: an MP4 file, less than 180 seconds, aspect ratio of 16:9, at 720p and remember to add open captions for muted auto-play social media.</description></item><item><title>Social Media Guide To Video 2</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/social-media-guide-to-video-linkedin-tumblr-pinterest-youku/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/social-media-guide-to-video-linkedin-tumblr-pinterest-youku/</guid><description>INTRODUCTION If you’re planning to post your video to social media, it’s important to make sure your video meets social channel specific formatting requirements.
Not doing this can affect your users experience, from looking distorted, to unreadable captioning, to simply not playing, the below simple tips and tricks will make your content convert faster!
Video Formats, Size And Recommendations Video Lengths, Preferred Quality And Resolution Ratio&amp;rsquo;s Subtitles And Caption Options - Open Or Closed Metadata Heuristics LINKEDIN Formats for video on LinkedIn depends on whether the video is an advertisement.</description></item><item><title>Solutions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/solutions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/solutions/</guid><description>BENEFITS OF SAAS SOLUTIONS Benefits of Saas Solutions: VideoTranslator.AI app Benefits Of Saas Solutions Video Translator provides a Software-As-A-Service (SaaS) application to deliver real time Artificial Intelligence (AI) transcription and translation to clients.
With our Saas application, there are no software setup costs and the entire application is deployed via your Internet browser.
Using this application clients are able to:
Upload their text, image, audio and video content into the application.</description></item><item><title>Bleeding Edge AI: How A DeepMind Just Beat Team Liquid At StarCraft II</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-deepmind-just-beat-team-liquid-at-starcraft-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-deepmind-just-beat-team-liquid-at-starcraft-ii/</guid><description>If you didn&amp;rsquo;t catch it, last Thursday January 24, 2019 DeepMind&amp;rsquo;s new AI, AlphaStar beat a Team Liquid player Grzegorz Komincz, also known as MaNa in a professional game of StarCraft II.
What are we talking about? StarCraft II is a real-time strategy game by Blizzard Entertainment, which has become a staple of the eSports community. Professional play has been ongoing since the game&amp;rsquo;s initial release in 2010, following on the success of StartCraft and StarCraft: Brood Wars, both of which had substantial eSports fan bases.</description></item><item><title>How To Add A Forum To Your Website</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-add-a-forum-to-your-website/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-add-a-forum-to-your-website/</guid><description>Given we are getting super close to launch, there are a lot of conversations with prospects who are keen to use our product. We get many (welcome) questions from prospects/clients on how to use the platform. Additionally, because we are a new start up, we don't have great documentation. How to solve this problem with limited bandwidth?
The requirement is pretty simple, an easy way to communicate with prospects and clients, which stacks.</description></item><item><title>How To Transcribe A Foreign Language Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-a-foreign-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-a-foreign-language/</guid><description>Today we are going to look at how to transcribe a foreign language video. But how does this work when we live in a globalised world where people are from many different places - exactly what is foreign?
Well, Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here.
What we are looking at today, is how to transcribe a video in an language you do not know.</description></item><item><title>Multi-Lingual Forms... What Black Magic Is This???</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/multi-lingual-forms-what-black-magic-is-this/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/multi-lingual-forms-what-black-magic-is-this/</guid><description>We live in a modern world, which means working with colleagues, internal and external stakeholder, and clients from different backgrounds. For everyday interactions, this is fine, but every now and then, it can get messy.
Does this resonate with you? An important client in Asia needs something, and they are not happy. However, the operations person you are speaking to does not speak great English, and so an important deal has been bungled.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Manage Your Account</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-manage-your-account/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-manage-your-account/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s post we look at how to manage your account. This will cover Root and Management workspaces. The ordering reflects the navigation pane at the top right of the application. Please note, for more information covering how to add and remove languages specifically, please have a look at this post. Information about the Finance section will be covered in a later post.
This post is written to explain the use cases of account management, and why options are laid out as they are - if we have reached out to you for feedback, please feel free to come back with ideas on how you use/would like to use the interface.</description></item><item><title>English To German Video Translation: What is a Babybündel?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/english-to-german-video-translation-what-is-a-babyb%C3%BCndel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/english-to-german-video-translation-what-is-a-babyb%C3%BCndel/</guid><description>Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here. What we are going to do today is transcribe content to a different language, and use a practical example to demonstrate the technology.
We will be using this video, from the team at NSWHealth. The video is a simple, but effective solution for young mothers, where NSWHealth provide a useful box of household items aimed at first time mothers.</description></item><item><title>More Text-To-Speech Transcription!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/more-text-to-speech-transcription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/more-text-to-speech-transcription/</guid><description>Our platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here. Recently, we added a number of additional languages specific to Text-To-Speech transcription. These are, (a) French (Canadian), (b) Portuguese (Brazilian), (c) Spanish, (d) Swedish, and (e) Turkish.
In total, Text-To-Speech transcription now has the below set of languages available. Please note each language has multiple dialects, and gender specific voices are available.</description></item><item><title>What Languages Are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-languages-are-available/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-languages-are-available/</guid><description>We look at the number of languages which you can use with your content. Remember, each languages is potentially a new market, and care needs to be taken to properly target your preferred leads.
There are two kinds of transcription, the first is Speech-To-Text Transcription, the second is a Text-To-Speech Transcription. In both cases, speech is involved, hence these are referred to as transcription AI&amp;rsquo;s. Similarly, with translation, what we are actually using is a Text-To-Text Translation AI.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year/</guid><description>We had a very good 2018 here at Video Translator. While a challenging year, the majority of the platform was built in 2018. Oddly, doing hard things well is enormously empowering, if a little scary. Important events in 2018 included:
Moved into Fishburners, our brilliant co-working space, in the new Sydney Start Up Hub. Brought on two fantastic developers, Vivek Kumar and Pranay Shah. Both these guys have been absolutely critical in getting our platform over the line.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Add Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-add-languages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-add-languages/</guid><description>We look at how to add languages for transcription, translation and transliteration.
That is, assume we have a video in English. We now need to translate into French and German. We need to add French and add German into our account, before the transcription or translation will work.
In brief, we assume that no additional languages were selected during the sign up process, and now we are looking to add additional languages to our account.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Translate A Video without Sound</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-translate-a-video-without-sound/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-translate-a-video-without-sound/</guid><description>We look at how to translate video content. Translation is the communication of the meaning of a source-language text by means of an equivalent target-language text1. In brief, we will (i) upload a video, (ii) add text, (iii) translate the video text, (iv) download a translated video.
Steps We need a sample video to work with, and will use the Big Bunny video from Sample Video&amp;rsquo;s.
Click on the New Item button to create an item.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Transcribe a Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-transcribe-a-video/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 16:45:05 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-transcribe-a-video/</guid><description>We look at how to transcribe video content. From Wikipedia, &amp;lsquo;Transcription in the linguistic sense is the systematic representation of language in written form. The source can either be utterances (speech or sign language) or pre-existing text in another writing system.&amp;rsquo;
In brief, we will (i) upload our content, (ii) trigger transcription, and (iii) download a video with our embedded transcript. To transcribe your existing video content, please follow the below steps.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Sign-Up</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-sign-up/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 14:45:05 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-sign-up/</guid><description>The below describes how to sign-up to the Video Translator application. Following sign-up, how to login to the platform is also covered.
Steps To sign-up for the application, please follow the below steps:
Please direct your browser to videotranslator.ai, and then click on the Sign Up button.
Please input your email address, and select languages. Your primary language is assumed to be English, and you will be able to select an additional 2 languages (additional languages are available within the application).</description></item><item><title>What are the benefits of using Professional Translators?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-are-the-benefits-of-using-professional-translators/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 12:06:52 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-are-the-benefits-of-using-professional-translators/</guid><description>Why do we prefer to use professionals, especially in a business environment? Professionals execute the same tasks regularly, hence they know the in&amp;rsquo;s and the out&amp;rsquo;s of a problem and can solve it better, in a short amount of time and most often with improved costs. Knowledge, practice and experience is valued in all professions. The translation industry is not different and experienced translation professionals are most often preferred.
Using professional translation services should be your preferred default, especially when the content is aimed at business customers.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/welcome-to-video-translator/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 11:16:52 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/welcome-to-video-translator/</guid><description>Welcome to the Video Translator. We are a Sydney based, media focused technology platform provider, looking to make the world a more accessible place. Our primary value proposition is a translation platform, with a focus on video translation.
Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s translation platform (&amp;ldquo;the application&amp;rdquo;) is an Internet-enabled SaaS (Software as a Service) platform which assists content creators (&amp;ldquo;the client&amp;rdquo;) to engage with stakeholders (&amp;ldquo;the audience&amp;rdquo;) from different linguistic backgrounds. The application is used to convert hypermedia content from one language to another, using an Artificial Intelligence (AI) assisted process.</description></item><item><title>AI Transcription and Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/free-trial/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 10:03:06 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/free-trial/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 10:03:06 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/privacy-policy/</guid><description>SECTION 1 - PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site.</description></item><item><title>Terms Of Service</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/terms-of-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 10:03:06 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/terms-of-service/</guid><description>OVERVIEW These terms and conditions govern your use of the website and services enabled on that website (together referred to as the Video Translator Platform, the Platform) made available by QBL Media Pty Ltd.
The Platform is provided by QBL Media Pty Ltd (ABN: 73 602 663 141) (QBL, QBLM, Video Translator, we, us and our) to users (you and your and the Client).
The Platform is a managed software service hosted in a ‘cloud-style’ online environment.</description></item><item><title>Thank You</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/thanks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 10:03:06 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/thanks/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>