<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kathleen Aikin on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/authors/kathleen-aikin/</link><description>Recent content in Kathleen Aikin on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/authors/kathleen-aikin/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The 8 Best Short Video Apps for Android</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-8-best-short-video-apps-for-android/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-8-best-short-video-apps-for-android/</guid><description>Short video clips continue to gain in popularity along with social platforms like Instagram and Snapchap. As smartphone video technology has improved along with our access to video media online, there has been a growing need for short video apps on smartphones. TechloMedia recently published a report on trending social video apps. We’ve taken a look at these as well as the top performing video apps in the Google Play Store (as of August 2019).</description></item><item><title>Why Post Video To Social Media: 3 Tips</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-post-video-to-social-media-3-tips/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-post-video-to-social-media-3-tips/</guid><description>Several recent reports show that video content outperforms every other type of post on social media. In other words, using video content in social media marketing is a very good strategy. In this post we look at some numbers, and try to work out what this means for content creators and marketers.
Renderforest put together an insightful report on social video marketing. Here are some of their statistics:
100 million hours of video per day is watched on Facebook.</description></item><item><title>Comparison Between Rev.com And VideoTranslator.ai</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/comparison-between-rev-dot-com-and-videotranslator-dot-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/comparison-between-rev-dot-com-and-videotranslator-dot-ai/</guid><description>These days, there are a large number of video editing tools available. The majority of these can add captions, or add subtitles, to your video. However, to do this we first need a transcript of the audio or video content.
Given the number of video transcription services out there, which one should you choose?
Before you take on the monotonous task of transcribing audio to text, read this blog post to see the major differences between two transcription platforms, rev.</description></item></channel></rss>