<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Translation Professionals on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/translation-professionals/</link><description>Recent content in Translation Professionals on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/translation-professionals/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why You Should Use AI Powered Translator?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-use-ai-powered-translator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-use-ai-powered-translator/</guid><description>In this article, we are going to give you 3 reasons why you should use AI-Powered translators.
To begin with, let us jump into the history of AI.
History of Artificial Intelligence Believe it or not, artificial intelligence was familiarized by a children’s story called The Wizard of Oz. It began with the “heartless” Tin man from the Wizard of Oz and continued with the humanoid robot that impersonated Maria in Metropolis.</description></item><item><title>One Igbo Woman Trying To Save Her Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</guid><description>Oddly, its the feel-good stories which we think are the most important. This week we had a few stories come by which show much progress is being made in the popularity of regional languages.
Here at VideoTranslator we feel that most people are quite proud of where they come from - its totally natural.
Each one of us has a story of how we came to be, and the stories of those who came before are a vital part of any human identity.</description></item><item><title>How To Reach Gen Z Using AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we keep an eye on what everyone else is doing.
Well, we try to anyways. And one of the better resources out there is Social Media Today. This article, &amp;lsquo;What Gen Z is Watching Online - and What That Means for Marketers in 2020&amp;rsquo; is full of wonderful titbits about how to think about video.
How Gen Z Is Using YouTube The big takeaway from the article is that Vlogging and Informative Videos are the biggest draws.</description></item><item><title>Clients: Why You Make Me Blush!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:02 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we get lots of feedback from clients. Most of it is good, some of it not so much. Recently, as we have started to build out our retail client base it has become interesting.
The product challenge with retail is quite different from an enterprise offering or a managed service. Because the user is not being paid to use the product (or being told to by their manager) expectations for the product are totally different.</description></item><item><title>Accessibility: Why It Matters And How To Avoid Being Sued</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work with clients who are part of the healthcare ecosystem.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, voice over artists, or in this case, nurses/doctors. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing - we are technologists who are trying to service our clients to the best of our ability.
Every now and then a story turns up which brings a lot of our work into sharp focus.</description></item><item><title>Quick Transcribe: For When You Need To Get Transcription Done Quickly</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator.Ai, we work closely with the Internationalization And Localization industry. This industry has many different participants, and they use our technology in different ways.
As a software firm, the hardest thing is to really understand what our clients do and why they do these things. Sounds funny, but it is true.
We had a strong response to our previous article, 3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency, and a number of questions and suggestions.</description></item><item><title>Mr Sh*thole: What To Do When Your AI Misbehaves</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</guid><description>Today we look at a humorous articles which look at what happens when AI goes wrong. Here at video translator we like to keep abreast of the latest news in the intersection of Artificial Intelligence, Natural Language Programming, Human Languages and Culture.
Read on to find out how Facebook&amp;rsquo;s AI got in trouble, and why Oracle thinks replacing your manager with a robot is likely, and a good thing to boot!</description></item><item><title>3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work in what is called the Internationalization And Localization industry.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
When do we do this work for our clients? Generally when a client needs a managed service. This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year 2020!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year-2020/</guid><description>Its the start of a new decade! This is a big deal, the only question is will this be the roaring 20&amp;rsquo;s all over again. Here at VideoTranslator we think it is going to be an exciting year.
Several amazing things happened last year, and this was mostly due to the kindness of strangers. Thank you very much to all the folks who took an interest in our work.
We started to get some traction, we found a niche where our tech was useful, and slowly slowly things started to come together.</description></item><item><title>Changes In The Internationalization And Localization Industry</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/changes-in-the-internationalization-and-localization-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/changes-in-the-internationalization-and-localization-industry/</guid><description>Rev.com, a online transcription platform, got in trouble last month. It picked up a negative profile last month by none other than the New York Times.
Even worse was that Rev managed to become the poster child of gig-economy companies who mistreat workers. This led to a lot of negative media coverage which is probably not what Rev is looking to do.
What Set Off Media Focus This article by the NYT set of this series of events.</description></item><item><title>We Just Launched And We Need Luck</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-just-launched-and-we-need-luck/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-just-launched-and-we-need-luck/</guid><description>For the last 2 years or so, we have been working on a new platform which we think will be super useful for content creators. This includes marketers for exporters, tourism concerns, media shops and everyday folks looking to build brands and businesses using tools like YouTube and LinkedIn.
Just for some background, we are a tiny software company, and think of ourselves as basically an independent studio, trying to craft the best tools we can.</description></item></channel></rss>