<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Localization Industry on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/localization-industry/</link><description>Recent content in Localization Industry on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/localization-industry/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Seperti Apa Kerjasama Dengan Perusahaan Penerjemah Video?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/seperti-apa-kerjasama-dengan-perusahaan-penerjemah-video/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/seperti-apa-kerjasama-dengan-perusahaan-penerjemah-video/</guid><description>Halo semuanya!
Beberapa minggu yang lalu, kita baru aja ngebahas tentang penerjemah bertenaga kecerdasan buatan. Kali ini, kita bakalan ngebahas tentang terjemahan video.
Kebanyakan dari kalian pasti udah akrab dengan istilah penerjemah tulisan, misalnya penerjemah buku. Tapi, kebanyakan dari kalian mungkin belum tau tentang istilah penerjemah video. Jadi, apa sih penerjemah video itu?
Terjemahan Video adalah proses menerjemahkan konten video, umumnya dalam bahasa Inggris, ke bahasa lain.
Proses ini bisa melibatkan hal-hal berikut:</description></item><item><title>What Does A Video Translation Partnership Look Like?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-does-a-video-translation-partnership-look-like/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-does-a-video-translation-partnership-look-like/</guid><description>Many people are wondering about video translation. What is it, how to use it, where it may be useful, and what do agreements involving video translation look like?
What Is Video Translation? Video Translation is the process of translating video content, generally in English, to a different language. It can involve the below steps:
Video Transcription Video Translation Video Dubbing (optional)
To learn how video translation actually works, please look at this article.</description></item><item><title>10 TikTok Content Ideas</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/10-tiktok-content-ideas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/10-tiktok-content-ideas/</guid><description>We know that you&amp;rsquo;ve been guilty of spending hours and hours scrolling through your ForYou page on TikTok.
The microblogging app called Tik Tok is the trend these days. Most of the viral videos online come from this platform.
You know as well as we do that TikTok can bring you a lot of traction. So, you also want to make TikTok videos. However, you don’t know what contents you should post.</description></item><item><title>Year In Review 2020</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/year-in-review-2020-may-you-live-in-interesting-times/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/year-in-review-2020-may-you-live-in-interesting-times/</guid><description>Happy New Year 2020 is over. Thankfully.
This might be tempting the fates just a bit, but really, 2021 has got to be better right!
Team VideoTranslator: Happy New Year
Jokes aside, the big learning from 2020 was to be more grateful. The strength shown by people worldwide was extraordinary, and we could not be more grateful for the kindness of strangers, friends, and family in what was a difficult time.</description></item><item><title>One Igbo Woman Trying To Save Her Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</guid><description>Oddly, its the feel-good stories which we think are the most important. This week we had a few stories come by which show much progress is being made in the popularity of regional languages.
Here at VideoTranslator we feel that most people are quite proud of where they come from - its totally natural.
Each one of us has a story of how we came to be, and the stories of those who came before are a vital part of any human identity.</description></item><item><title>How To Reach Gen Z Using AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we keep an eye on what everyone else is doing.
Well, we try to anyways. And one of the better resources out there is Social Media Today. This article, &amp;lsquo;What Gen Z is Watching Online - and What That Means for Marketers in 2020&amp;rsquo; is full of wonderful titbits about how to think about video.
How Gen Z Is Using YouTube The big takeaway from the article is that Vlogging and Informative Videos are the biggest draws.</description></item><item><title>Quick Transcribe: For When You Need To Get Transcription Done Quickly</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator.Ai, we work closely with the Internationalization And Localization industry. This industry has many different participants, and they use our technology in different ways.
As a software firm, the hardest thing is to really understand what our clients do and why they do these things. Sounds funny, but it is true.
We had a strong response to our previous article, 3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency, and a number of questions and suggestions.</description></item><item><title>Mr Sh*thole: What To Do When Your AI Misbehaves</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</guid><description>Today we look at a humorous articles which look at what happens when AI goes wrong. Here at video translator we like to keep abreast of the latest news in the intersection of Artificial Intelligence, Natural Language Programming, Human Languages and Culture.
Read on to find out how Facebook&amp;rsquo;s AI got in trouble, and why Oracle thinks replacing your manager with a robot is likely, and a good thing to boot!</description></item><item><title>3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work in what is called the Internationalization And Localization industry.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
When do we do this work for our clients? Generally when a client needs a managed service. This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.</description></item><item><title>60% Of The Content Produced By US YouTubers Is Watched In Other Countries</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/60-of-the-content-produced-by-us-youtubers-is-watched-in-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/60-of-the-content-produced-by-us-youtubers-is-watched-in-other-countries/</guid><description>Google produces all sorts of very interesting research. I mean, all kinds! One of the specific bits of intel which is well worth tracking is Think With Google.
Today we are going to look at a set of remarkable trend lines which point the way in which the world is heading.
We look at a 3 behaviour and cultural shifts inside YouTube.
2 Behavioural And Cultural Shifts You should really read the article yourself, but the below was what we found super useful.</description></item><item><title>Changes In The Internationalization And Localization Industry</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/changes-in-the-internationalization-and-localization-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/changes-in-the-internationalization-and-localization-industry/</guid><description>Rev.com, a online transcription platform, got in trouble last month. It picked up a negative profile last month by none other than the New York Times.
Even worse was that Rev managed to become the poster child of gig-economy companies who mistreat workers. This led to a lot of negative media coverage which is probably not what Rev is looking to do.
What Set Off Media Focus This article by the NYT set of this series of events.</description></item><item><title>What are the benefits of using Professional Translators?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-are-the-benefits-of-using-professional-translators/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 12:06:52 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-are-the-benefits-of-using-professional-translators/</guid><description>Why do we prefer to use professionals, especially in a business environment? Professionals execute the same tasks regularly, hence they know the in&amp;rsquo;s and the out&amp;rsquo;s of a problem and can solve it better, in a short amount of time and most often with improved costs. Knowledge, practice and experience is valued in all professions. The translation industry is not different and experienced translation professionals are most often preferred.
Using professional translation services should be your preferred default, especially when the content is aimed at business customers.</description></item></channel></rss>