<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kathleen Aikin and Renee Dubé on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/authors/kathleen-aikin-and-renee-dub%C3%A9/</link><description>Recent content in Kathleen Aikin and Renee Dubé on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/authors/kathleen-aikin-and-renee-dub%C3%A9/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What's Hot in Short Video Apps for iOS</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/whats-hot-in-short-video-apps-for-ios/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/whats-hot-in-short-video-apps-for-ios/</guid><description>With the ever increasing popularity of short video apps amongst iOS users, more and more developers are trying to get their apps to the top. This has resulted in a plethora of short video apps being created with different features based on the users needs and wants. We&amp;rsquo;ve taken a look at the top ranking short video apps in the Apple App Store (as of August 2019) to see what these apps for iPhone have to offer.</description></item><item><title>The 8 Best Short Video Apps for Android</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-8-best-short-video-apps-for-android/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-8-best-short-video-apps-for-android/</guid><description>Short video clips continue to gain in popularity along with social platforms like Instagram and Snapchap. As smartphone video technology has improved along with our access to video media online, there has been a growing need for short video apps on smartphones. TechloMedia recently published a report on trending social video apps. We’ve taken a look at these as well as the top performing video apps in the Google Play Store (as of August 2019).</description></item><item><title>9 of China's Best Short Video Apps</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/9-of-chinas-best-short-video-apps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/9-of-chinas-best-short-video-apps/</guid><description>Short video makers are an up and coming category of apps that are really hitting the ground running in China. Short video clips (even less than a second long) have been gaining in popularity along with social platforms like Instagram and Snapchat, and especially in China with Wechat and Weibo. The social component to online video broadcasting has changed how we consume short videos, and what we expect from them.</description></item></channel></rss>