<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Case Study on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/case-study/</link><description>Recent content in Case Study on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/case-study/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flag Monkey Goes Swedish!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/flag-monkey-goes-swedish/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/flag-monkey-goes-swedish/</guid><description>A good friend of ours, Flag Monkey, has been experimenting with AI video translation. Lets have a look at his use case, why he is using our product and what he hopes will work based on the content!
Meet Kevin and Jay! Flag Monkey is a flags and bunting sales business, which relies on social media to create an ecosystem of flag enthusiasts.
So who is Kevin?
Kevin is a puppet, and is the star of the Flag Monkey channel!</description></item><item><title>Is Your AI Talking Back?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/is-your-ai-talking-back-the-cio-show/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/is-your-ai-talking-back-the-cio-show/</guid><description>In a very exciting turn of events, a Google engineer, Blake Lemoine, claimed that an AI he was working on had achieved sentience.
&amp;ldquo;If I didn’t know exactly what it was, which is this computer program we built recently, I’d think it was a 7-year-old, 8-year-old kid that happens to know physics,&amp;rdquo; the 41-year-old Lemoine told The Washington Post.
This was obviously quite a provocative claim, as ZeroHedge reported.
Google Engineer Placed On Leave After Insisting Company&amp;#39;s AI Is Sentient</description></item><item><title>What Makes Translation So Difficult?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-makes-translation-so-difficult/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-makes-translation-so-difficult/</guid><description>The earliest language is believed to have evolved between 50,000 and 150,000 years ago, which is around the time when modern humans emerged. Today, over 7,000 languages exist.
The sheer number of languages now available makes translation so challenging, but what exactly are the reasons?
What Makes Translation So Difficult? Most linguists face these challenges when it comes to translation.
1 - Idioms An idiom is an expression that cannot be understood from the meanings of its separate words but that has a separate meaning of its own.</description></item><item><title>What Does A Video Translation Partnership Look Like?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-does-a-video-translation-partnership-look-like/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-does-a-video-translation-partnership-look-like/</guid><description>Many people are wondering about video translation. What is it, how to use it, where it may be useful, and what do agreements involving video translation look like?
What Is Video Translation? Video Translation is the process of translating video content, generally in English, to a different language. It can involve the below steps:
Video Transcription Video Translation Video Dubbing (optional)
To learn how video translation actually works, please look at this article.</description></item><item><title>Leaving A Long-Lasting Legacy: Curating Your Family’s History</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/leaving-a-long-lasting-legacy-by-curating-your-familys-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/leaving-a-long-lasting-legacy-by-curating-your-familys-history/</guid><description>I believe everyone wants to leave a legacy.
Many people choose to pass on their homes, investments and possessions.
For Jeff Dormish, leaving a legacy means so much more than that. He does not just want to leave possessions; he wants to pass on his history.
For many Americans, most of their ancestors came from Europe in the great emigration wave before the First World War. Jeff Dormish’s ancestors also came from Europe, Slovenia, to be exact.</description></item><item><title>How To Conveniently Translate Your Videos</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-conveniently-translate-your-videos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-conveniently-translate-your-videos/</guid><description>Many of you would have heard about translation. According to Kristen Malmkjær, translation is an activity that aims to convey meaning or meanings of a given linguistic discourse from one language to another.
What are the difficulties in translation? As a multilingual speaker, I have frequently asked to translate different languages. My family would ask me to translate files such as reports, articles and legal documents. However, translation also comes with its challenges.</description></item><item><title>Why Should You Translate Video Content: A Client Perspective</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-translate-video-content-a-client-perspective/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-translate-video-content-a-client-perspective/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we do a lot of work in the Internationalization And Localization industry.
But we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.
Sometimes however, the most useful thing we can do is just have a conversation.</description></item><item><title>How NSW Health Is Using Video Translation To Empower Occupational Therapists</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</guid><description>One major challenge in diverse societies is the provision of healthcare services.
In western Sydney, this problem is directly tackled by the South-West Sydney Local Health District, which sits under New South Wales Health.
Ok - so obviously this is complicated stuff. But how does video translation help?
If you don't speak good English, specifically business English, finding information is very hard. The doctor is the only resource who can help, but what happens when they don't speak your language?</description></item><item><title>How Vyasa University Is Fighting Covid With Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</guid><description>Vivekananda Yoga Anusandhana Samsthana or VYASA is a registered charitable institution (1986) working to make Yoga a socially relevant field of study.
Based on the teachings of Swami Vivekananda, Vyasa University combines the four streams of Yoga with unity in their diversity, the key essence of Indian culture, applications of Yoga to bring health, harmony, peace the world over are now spread across the globe in nearly 30 countries.
Vyasa University: Using scientific research to bring Yoga into the modern world!</description></item><item><title>How QAChef Is Reaching Clients In A Tough Market</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</guid><description>The hospitality business is in a hard place right now because of Covid 19.
QAChef is a technology company which digitizes food safety compliance processes through a single handheld device, thus enabling unprecedented ingredient-to-customer food traceability and greater efficiency and productivity.
QAChef&amp;#39;s handheld device being used to measure temperature during cooking So QAChef is in a fantastic position, a ready for market product which enhances traceability across large scale food production - perfect given the focus on food safety and associated health implications in the wake of the Covid-19 pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Translate Your English Video Into Filipino And Chinese</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</guid><description>Business today relies on content creation. How do you expand your market? We show you how to add open captions for accessibility wins, and translate your video content into Tagalog and Chinese to expand your target client base!
Matija Squire is a LinkedIn coach, all round nice person plus a good friend. And she is doing something really cool!
We all know Covid-19 has distrupted all our lives. Some of us are lucky enough to be able to earn an income by working from home online.</description></item><item><title>How AI Dubbing Will Change Everything: Building A Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</guid><description>There is a very interesting piece of content we are looking at today. A team from IIIT-H (Indian Institute of Information Technology - Hyderabad) has build an AI which translates and lip-syncs a video from one language to another.
This originally came to our attention in this article from the folks at TNW. The paper this article is based on is here, and if you are interested in AI/Language you should absolutely have a look.</description></item><item><title>Clients: Why You Make Me Blush!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:02 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we get lots of feedback from clients. Most of it is good, some of it not so much. Recently, as we have started to build out our retail client base it has become interesting.
The product challenge with retail is quite different from an enterprise offering or a managed service. Because the user is not being paid to use the product (or being told to by their manager) expectations for the product are totally different.</description></item></channel></rss>