<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hindi on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/tags/hindi/</link><description>Recent content in Hindi on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/tags/hindi/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Vyasa University Is Fighting Covid With Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</guid><description>Vivekananda Yoga Anusandhana Samsthana or VYASA is a registered charitable institution (1986) working to make Yoga a socially relevant field of study.
Based on the teachings of Swami Vivekananda, Vyasa University combines the four streams of Yoga with unity in their diversity, the key essence of Indian culture, applications of Yoga to bring health, harmony, peace the world over are now spread across the globe in nearly 30 countries.
Vyasa University: Using scientific research to bring Yoga into the modern world!</description></item><item><title>How To Translate YouTube Videos And Dominate SEO</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</guid><description>The basic steps to translate a YouTube video are:
Download the video to your computer. Upload the video into an AI transcription service. Get the transcript in an .srt file. Translate the transcript using an AI translation service. Embed the translation into your video. You should only translate videos that you expect a good Return On Investment from - so you have a good feeling this video will work in a different language.</description></item><item><title>Speaking In The Mother Tongue: AI Indian Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</guid><description>We recently came across an article with the exciting news that the Indian government is planning on making its Internet content available in regional languages &amp;ldquo;to remove the language barrier among Indians.&amp;quot;
Currently websites are available in English and Hindi but that leaves out the remaining 20 regional languages that are spoken across the country.
&amp;ldquo;We need a method through which any Indian using his or her language should be able to converse with any user in any other Indian language without the impediment of English as a link language.</description></item><item><title>60% Of The Content Produced By US YouTubers Is Watched In Other Countries</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/60-of-the-content-produced-by-us-youtubers-is-watched-in-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/60-of-the-content-produced-by-us-youtubers-is-watched-in-other-countries/</guid><description>Google produces all sorts of very interesting research. I mean, all kinds! One of the specific bits of intel which is well worth tracking is Think With Google.
Today we are going to look at a set of remarkable trend lines which point the way in which the world is heading.
We look at a 3 behavior and cultural shifts inside YouTube.
2 Behavioural And Cultural Shifts You should really read the article yourself, but the below was what we found super useful.</description></item><item><title>What A Hindi Speaking AI Sounds Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</guid><description>A few posts ago we transcribed an Indian English video using a Speech-To-Text Indian English transcription Artificial Intelligence (AI). Today we are going to take the same idea forward, and now going to translate the video into Hindi.
To recap, we used a sample clip from Rajya Sabha TV which as (a) transcribed using a speech-to-text AI, and (b) cleaned up by a human. We will now clean it up a little bit more, and then translate the content into Hindi.</description></item><item><title>The Growing Pains Of Diversity And A Possible Solution</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-growing-pains-of-diversity-and-a-possible-solution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-growing-pains-of-diversity-and-a-possible-solution/</guid><description>This post is not really about diversity. It is about the granular challenges around governance in an increasingly complex world, and operational solutions which may work going forward.
We look at three events which took place in this week. What the problem is, and what a solution might be. These events are:
Trump Administration’s Deregulation Drive Begins to Impact Language Industry Sometimes Lost In Translation, With Dialects Context Is Key Translating verdicts will help all litigants Trump Administration’s Deregulation Drive Begins to Impact Language Industry US federal regulations have generally favored the language services industry.</description></item><item><title>Product Update: May 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/product-update-may-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/product-update-may-2019/</guid><description>We have been putting in for a number of grant applications in the innovation space. One of the applications needed a small video as part of the application process.
The video covers the basic use cases, and we added the captions to the asset.
May 2019: Product update Product Update: May 2019 (English)
Conclusion Please connect with us on LinkedIn, YouTube or Facebook for any comments, questions, or just to keep up to date with the work we do!</description></item><item><title>मोम का हाथ बनाने की कला: अंग्रेजी से हिंदी मे वीडियो अनुवादित</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A5-%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%A8%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%A4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A5-%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%A8%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%A4/</guid><description>यह वीडियो मैडम तुसाद सिडनी यूट्यूब पृष्ठ से है और यह मैडम तुसाद सिडनी में मोम के हाथ बनाने के बारे में है, जहां वे तरल मोम से लोगों के हाथ के नक्से, कुछ सरल चरणों का पालन करके बनाते है।
प्रक्रिया के अनुसार ठंडे पानी में लोगों के हाथों को डुबोना, और फिर तरल मोम में उनके हाथ डुबोने शामिल है । यह करीब 5 बार दोहराया जाता है, हाथों का सांचा बनाने के लिए ।</description></item><item><title>The Art Of Making Wax Hands: English To Hindi Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-art-of-making-wax-hands-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-art-of-making-wax-hands-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</guid><description>This video is from Madame Tussauds Sydney&amp;rsquo;s Youtube page and it is about making wax hands at Madame Tussauds Sydney, where they make moulds of people hands out of liquid wax, by following a few simple steps.
The process involves dipping people hands into cold water, and then dipping their hands in liquid wax. This is repeated about 5 times, to make a mould of the hands.
The Art Of Making Wax Hands: English Video Translation From English To Hindi</description></item><item><title>एक प्रकृति की कला बंगू यिलबारा संग्रह: अंग्रेजी से हिंदी वीडियो प्रतिलेखन और अनुवाद</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%83%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%82-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%B9-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%83%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%82-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%AC%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%B9-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</guid><description>हमें यह वीडियो म्यूजियम ऑफ कंटेम्पररी आर्ट् ऑस्ट्रेलिया के वेबसाइट के यूट्यूब पृष्ठ से मिला है ।
यह वीडियो एमसीए कलेक्शन के बंगू यिलबारा कला के बारे में है । बंगू यिलबारा शब्द अपने आप में कला के प्रयास का वर्णन है, और उस काम को बनाने का इरादा के लिए , प्रदर्शनी के लिए काम का वर्णन करने पर ज्यादा ध्यान केंद्रित नहीं करना है।
प्रदर्शनी कुछ अतिरिक्त लेबल के बिना जीवन की वास्तविकता के साथ संपर्क में लाने के लिए, प्रयास और दृष्टि के लिए कलाकार अभ्यास से संबंधित कला को प्रदर्शित करने पर केंद्रित है।</description></item><item><title>A Nature Of Art Bangu Yilbara Collection: English To Hindi Video Transcription And Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-nature-of-art-bangu-yilbara-collection-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-nature-of-art-bangu-yilbara-collection-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</guid><description>We got this video from Museum of Contemporary Art Australia&amp;rsquo;s Youtube page This video is about Bangu Yilbara collection at the MCA. The collection is focused on art produced by the Aboriginal and Torres Straits Islander cultures.
The exhibition focuses on the diversity of Aboriginal and Torres Straits Islander culture, primarily by looking to the artists to define their work, as opposed to labelling the work &amp;lsquo;Aboriginal&amp;rsquo; and boxing it into any particular style.</description></item><item><title>ऑस्ट्रेलियाई फैशन के माध्यम से एक यात्रा: अंग्रेजी से हिंदी में वीडियो प्रतिलेख और अनुवाद</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%91%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%88-%E0%A4%AB%E0%A5%88%E0%A4%B6%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A7%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A4%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%91%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%88-%E0%A4%AB%E0%A5%88%E0%A4%B6%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A7%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A4%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</guid><description>ये वीडियो है म्यूजियम ऑफ एप्लाइड आर्ट्स एंड साइंसेज यूट्यूब चैनल। यह वीडियो म्यूजियम ऑफ एप्लाइड आर्ट्स एंड साइंसेज (मॉस) के परिधान और डिजाइन संग्रह के बारे में है।
परिधान संग्रह 18 वीं सदी से वर्तमान उदाहरण के टुकड़े को दर्शाता है। इन्हें मॉस के नए सेंटर फॉर फैशन में दिखाया गया है । कुल मिलाकर लगभग 30,000 अद्भुत टुकड़े हैं, जो मॉस, आशा करता हैं कि भविष्य की पीढ़ियों के फैशन डिजाइनरों को प्रभावित और प्रेरित करेंगे।</description></item><item><title>A Journey Through Australian Fashion: English To Hindi Video Transcription And Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-journey-through-australian-fashion-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-journey-through-australian-fashion-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</guid><description>This video is from Museum of Applied Arts and Sciences Youtube channel. This video is about the garments and design collection at the Museum of Applied Arts and Sciences (MAAS).
The garment collection covers pieces from the 18th century to present day examples. These are shown at the new Centre For Fashion at MAAS. There are around 30,000 amazing pieces in total, which MAAS hopes will impact and inspire future generations of fashion designers.</description></item><item><title>वीडियो अनुवाद किया गया अंग्रेजी से हिंदी में: एक कोन्विक्ट हेरिटेज</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%97%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%97%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C/</guid><description>आज का वीडियो हयडे पार्क बैरक्स म्यूजियमस से है। यूटूब पेज, विशेष रूप से यह वीडियो है । हम इस वीडियो को अंग्रेजी से हिंदी में बदल देंगे ।
हाइडल पार्क बैरक्स म्यूजियम नवीनीकरण के दौर से गुजर रहा है । इस 2019 के अंत तक पूरा होने की उम्मीद है । क्यूरेटर और शोधकर्ताओं द्वारा नए शोध की एक बड़ी मात्रा हाइड पार्क बैरक में स्थित संग्रहालय को फिर से खोलने के बाद दिखाए जाने की उम्मीद है। यह नया प्रदर्शन ऑस्ट्रेलिया की सिद्धदोष विरासत के बारे में है । प्रारंभिक औपनिवेशिक ऑस्ट्रेलिया में अपराधियों के प्रभाव का दस्तावेजीकरण किया गया है, आंखों के माध्यम से देखा स्थानीय आदिवासी लोगों, और बसने वाले दोनों ने।</description></item><item><title>Video Translation From English To Hindi: A Convict Heritage</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-from-english-to-hindi-a-convict-heritage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-from-english-to-hindi-a-convict-heritage/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s video is from the Hyde Park Barracks Museum&amp;rsquo;s Youtube page, specifically this video. We will convert this video from English to Hindi.
Hyde Park Barracks Museum is undergoing a refurbishment. This is expected to be complete late 2019. A large amount of new research by curators and researchers based at Hyde Park Barracks is also expected to be shown once the museum is reopened.
This new exhibit is about Australia&amp;rsquo;s convict heritage.</description></item><item><title>How To Get The Most Out Of Your AI: English To Hindi Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-get-the-most-out-of-your-ai-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-get-the-most-out-of-your-ai-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</guid><description>Today, we will cover simple heuristics to get the most out of your AI. As always, use the AI to do the heavy lifting, and use a human subject matter expert to finesse the results, producing a superior outcome with less time/effort.
The process followed is:
Transcribe the Gram Marg (literally, &amp;lsquo;road map&amp;rsquo; in Hindi) video using Indian English. Clean up the transcribed Gram Marg video, and present simple heuristics to the the most out of your AI.</description></item><item><title>How To Transcribe A Foreign Language Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-a-foreign-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-a-foreign-language/</guid><description>Today we are going to look at how to transcribe a foreign language video. But how does this work when we live in a globalised world where people are from many different places - exactly what is foreign?
Well, Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here.
What we are looking at today, is how to transcribe a video in an language you do not know.</description></item><item><title>Multi-Lingual Forms... What Black Magic Is This???</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/multi-lingual-forms-what-black-magic-is-this/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/multi-lingual-forms-what-black-magic-is-this/</guid><description>We live in a modern world, which means working with colleagues, internal and external stakeholder, and clients from different backgrounds. For everyday interactions, this is fine, but every now and then, it can get messy.
Does this resonate with you? An important client in Asia needs something, and they are not happy. However, the operations person you are speaking to does not speak great English, and so an important deal has been bungled.</description></item></channel></rss>