<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Healthcare on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/healthcare/</link><description>Recent content in Healthcare on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/healthcare/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How AI Dubbing Will Change Everything: Building A Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</guid><description>There is a very interesting piece of content we are looking at today. A team from IIIT-H (Indian Institute of Information Technology - Hyderabad) has build an AI which translates and lip-syncs a video from one language to another.
This originally came to our attention in this article from the folks at TNW. The paper this article is based on is here, and if you are interested in AI/Language you should absolutely have a look.</description></item><item><title>Accessibility: Why It Matters And How To Avoid Being Sued</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work with clients who are part of the healthcare ecosystem.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, voice over artists, or in this case, nurses/doctors. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing - we are technologists who are trying to service our clients to the best of our ability.
Every now and then a story turns up which brings a lot of our work into sharp focus.</description></item><item><title>English German Video Translation (What is a Babybündel?)</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/english-to-german-video-translation-what-is-a-babyb%C3%BCndel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/english-to-german-video-translation-what-is-a-babyb%C3%BCndel/</guid><description>Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here. What we are going to do today is transcribe content to a different language, and use a practical example to demonstrate the technology.
We will be using this video, from the team at NSWHealth. The video is a simple, but effective solution for young mothers, where NSWHealth provide a useful box of household items aimed at first time mothers.</description></item></channel></rss>