<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Visual Guides on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/visual-guides/</link><description>Recent content in Visual Guides on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/visual-guides/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AI Internationalization: How Subtitling Can Boost ROI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</guid><description>Today we look at how to boost ROI or ROAS across your video production lifecycle, and how to make structural decisions which will pay off over a long time frame.
ROI or ROAS: Which One Should I Use? Its actually a pretty messy question, but here are the basics.
ROI: Return On Investment Getting a definition is the starting point, and according to the smart folks at Investopia:
Return on Investment (ROI) is a performance measure used to evaluate the efficiency of an investment or compare the efficiency of a number of different investments.</description></item><item><title>Video Series: How to Quickly Transcribe Your Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-series-how-to-quickly-transcribe-your-video/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-series-how-to-quickly-transcribe-your-video/</guid><description>The QuickTranscribe feature is our most used feature in the video transcription and translation process.
Our easy how-to guide on using the Quick Transcribe feature. For more information on Quick Transcribe visit our written guide here.
How to quickly transcribe your video
We are very grateful for your support!
Please connect with us on LinkedIn, YouTube or Facebook for any comments, questions, or just to keep up to date with the work we do!</description></item><item><title>A Step by Step Guide to Translating Your First Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-step-by-step-guide-to-translating-your-first-video/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-step-by-step-guide-to-translating-your-first-video/</guid><description>Having the ability to translate your video into a number of different languages and dialects puts your business a step ahead of the rest in means of reaching a larger audience and in turn, customers.
But getting your content translated and transcribed into another language seems expensive and time consuming, right?
Good news, friend. You&amp;rsquo;re wrong!
Dubbing and/or subtitling your video is a quick and easy process if you&amp;rsquo;re using our app and we hope that&amp;rsquo;s why you&amp;rsquo;re here&amp;hellip; to find out how to do it.</description></item><item><title>Translate Your English Video Into Filipino And Chinese</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</guid><description>Business today relies on content creation. How do you expand your market? We show you how to add open captions for accessibility wins, and translate your video content into Tagalog and Chinese to expand your target client base!
Matija Squire is a LinkedIn coach, all round nice person plus a good friend. And she is doing something really cool!
We all know Covid-19 has distrupted all our lives. Some of us are lucky enough to be able to earn an income by working from home online.</description></item><item><title>How To Translate YouTube Videos And Dominate SEO</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</guid><description>The basic steps to translate a YouTube video are:
Download the video to your computer. Upload the video into an AI transcription service. Get the transcript in an *.srt file. Translate the transcript using an AI translation service. Embed the translation into your video. You should only translate videos that you expect a good Return On Investment from - so you have a good feeling this video will work in a different language.</description></item><item><title>Clipping Chinese App: How To Translate Video Into Mandarin Chinese With AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</guid><description>One very common use case of video translator is as a Chinese clipping app. What is a Chinese clipping app?
This term is used by content creators to mean how to translate a video from English to Chinese, and they generally mean a short video for various social media channels.
In this blog post we are going to look at how to translate a small video from English to Mandarin (Simplified Chinese).</description></item><item><title>How AI Dubbing Will Change Everything: Building A Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</guid><description>There is a very interesting piece of content we are looking at today. A team from IIIT-H (Indian Institute of Information Technology - Hyderabad) has build an AI which translates and lip-syncs a video from one language to another.
This originally came to our attention in this article from the folks at TNW. The paper this article is based on is here, and if you are interested in AI/Language you should absolutely have a look.</description></item><item><title>How To Reach Gen Z Using AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we keep an eye on what everyone else is doing.
Well, we try to anyways. And one of the better resources out there is Social Media Today. This article, &amp;lsquo;What Gen Z is Watching Online - and What That Means for Marketers in 2020&amp;rsquo; is full of wonderful titbits about how to think about video.
How Gen Z Is Using YouTube The big takeaway from the article is that Vlogging and Informative Videos are the biggest draws.</description></item><item><title>Quick Transcribe: For When You Need To Get Transcription Done Quickly</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator.Ai, we work closely with the Internationalization And Localization industry. This industry has many different participants, and they use our technology in different ways.
As a software firm, the hardest thing is to really understand what our clients do and why they do these things. Sounds funny, but it is true.
We had a strong response to our previous article, 3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency, and a number of questions and suggestions.</description></item><item><title>3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work in what is called the Internationalization And Localization industry.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
When do we do this work for our clients? Generally when a client needs a managed service. This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.</description></item><item><title>What A Hindi Speaking AI Sounds Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</guid><description>A few posts ago we transcribed an Indian English video using a Speech-To-Text Indian English transcription Artificial Intelligence (AI). Today we are going to take the same idea forward, and now going to translate the video into Hindi.
To recap, we used a sample clip from Rajya Sabha TV which as (a) transcribed using a speech-to-text AI, and (b) cleaned up by a human. We will now clean it up a little bit more, and then translate the content into Hindi.</description></item><item><title>Open Captions: Enhancements November 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/open-captions-enhancements-november-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/open-captions-enhancements-november-2019/</guid><description>Working with a prospect, we added a number of enhancements to our open captions workflow. If you are interested in what open captions are and what its use cases are please have a look at this blog post.
Very simply open captions are generally used as an accessibility tool focused on people who have hearing impairments. More recently due to the rise of streaming services, open captions have been making a come back.</description></item><item><title>Transcribing Indian English: A Simple Guide To Using AI To Speed Up Transcription And Add Open Captions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcribing-indian-english-a-simple-guide-to-using-ai-to-speed-up-transcription-and-add-open-captions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcribing-indian-english-a-simple-guide-to-using-ai-to-speed-up-transcription-and-add-open-captions/</guid><description>Today we are going to look at how to transcribe Indian English. Firstly of course, what is Indian English, and what does it sound like? How many such dialects exist? Have a look.
Now that we know what Indian English sounds like, we are going to use a short clip from Rajya Sabha TV, an Indian government content creator. We use our AI to transcribe this clip.
Lastly, we add an Auto-Overlay so that we can show you the video.</description></item><item><title>AI Transcription, Translation And Dubbing: How To Think About Accuracy</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-transcription-translation-and-dubbing-how-to-think-about-accuracy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-transcription-translation-and-dubbing-how-to-think-about-accuracy/</guid><description>We get a number of questions around AI Accuracy, and depending on the context, the question can refer to a number of things.
Wanted to put down a note describing the various iterations of what Accuracy in Artificial Intelligence refers to, and where it is going from my point of view.
Is the AI accurate? Is AI accurate when it comes to Transcription? Is AI accurate when it comes to Translation?</description></item><item><title>Text-To-Speech: AI Dubbing And What You Can Do With It</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/text-to-speech-ai-dubbing-and-what-you-can-do-with-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/text-to-speech-ai-dubbing-and-what-you-can-do-with-it/</guid><description>Today we are going to look AI dubbing and its various use cases. If you are wondering, is my content suitable for AI dubbing, or AI localisation? In simple terms:
What is dubbing or dub localisation? Should I use a human, or a machine for my dubbing? How do I use a video translator to dub my video? Rules of thumb, or heuristics, to achieve a superior outcome with AI dubbing?</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Open Captions for Deaf and Hard of Hearing People</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/importance-of-open-captions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/importance-of-open-captions/</guid><description>It comes as no surprise that for hard of hearing and deaf people, closed captions are a necessity for being able to watch TV, films and online videos. We&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned before the need for more captions and subtitles to be present in cinemas and as highlighted in this Washington Post article, &amp;ldquo;accessing online material&amp;hellip;can be a challenge for differently abled people.&amp;rdquo;
This is one of the reasons we believe it is so important to include open captions in online videos.</description></item><item><title>Transcripción y Traducción de Videos de Español a Inglés</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcripci%C3%B3n-y-traducci%C3%B3n-de-videos-de-espa%C3%B1ol-a-ingl%C3%A9s/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcripci%C3%B3n-y-traducci%C3%B3n-de-videos-de-espa%C3%B1ol-a-ingl%C3%A9s/</guid><description>Este video pertenece al canal de YouTube Mariel de Viaje.
El video ofrece consejos básicos para afrontar con facilidad, comodidad y familiaridad cualquier viaje en plan turístico a la República Dominicana, e incluye sugerencias para visitar lugares emblemáticos como Punta Cana y Santo Domingo.
La República Dominicana es el segundo país más grande y diverso del Caribe. Cuenta con vuelos directos desde las principales ciudades de Latinoamérica, Estados Unidos, Canadá y Europa, es un país que se destaca por la calidez de su clima y la hospitalidad de su gente.</description></item><item><title>Transcripción y Traducción de Videos de Inglés a Español</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcripci%C3%B3n-y-traducci%C3%B3n-de-videos-de-ingl%C3%A9s-a-espa%C3%B1ol/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcripci%C3%B3n-y-traducci%C3%B3n-de-videos-de-ingl%C3%A9s-a-espa%C3%B1ol/</guid><description>Este video pertenece al canal de YouTube History Matters. El video habla sobre el personaje histórico ruso con repercusiones en la historia universal, Ivan El Terrible.
Iván IV Vasílievich, llamado Iván el Terrible, fue un gran príncipe de Moscú y de toda Rusia, además de ser el primer monarca ruso en adoptar el título de Zar. Es considerado como uno de los creadores del Estado Ruso.
Pasos A Seguir Abre tu navegador y dirígete a videotranslator.</description></item><item><title>Translating Your Video From English To French: A Step By Step Guide</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translating-your-video-from-english-to-french-a-step-by-step-guide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translating-your-video-from-english-to-french-a-step-by-step-guide/</guid><description>The Sydney Opera House is one of the most well known landmarks in the world. With over 10.9 million people visiting it each year, it&amp;rsquo;s obviously one of Australia&amp;rsquo;s hottest tourist spots.
When searching online, the official videos for the Opera House are all in English, which is great for English speakers, but what about those who aren&amp;rsquo;t?
Using the videotranslator.ai app and creating translated videos would be a great way to reach millions of people worldwide who aren&amp;rsquo;t native English speakers.</description></item><item><title>Subtitling For The Win</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/subtitling-for-the-win/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/subtitling-for-the-win/</guid><description>It started with a Tweet, which was then picked up by the Guardian, re-Tweeted and the rest is history. The post got re-tweeted 70K+ times, and liked 74K+ times. That is clearly something which struck a cord. Why?
Who is using subtitles or captions, why are they using it, and how can you also use subtitles or captions. For a technical discussion on subtitles or captions, see this. This post is more about the value in subtitles or captions.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guide: Audio To Text</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-audio-to-text/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-audio-to-text/</guid><description>This post covers how to transcribe audio content. We will use a podcast as our sample audio content, and assume you are on a free trial. This post covers:
Sign into the application. Create an audio specific template. Create a new item, with our audio specific template as parent. Upload our podcast, and then use an Artificial Intelligence (AI) to transcribe our content. On reviewing this visual guide, you will be able to upload your own audio content, and transcribe using an AI.</description></item><item><title>A Journey Through Australian Fashion: English To Hindi Video Transcription And Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-journey-through-australian-fashion-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-journey-through-australian-fashion-english-to-hindi-video-transcription-and-translation/</guid><description>This video is from Museum of Applied Arts and Sciences Youtube channel. This video is about the garments and design collection at the Museum of Applied Arts and Sciences (MAAS).
The garment collection covers pieces from the 18th century to present day examples. These are shown at the new Centre For Fashion at MAAS. There are around 30,000 amazing pieces in total, which MAAS hopes will impact and inspire future generations of fashion designers.</description></item><item><title>वीडियो अनुवाद किया गया अंग्रेजी से हिंदी में: एक कोन्विक्ट हेरिटेज</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%97%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6-%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%97%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8B%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C/</guid><description>आज का वीडियो हयडे पार्क बैरक्स म्यूजियमस से है। [यूटूब पेज] (https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCLjeUPvTffpHRH3CP1_yddA), विशेष रूप से यह वीडियो है । हम इस वीडियो को अंग्रेजी से हिंदी में बदल देंगे ।
हाइडल पार्क बैरक्स म्यूजियम नवीनीकरण के दौर से गुजर रहा है । इस 2019 के अंत तक पूरा होने की उम्मीद है । क्यूरेटर और शोधकर्ताओं द्वारा नए शोध की एक बड़ी मात्रा हाइड पार्क बैरक में स्थित संग्रहालय को फिर से खोलने के बाद दिखाए जाने की उम्मीद है। यह नया प्रदर्शन ऑस्ट्रेलिया की सिद्धदोष विरासत के बारे में है । प्रारंभिक औपनिवेशिक ऑस्ट्रेलिया में अपराधियों के प्रभाव का दस्तावेजीकरण किया गया है, आंखों के माध्यम से देखा स्थानीय आदिवासी लोगों, और बसने वाले दोनों ने।</description></item><item><title>Video Translation From English To Hindi: A Convict Heritage</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-from-english-to-hindi-a-convict-heritage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-from-english-to-hindi-a-convict-heritage/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s video is from the Hyde Park Barracks Museum&amp;rsquo;s Youtube page, specifically this video. We will convert this video from English to Hindi.
Hyde Park Barracks Museum is undergoing a refurbishment. This is expected to be complete late 2019. A large amount of new research by curators and researchers based at Hyde Park Barracks is also expected to be shown once the museum is reopened.
This new exhibit is about Australia&amp;rsquo;s convict heritage.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guide: Free Trial Registration</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-free-trial-registration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-free-trial-registration/</guid><description>Everyone likes to try before they buy. This post is a visual guide to how to sign up for the free trial, and logging into the Video Translator platform. This post covers:
Sign up for the free trial Select your preferred languages Verify your email address, and log into the application On reviewing this visual guide, you should be able to sign up to Video Translator platform for free, and transcribe and translate up to 20 minutes of video content.</description></item><item><title>How To Use Auto Overlay To Simplify Transcription</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-auto-overlay-to-simplify-transcription/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-auto-overlay-to-simplify-transcription/</guid><description>We got this video from OSL Brokerage&amp;rsquo;s LinkedIn page. We are not suggesting that we have any relationship with OSL, and largely, we are using this content to demonstrate the process by which video content can be translated.
This specific video already has captions, so we don&amp;rsquo;t need these per se. However, we will be adding Chinese captions as an overlay, as opposed to captions.
The final output is shown below.</description></item><item><title>We Have An Explainer Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-have-an-explainer-video/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-have-an-explainer-video/</guid><description>We are a Sydney based, media focused technology platform provider, looking to make the world a more accessible place. Our primary value proposition is a transcription and translation platform, with a focus on audio and video content.
Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s translation platform (&amp;ldquo;the application&amp;rdquo;) is an Internet-enabled SaaS (Software as a Service) platform which assists content creators (&amp;ldquo;the client&amp;rdquo;) to engage with stakeholders (&amp;ldquo;the audience&amp;rdquo;) from different linguistic backgrounds. The application is used to convert hypermedia content from one language to another, using an Artificial Intelligence (AI) assisted process.</description></item><item><title>How To Get The Most Out Of Your AI: English To Hindi Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-get-the-most-out-of-your-ai-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-get-the-most-out-of-your-ai-english-to-hindi-video-translation/</guid><description>Today, we will cover simple heuristics to get the most out of your AI. As always, use the AI to do the heavy lifting, and use a human subject matter expert to finesse the results, producing a superior outcome with less time/effort.
The process followed is:
Transcribe the Gram Marg (literally, &amp;lsquo;road map&amp;rsquo; in Hindi) video using Indian English. Clean up the transcribed Gram Marg video, and present simple heuristics to the the most out of your AI.</description></item><item><title>How To Transcribe English Into Hebrew: ChangePlan</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-english-into-hebrew-changeplan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-english-into-hebrew-changeplan/</guid><description>Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here. Today, we will be using the video translation platform on a video from our friends at ChangePlan. We will do the following:
Transcribe ChangePlan&amp;rsquo;s video using Australian English. Fix up spelling/grammar in our captions. Translate ChangePlan&amp;rsquo;s video from English -&amp;gt; Hebrew. If you are looking to replicate this process, please note, after the translation step, it is highly recommended that you have a Hebrew qualified subject-matter expert finesse the captions.</description></item><item><title>How To Add A Forum To Your Website</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-add-a-forum-to-your-website/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-add-a-forum-to-your-website/</guid><description>Given we are getting super close to launch, there are a lot of conversations with prospects who are keen to use our product. We get many (welcome) questions from prospects/clients on how to use the platform. Additionally, because we are a new start up, we don't have great documentation. How to solve this problem with limited bandwidth?
The requirement is pretty simple, an easy way to communicate with prospects and clients, which stacks.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Manage Your Account</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-manage-your-account/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-manage-your-account/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s post we look at how to manage your account. This will cover Root and Management workspaces. The ordering reflects the navigation pane at the top right of the application. Please note, for more information covering how to add and remove languages specifically, please have a look at this post. Information about the Finance section will be covered in a later post.
This post is written to explain the use cases of account management, and why options are laid out as they are - if we have reached out to you for feedback, please feel free to come back with ideas on how you use/would like to use the interface.</description></item><item><title>More Text-To-Speech Transcription!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/more-text-to-speech-transcription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/more-text-to-speech-transcription/</guid><description>Our platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here. Recently, we added a number of additional languages specific to Text-To-Speech transcription. These are, (a) French (Canadian), (b) Portuguese (Brazilian), (c) Spanish, (d) Swedish, and (e) Turkish.
In total, Text-To-Speech transcription now has the below set of languages available. Please note each language has multiple dialects, and gender specific voices are available.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Add Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-add-languages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-add-languages/</guid><description>We look at how to add languages for transcription, translation and transliteration.
That is, assume we have a video in English. We now need to translate into French and German. We need to add French and add German into our account, before the transcription or translation will work.
In brief, we assume that no additional languages were selected during the sign up process, and now we are looking to add additional languages to our account.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Translate A Video without Sound</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-translate-a-video-without-sound/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-translate-a-video-without-sound/</guid><description>We look at how to translate video content. Translation is the communication of the meaning of a source-language text by means of an equivalent target-language text1. In brief, we will (i) upload a video, (ii) add text, (iii) translate the video text, (iv) download a translated video.
Steps We need a sample video to work with, and will use the Big Bunny video from Sample Video&amp;rsquo;s.
To view this video please enable JavaScript, and consider upgrading to a web browser that supports HTML5 video</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Transcribe a Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-transcribe-a-video/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 16:45:05 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-transcribe-a-video/</guid><description>We look at how to transcribe video content. From Wikipedia, &amp;lsquo;Transcription in the linguistic sense is the systematic representation of language in written form. The source can either be utterances (speech or sign language) or pre-existing text in another writing system.&amp;rsquo;
In brief, we will (i) upload our content, (ii) trigger transcription, and (iii) download a video with our embedded transcript. To transcribe your existing video content, please follow the below steps.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Sign-Up</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-sign-up/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 14:45:05 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-sign-up/</guid><description>The below describes how to sign-up to the Video Translator application. Following sign-up, how to login to the platform is also covered.
Steps To sign-up for the application, please follow the below steps:
Please direct your browser to videotranslator.ai, and then click on the Sign Up button.
Please input your email address, and select languages. Your primary language is assumed to be English, and you will be able to select an additional 2 languages (additional languages are available within the application).</description></item></channel></rss>