<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Accessibility on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/accessibility/</link><description>Recent content in Accessibility on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:00:01 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/accessibility/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Implications Of AI Adoption In Our Tools</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-implications-of-ai-adoption-in-our-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-implications-of-ai-adoption-in-our-tools/</guid><description>AI is everywhere in the news these days. But something critical has changed recently.
In the near past, AI has gone from being super fancy to being, well... pedestrian.
Say what now?
Well - AI is becoming ordinary. And turning up in our office/productivity toolkits.
In recent days, Google has expanded its offering using AI, as has Microsoft, and so has Amazon.
What does this mean for how we work, and how can you use this trend to advantage your business?</description></item><item><title>How NSW Health Is Using Video Translation To Empower Occupational Therapists</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</guid><description>One major challenge in diverse societies is the provision of healthcare services.
In western Sydney, this problem is directly tackled by the South-West Sydney Local Health District, which sits under New South Wales Health.
Ok - so obviously this is complicated stuff. But how does video translation help?
If you don't speak good English, specifically business English, finding information is very hard. The doctor is the only resource who can help, but what happens when they don't speak your language?</description></item><item><title>Why YouTube Stopped Community Caption Contributions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</guid><description>Community captions are a function in YouTube. This function allows a YouTube content creator to crowd source captions for their video content.
YouTube is shutting this down. Here is how it will affect you!
Change To Community Contributions On YouTube Notice about an upcoming change to community contributions on YouTube Both creators and viewers have reported problems with the community contributions feature, including spam, abuse, and low quality submissions.</description></item><item><title>How Vyasa University Is Fighting Covid With Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</guid><description>Vivekananda Yoga Anusandhana Samsthana or VYASA is a registered charitable institution (1986) working to make Yoga a socially relevant field of study.
Based on the teachings of Swami Vivekananda, Vyasa University combines the four streams of Yoga with unity in their diversity, the key essence of Indian culture, applications of Yoga to bring health, harmony, peace the world over are now spread across the globe in nearly 30 countries.
Vyasa University: Using scientific research to bring Yoga into the modern world!</description></item><item><title>How QAChef Is Reaching Clients In A Tough Market</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</guid><description>The hospitality business is in a hard place right now because of Covid 19.
QAChef is a technology company which digitizes food safety compliance processes through a single handheld device, thus enabling unprecedented ingredient-to-customer food traceability and greater efficiency and productivity.
QAChef&amp;#39;s handheld device being used to measure temperature during cooking So QAChef is in a fantastic position, a ready for market product which enhances traceability across large scale food production - perfect given the focus on food safety and associated health implications in the wake of the Covid-19 pandemic.</description></item><item><title>How Subtitling Can Boost ROI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</guid><description>Today we look at how to boost ROI or ROAS across your video production lifecycle, and how to make structural decisions which will pay off over a long time frame.
ROI or ROAS: Which One Should I Use? It&amp;rsquo;s actually a pretty messy question, but here are the basics.
ROI: Return on Investment Getting a definition is the starting point, and according to the smart folks at Investopia:
Return on Investment (ROI) is a performance measure used to evaluate the efficiency of an investment or compare the efficiency of a number of different investments.</description></item><item><title>Video Translation And Its Implications For FireTech</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</guid><description>A recent interview with FireTech Connect was really good fun, with Leigh Kelson hosting a free-wheeling discussion about crisis, technology and the future of AI in the internationalization and localization space.
FireTech Connect The FireTech 2020 program is an initiative of the Peregian Digital Hub, a leading technology incubator based in Noosa on Queensland&amp;rsquo;s Sunshine Coast.
FireTech Connect is funded by the Department of Industry, Science, Energy and Resources through the AusIndustry Entrepreneurs’ Programme; The Queensland State Government&amp;rsquo;s Advance Queensland Program; and Noosa Shire Council.</description></item><item><title>AI Localisation: Help Me Help You</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-localisation-help-me-help-you/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-localisation-help-me-help-you/</guid><description>Today we look at AI localisation. Essentially, how to use AI to reach a broader market at scale.
Its a really simple question. Does AI Localisation work at scale?
As always, the answer is yes and no, but mostly it depends on what you are trying to do.
The context is this: localisation project managers often burn themselves out by performing tons of routine operations every single day.
So the question becomes, how to use AI localisation at scale, and then, how to best use AI in localisation efforts at the process level?</description></item><item><title>How To Do Video SEO Right</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-do-video-seo-right/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-do-video-seo-right/</guid><description>There are a large number of reasons as to why people create content. Here is the one thing all content creators have in common.
They need to market their content. And step one is thinking about Search Engine Optimisation (SEO).
This blog post covers what you need to know about making video content indexable, and hence searchable.
Read on to understand what you need to do to make your video SEO friendly!</description></item><item><title>Video SEO: Keywords, Titles, Descriptions And The Transcript</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-seo-keywords-titles-descriptions-and-the-transcript/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-seo-keywords-titles-descriptions-and-the-transcript/</guid><description>This post is dedicated to simple rules to maximise your SEO (Search Engine Optimisation) impact with video content.
There are 4 things you need to do to maximise your video content&amp;rsquo;s SEO impact. They are, title, description, keywords and the transcript, we will look at each one of these in detail.
Why Do Video SEO? From this DeepCrawl article, search engines cannot index video content. This is because search engines can only index text content.</description></item><item><title>What Is The Best Subtitling Software Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-is-the-best-subtitling-software-available/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-is-the-best-subtitling-software-available/</guid><description>Are you a content creator? Or Are you a court reporter looking for an easy way to caption lots of content? This blog post might be for you.
Having captions is very useful these days. Its really good for engagement, and its also really good for accessibility - specifically hearing impaired folk.
However, and there is no getting around this, it is painful to do.
Manual audio or video transcription takes ages.</description></item><item><title>How Safe Is AI Transcription: What You Need To Know</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-safe-is-ai-transcription-what-you-need-to-know/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-safe-is-ai-transcription-what-you-need-to-know/</guid><description>You are a content creator who uses AI.
But how safe is the AI you use, whether for transcription, translation or dubbing. Also some tips on how to use AI better in your journey into expanding your market.
There was a great article on this recently at How-To-Geek.
Ok - so why do you use AI? As a content creator you care about engagement. AI Transcription combined with Open Captions is fantastic for engagement.</description></item><item><title>Translate Your English Video Into Filipino And Chinese</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</guid><description>Business today relies on content creation. How do you expand your market? We show you how to add open captions for accessibility wins, and translate your video content into Tagalog and Chinese to expand your target client base!
Matija Squire is a LinkedIn coach, all round nice person plus a good friend. And she is doing something really cool!
We all know Covid-19 has distrupted all our lives. Some of us are lucky enough to be able to earn an income by working from home online.</description></item><item><title>How To Translate YouTube Videos And Dominate SEO</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</guid><description>The basic steps to translate a YouTube video are:
Download the video to your computer. Upload the video into an AI transcription service. Get the transcript in an .srt file. Translate the transcript using an AI translation service. Embed the translation into your video. You should only translate videos that you expect a good Return On Investment from - so you have a good feeling this video will work in a different language.</description></item><item><title>The Girls and Women Revitalising Canada's Indigenous Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-girls-and-women-revitalising-canadas-indigenous-languages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-girls-and-women-revitalising-canadas-indigenous-languages/</guid><description>It was International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day this past Sunday 8 March and in honour of the day we&amp;rsquo;re looking at some incredible females who are doing all they can for their native languages.
The Girls and Women Revitalising Canada&amp;#39;s Indigenous Languages
Celebrating Indigenous Women Who Are Reclaiming and Revitalising Their Languages Image courtesy of Marion Konwanénhon Delaronde and Karihwiióstha Callie Montour In light of International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day which was this past Sunday, March 8, CBC News in Canada put together an article celebrating a number of Indigenous women and their plight to preserve and revitalise their traditional languages.</description></item><item><title>Clipping Chinese App: How To Translate Video Into Mandarin Chinese With AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</guid><description>One very common use case of video translator is as a Chinese clipping app. What is a Chinese clipping app?
This term is used by content creators to mean how to translate a video from English to Chinese, and they generally mean a short video for various social media channels.
In this blog post we are going to look at how to translate a small video from English to Mandarin (Simplified Chinese).</description></item><item><title>Fighting the Coronavirus and E. Coli with Machine Learning</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/fighting-the-coronavirus-and-e-coli-with-machine-learning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/fighting-the-coronavirus-and-e-coli-with-machine-learning/</guid><description>When it comes to combating superbugs and viruses, the human raced needs all the help it can get. Artificial Intelligence is being implemented to find treatments to fight bacteria that was formally resistant to all forms of antibiotics. China is also using AI to quickly determine if a person is showing symptoms of the coronavirus, which could be a great win against getting a handle on the respiratory disease.
Fighting The Coronavirus And E-Coli With Machine Learning</description></item><item><title>How AI Dubbing Will Change Everything: Building A Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</guid><description>There is a very interesting piece of content we are looking at today. A team from IIIT-H (Indian Institute of Information Technology - Hyderabad) has build an AI which translates and lip-syncs a video from one language to another.
This originally came to our attention in this article from the folks at TNW. The paper this article is based on is here, and if you are interested in AI/Language you should absolutely have a look.</description></item><item><title>How AI Transcription Fails And What To Do About It</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</guid><description>AI Transcription has been all the rage recently. Several companies have been coming out with new products to meet this requirement.
What does it mean? Does it work? How to evaluate these products? We take a look and try to think behind the hype.
First we look at some of the incoming offerings. Then some issues with AI Transcription and Translation.
Incoming Offerings There is a very large number of AI products hitting the market place.</description></item><item><title>One Igbo Woman Trying To Save Her Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</guid><description>Oddly, its the feel-good stories which we think are the most important. This week we had a few stories come by which show much progress is being made in the popularity of regional languages.
Here at VideoTranslator we feel that most people are quite proud of where they come from - its totally natural.
Each one of us has a story of how we came to be, and the stories of those who came before are a vital part of any human identity.</description></item><item><title>How To Reach Gen Z Using AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we keep an eye on what everyone else is doing.
Well, we try to anyways. And one of the better resources out there is Social Media Today. This article, &amp;lsquo;What Gen Z is Watching Online - and What That Means for Marketers in 2020&amp;rsquo; is full of wonderful titbits about how to think about video.
How Gen Z Is Using YouTube The big takeaway from the article is that Vlogging and Informative Videos are the biggest draws.</description></item><item><title>AI &amp; Wildlife Preservation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-and-wildlife-preservation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-and-wildlife-preservation/</guid><description>If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing most of us can agree on, it&amp;rsquo;s that wildlife preservation is important. The animals on this planet have been suffering a lot since we humans came on the scene. Luckily, there are amazing people out there trying to right the wrongs. Using Artificial Intelligence, researchers are able to continue this quest all the more and we&amp;rsquo;re looking into just how that&amp;rsquo;s being done.
How Artificial Intelligence Is Changing Wildlife Research Giraffe populations are rapidly declining but AI is here to help Researcher Jenna Stacy-Dawes and her team at San Diego Zoo&amp;rsquo;s Institute for Conservation Research are being assisted in their work in giraffe conservation with the AI software program, Wildbook.</description></item><item><title>Speaking In The Mother Tongue: AI Indian Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</guid><description>We recently came across an article with the exciting news that the Indian government is planning on making its Internet content available in regional languages &amp;ldquo;to remove the language barrier among Indians.&amp;quot;
Currently websites are available in English and Hindi but that leaves out the remaining 20 regional languages that are spoken across the country.
&amp;ldquo;We need a method through which any Indian using his or her language should be able to converse with any user in any other Indian language without the impediment of English as a link language.</description></item><item><title>Accessibility: Why It Matters And How To Avoid Being Sued</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work with clients who are part of the healthcare ecosystem.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, voice over artists, or in this case, nurses/doctors. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing - we are technologists who are trying to service our clients to the best of our ability.
Every now and then a story turns up which brings a lot of our work into sharp focus.</description></item><item><title>On The Brink Of Extinction: Nearly Dead Languages And The Dedicated Linguists Bringing Them Back To Life</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</guid><description>Thousands of kilometres apart, and in incredibly different cultures; three linguists are doing their part to save the culture of their people through language.
Masahiro Yamada and Natsuko Nakagawa in Japan and Kenny Pheasant in the United States are all passionate about ensuring almost lost languages are preserved and continue to be taught; and a lot of it comes down to teaching the languages to children.
Linguists Work To Preserve Ryukyu Dialects Now Dying Out Image courtesy of Nobuaki Tanaka Professors at the National Institute for Japanese Language and Linguistics made an alarming discovery when they found that many dialects in the Okinawa Prefecture are on the verge of dying out.</description></item><item><title>Sign Languages: Their past, present and future</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/sign-languages-their-past-present-and-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/sign-languages-their-past-present-and-future/</guid><description>For something that is used by an estimated 70 million people worldwide, there is still a lot we don&amp;rsquo;t know when it comes to the origin of sign language - luckily research is being done to change that. Going from the past to the future, Google Translate is developing a way to translate sign language into speech and we are excited about the possibilities that this brings for, well, everyone!</description></item><item><title>Quick Transcribe: For When You Need To Get Transcription Done Quickly</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator.Ai, we work closely with the Internationalization And Localization industry. This industry has many different participants, and they use our technology in different ways.
As a software firm, the hardest thing is to really understand what our clients do and why they do these things. Sounds funny, but it is true.
We had a strong response to our previous article, 3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency, and a number of questions and suggestions.</description></item><item><title>Where are we heading with AI computing in the 2020s? And how human can they really become?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/where-are-we-heading-with-ai-computing-in-the-2020s-and-how-human-can-they-really-become/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/where-are-we-heading-with-ai-computing-in-the-2020s-and-how-human-can-they-really-become/</guid><description>We now well and truly know that Artificial Intelligence is here to stay (and in fact has been for quite some time), but what will become of it, and us, in the future? One author has some very interesting thoughts on how AI computing will reach beyond just recognising how to act like a human but rather see the world the way we do and have a form of common sense.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: January 2020</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-january-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-january-2020/</guid><description>There are a number of bug fixes and patches, which may affect your experience. In fact, we hope it will affect your experience for the better!
Images below are from our UAT environment. Please contact your relationship manager for more information or access.
Fixes include the below. If you have any questions please contact us at hello@videotranslator.ai.
Spaces In FileTemplate And FileItem Names Transcription Without Time-Coding Transcription Copy Function Edit/Exit Modals Removed/Modified Fixes To Locking Cosmetic Fixes To Billing January 2020: Spaces In FileTemplate And FileItem Names Previously, it was not possible to have spaces in fileTemplate and fileItem names.</description></item><item><title>An Old Language Is Young Again...</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/an-old-language-feels-young-again/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/an-old-language-feels-young-again/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we are big fans of the work of Tim Brookes. Recently, his work has included a kickstarter to create art work in traditional Nepalese script known as Ranjana.
We look at a language he shone some light on today. We also look at work Comcast is doing to support hearing impaired clients. This is quite exciting from an operational perspective.
Lastly we look at a recent write up from the Latin Post which looks at how to interface with commercial translation firms for your localisation and internationalization requirements.</description></item><item><title>What A Hindi Speaking AI Sounds Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</guid><description>A few posts ago we transcribed an Indian English video using a Speech-To-Text Indian English transcription Artificial Intelligence (AI). Today we are going to take the same idea forward, and now going to translate the video into Hindi.
To recap, we used a sample clip from Rajya Sabha TV which as (a) transcribed using a speech-to-text AI, and (b) cleaned up by a human. We will now clean it up a little bit more, and then translate the content into Hindi.</description></item><item><title>Winning: We Won The JobsForNSW MVP Grant! Before, During And After...</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/winning-how-we-won-a-jobsfornsw-mvp-grant/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/winning-how-we-won-a-jobsfornsw-mvp-grant/</guid><description>DISCLAIMER: This blog post was updated after having a conversation with JobsForNSW. [3 Dec 2019]
Please check the JobsForNSW website for updates. The process covered below changes regularly and DO NOT rely on the below to be correct going forward. It was correct at time of publication, but talking to the JobsForNSW staff it is LIKELY to change pretty soon.
Earlier this year we put in an application for a Minimum Viable Product Grant from JobsForNSW, a NSW Government initiative.</description></item><item><title>Open Captions: Enhancements November 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/open-captions-enhancements-november-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/open-captions-enhancements-november-2019/</guid><description>Working with a prospect, we added a number of enhancements to our open captions workflow. If you are interested in what open captions are and what its use cases are please have a look at this blog post.
Very simply open captions are generally used as an accessibility tool focused on people who have hearing impairments. More recently due to the rise of streaming services, open captions have been making a come back.</description></item><item><title>Transcribing Indian English: A Simple Guide To Using AI To Speed Up Transcription And Add Open Captions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcribing-indian-english-a-simple-guide-to-using-ai-to-speed-up-transcription-and-add-open-captions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcribing-indian-english-a-simple-guide-to-using-ai-to-speed-up-transcription-and-add-open-captions/</guid><description>Today we are going to look at how to transcribe Indian English. Firstly of course, what is Indian English, and what does it sound like? How many such dialects exist? Have a look.
Now that we know what Indian English sounds like, we are going to use a short clip from Rajya Sabha TV, an Indian government content creator. We use our AI to transcribe this clip.
Lastly, we add an Auto-Overlay so that we can show you the video.</description></item><item><title>Samples From A Voice Over Robot: French, German and Dutch</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</guid><description>Following on from last week&amp;rsquo;s blog post, where we looked at different English dialects, we are going to do much the same today in Dutch, French and German.
Do you like the below examples? Let us know - we are super keen to hear what you think?
To try other languages (for FREE!) sign up to the free trial and give it a go!
Steps First, as per our usual create a new item using the English language template.</description></item><item><title>AI Dubbing: What Different Dialects Of English Sound Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</guid><description>Today we are going to look AI dubbing and look at a few different samples of what an AI can sound like in English. We are going to do something pretty simple, we will use the quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog for our seed text.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what this sentence is, quoting from Wikipedia, &amp;ldquo;The quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog&amp;rdquo; is an English-language pangram—a sentence that contains all of the letters of the alphabet.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Open Captions for Deaf and Hard of Hearing People</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/importance-of-open-captions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/importance-of-open-captions/</guid><description>It comes as no surprise that for hard of hearing and deaf people, closed captions are a necessity for being able to watch TV, films and online videos. We&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned before the need for more captions and subtitles to be present in cinemas and as highlighted in this Washington Post article, &amp;ldquo;accessing online material&amp;hellip;can be a challenge for differently abled people.&amp;rdquo;
This is one of the reasons we believe it is so important to include open captions in online videos.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: September 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-september-2019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-september-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy month for us so far. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of new and exciting features we&amp;rsquo;re still developing so watch this space! In the meantime, there are a couple of updates and patches to tell you about.
Embedding Captions Previously, to embed captions onto your video it was possible to do so from the captions tab. This tab is now only used to make edits to the captions. To embed captions, it is now done by using the Audio Overlay tab.</description></item><item><title>How Video Transcription Works Explainer</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-video-transcription-works-explainer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-video-transcription-works-explainer/</guid><description>We have been working really hard making a number of changes to our underlying application. Specifically we have (i) added a new architecture to our video processing, (ii) added a few more languages, (iii) large number of changes to the look/feel of the product.
All in all, we felt it was time for a new explainer video which covered how to use the platform.
Here it is&amp;hellip; enjoy!
How To Transcribe A Video Using AI Explainer: How to Transcribe A Video Using AI</description></item><item><title>Why Post Video To Social Media: 3 Tips</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-post-video-to-social-media-3-tips/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-post-video-to-social-media-3-tips/</guid><description>Several recent reports show that video content outperforms every other type of post on social media. In other words, using video content in social media marketing is a very good strategy. In this post we look at some numbers, and try to work out what this means for content creators and marketers.
Renderforest put together an insightful report on social video marketing. Here are some of their statistics:
100 million hours of video per day is watched on Facebook.</description></item><item><title>Subtitling For The Win</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/subtitling-for-the-win/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/subtitling-for-the-win/</guid><description>It started with a Tweet, which was then picked up by the Guardian, re-Tweeted and the rest is history. The post got re-tweeted 70K+ times, and liked 74K+ times. That is clearly something which struck a cord. Why?
Who is using subtitles or captions, why are they using it, and how can you also use subtitles or captions. For a technical discussion on subtitles or captions, see this. This post is more about the value in subtitles or captions.</description></item><item><title>Product Update: May 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/product-update-may-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/product-update-may-2019/</guid><description>We have been putting in for a number of grant applications in the innovation space. One of the applications needed a small video as part of the application process.
The video covers the basic use cases, and we added the captions to the asset.
May 2019: Product update Product Update: May 2019 (English)
Conclusion Please connect with us on LinkedIn, YouTube or Facebook for any comments, questions, or just to keep up to date with the work we do!</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: May 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-may-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-may-2019/</guid><description>There are a number of bug fixes and patches, which may affect your user experience. Fixes include (a) and upload bug, (b) a naming convention enhancement, (c) a UI timing bug, (d) UI help bug, and (e) UI folder bug.
May 2019: Upload Bug Previously, if you uploaded certain files, and exceeded certain file sizes, the application would error without notifying the user.
Specifically, on the operational side, we setup all client with file and size permissions at enrolment.</description></item></channel></rss>