<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Enterprise on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/enterprise/</link><description>Recent content in Enterprise on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/enterprise/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Vyasa University Is Fighting Covid With Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</guid><description>Vivekananda Yoga Anusandhana Samsthana or VYASA is a registered charitable institution (1986) working to make Yoga a socially relevant field of study.
Based on the teachings of Swami Vivekananda, Vyasa University combines the four streams of Yoga with unity in their diversity, the key essence of Indian culture, applications of Yoga to bring health, harmony, peace the world over are now spread across the globe in nearly 30 countries.
Vyasa University: Using scientific research to bring Yoga into the modern world!</description></item><item><title>How QAChef Is Reaching Clients In A Tough Market</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</guid><description>The hospitality business is in a hard place right now because of Covid 19.
QAChef is a technology company which digitizes food safety compliance processes through a single handheld device, thus enabling unprecedented ingredient-to-customer food traceability and greater efficiency and productivity.
QAChef&amp;#39;s handheld device being used to measure temperature during cooking So QAChef is in a fantastic position, a ready for market product which enhances traceability across large scale food production - perfect given the focus on food safety and associated health implications in the wake of the Covid-19 pandemic.</description></item><item><title>How Subtitling Can Boost ROI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</guid><description>Today we look at how to boost ROI or ROAS across your video production lifecycle, and how to make structural decisions which will pay off over a long time frame.
ROI or ROAS: Which One Should I Use? It&amp;rsquo;s actually a pretty messy question, but here are the basics.
ROI: Return on Investment Getting a definition is the starting point, and according to the smart folks at Investopia:
Return on Investment (ROI) is a performance measure used to evaluate the efficiency of an investment or compare the efficiency of a number of different investments.</description></item><item><title>Video Translation And Its Implications For FireTech</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</guid><description>A recent interview with FireTech Connect was really good fun, with Leigh Kelson hosting a free-wheeling discussion about crisis, technology and the future of AI in the internationalization and localization space.
FireTech Connect The FireTech 2020 program is an initiative of the Peregian Digital Hub, a leading technology incubator based in Noosa on Queensland&amp;rsquo;s Sunshine Coast.
FireTech Connect is funded by the Department of Industry, Science, Energy and Resources through the AusIndustry Entrepreneurs’ Programme; The Queensland State Government&amp;rsquo;s Advance Queensland Program; and Noosa Shire Council.</description></item><item><title>A Little Positivity: To Brighten Your Day, Week And Month!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-little-positivity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-little-positivity/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m not going to sugarcoat it, this pandemic sucks big time and if you&amp;rsquo;re anything like me, you&amp;rsquo;re overwhelmed with the horrifying statistics and negative news that surrounds this whole thing.
So we&amp;rsquo;re focusing on the good news today. As Fred Rogers famously said, &amp;ldquo;When I was a boy and I would see scary things in the news, my mother would say to me, &amp;lsquo;Look for the helpers. You will always find people who are helping.</description></item><item><title>The Girls and Women Revitalising Canada's Indigenous Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-girls-and-women-revitalising-canadas-indigenous-languages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-girls-and-women-revitalising-canadas-indigenous-languages/</guid><description>It was International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day this past Sunday 8 March and in honour of the day we&amp;rsquo;re looking at some incredible females who are doing all they can for their native languages.
The Girls and Women Revitalising Canada&amp;#39;s Indigenous Languages
Celebrating Indigenous Women Who Are Reclaiming and Revitalising Their Languages Image courtesy of Marion Konwanénhon Delaronde and Karihwiióstha Callie Montour In light of International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day which was this past Sunday, March 8, CBC News in Canada put together an article celebrating a number of Indigenous women and their plight to preserve and revitalise their traditional languages.</description></item><item><title>Fighting the Coronavirus and E. Coli with Machine Learning</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/fighting-the-coronavirus-and-e-coli-with-machine-learning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/fighting-the-coronavirus-and-e-coli-with-machine-learning/</guid><description>When it comes to combating superbugs and viruses, the human raced needs all the help it can get. Artificial Intelligence is being implemented to find treatments to fight bacteria that was formally resistant to all forms of antibiotics. China is also using AI to quickly determine if a person is showing symptoms of the coronavirus, which could be a great win against getting a handle on the respiratory disease.
Fighting The Coronavirus And E-Coli With Machine Learning</description></item><item><title>How AI Dubbing Will Change Everything: Building A Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</guid><description>There is a very interesting piece of content we are looking at today. A team from IIIT-H (Indian Institute of Information Technology - Hyderabad) has build an AI which translates and lip-syncs a video from one language to another.
This originally came to our attention in this article from the folks at TNW. The paper this article is based on is here, and if you are interested in AI/Language you should absolutely have a look.</description></item><item><title>How AI Transcription Fails And What To Do About It</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</guid><description>AI Transcription has been all the rage recently. Several companies have been coming out with new products to meet this requirement.
What does it mean? Does it work? How to evaluate these products? We take a look and try to think behind the hype.
First we look at some of the incoming offerings. Then some issues with AI Transcription and Translation.
Incoming Offerings There is a very large number of AI products hitting the market place.</description></item><item><title>One Igbo Woman Trying To Save Her Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</guid><description>Oddly, its the feel-good stories which we think are the most important. This week we had a few stories come by which show much progress is being made in the popularity of regional languages.
Here at VideoTranslator we feel that most people are quite proud of where they come from - its totally natural.
Each one of us has a story of how we came to be, and the stories of those who came before are a vital part of any human identity.</description></item><item><title>How To Reach Gen Z Using AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we keep an eye on what everyone else is doing.
Well, we try to anyways. And one of the better resources out there is Social Media Today. This article, &amp;lsquo;What Gen Z is Watching Online - and What That Means for Marketers in 2020&amp;rsquo; is full of wonderful titbits about how to think about video.
How Gen Z Is Using YouTube The big takeaway from the article is that Vlogging and Informative Videos are the biggest draws.</description></item><item><title>AI &amp; Wildlife Preservation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-and-wildlife-preservation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-and-wildlife-preservation/</guid><description>If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing most of us can agree on, it&amp;rsquo;s that wildlife preservation is important. The animals on this planet have been suffering a lot since we humans came on the scene. Luckily, there are amazing people out there trying to right the wrongs. Using Artificial Intelligence, researchers are able to continue this quest all the more and we&amp;rsquo;re looking into just how that&amp;rsquo;s being done.
How Artificial Intelligence Is Changing Wildlife Research Giraffe populations are rapidly declining but AI is here to help Researcher Jenna Stacy-Dawes and her team at San Diego Zoo&amp;rsquo;s Institute for Conservation Research are being assisted in their work in giraffe conservation with the AI software program, Wildbook.</description></item><item><title>Clients: Why You Make Me Blush!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:02 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we get lots of feedback from clients. Most of it is good, some of it not so much. Recently, as we have started to build out our retail client base it has become interesting.
The product challenge with retail is quite different from an enterprise offering or a managed service. Because the user is not being paid to use the product (or being told to by their manager) expectations for the product are totally different.</description></item><item><title>Speaking In The Mother Tongue: AI Indian Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</guid><description>We recently came across an article with the exciting news that the Indian government is planning on making its Internet content available in regional languages &amp;ldquo;to remove the language barrier among Indians.&amp;quot;
Currently websites are available in English and Hindi but that leaves out the remaining 20 regional languages that are spoken across the country.
&amp;ldquo;We need a method through which any Indian using his or her language should be able to converse with any user in any other Indian language without the impediment of English as a link language.</description></item><item><title>Accessibility: Why It Matters And How To Avoid Being Sued</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work with clients who are part of the healthcare ecosystem.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, voice over artists, or in this case, nurses/doctors. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing - we are technologists who are trying to service our clients to the best of our ability.
Every now and then a story turns up which brings a lot of our work into sharp focus.</description></item><item><title>On The Brink Of Extinction: Nearly Dead Languages And The Dedicated Linguists Bringing Them Back To Life</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</guid><description>Thousands of kilometres apart, and in incredibly different cultures; three linguists are doing their part to save the culture of their people through language.
Masahiro Yamada and Natsuko Nakagawa in Japan and Kenny Pheasant in the United States are all passionate about ensuring almost lost languages are preserved and continue to be taught; and a lot of it comes down to teaching the languages to children.
Linguists Work To Preserve Ryukyu Dialects Now Dying Out Image courtesy of Nobuaki Tanaka Professors at the National Institute for Japanese Language and Linguistics made an alarming discovery when they found that many dialects in the Okinawa Prefecture are on the verge of dying out.</description></item><item><title>Sign Languages: Their past, present and future</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/sign-languages-their-past-present-and-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/sign-languages-their-past-present-and-future/</guid><description>For something that is used by an estimated 70 million people worldwide, there is still a lot we don&amp;rsquo;t know when it comes to the origin of sign language - luckily research is being done to change that. Going from the past to the future, Google Translate is developing a way to translate sign language into speech and we are excited about the possibilities that this brings for, well, everyone!</description></item><item><title>Quick Transcribe: For When You Need To Get Transcription Done Quickly</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator.Ai, we work closely with the Internationalization And Localization industry. This industry has many different participants, and they use our technology in different ways.
As a software firm, the hardest thing is to really understand what our clients do and why they do these things. Sounds funny, but it is true.
We had a strong response to our previous article, 3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency, and a number of questions and suggestions.</description></item><item><title>Mr Sh*thole: What To Do When Your AI Misbehaves</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</guid><description>Today we look at a humorous articles which look at what happens when AI goes wrong. Here at video translator we like to keep abreast of the latest news in the intersection of Artificial Intelligence, Natural Language Programming, Human Languages and Culture.
Read on to find out how Facebook&amp;rsquo;s AI got in trouble, and why Oracle thinks replacing your manager with a robot is likely, and a good thing to boot!</description></item><item><title>One place, many languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-place-many-languages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-place-many-languages/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re talking language today and how diverse it can be even in the same country, or city! Germany is still a country divided when it comes to what a pancake should be called - maybe they should be called egg-cakes? Also Mandarin is now Melbourne and Sydney&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;most widely spoken community language.&amp;rdquo;
Language matters, it&amp;rsquo;s important culturally and on a deeper level to help us identify with ourselves and others.</description></item><item><title>Where are we heading with AI computing in the 2020s? And how human can they really become?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/where-are-we-heading-with-ai-computing-in-the-2020s-and-how-human-can-they-really-become/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/where-are-we-heading-with-ai-computing-in-the-2020s-and-how-human-can-they-really-become/</guid><description>We now well and truly know that Artificial Intelligence is here to stay (and in fact has been for quite some time), but what will become of it, and us, in the future? One author has some very interesting thoughts on how AI computing will reach beyond just recognising how to act like a human but rather see the world the way we do and have a form of common sense.</description></item><item><title>Real life Dr Dolittle: We are on our way to talking to the animals and AI may make happen sooner than you think!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-jan-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-jan-2020/</guid><description>Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be fantastic if we could understand what our pets were trying to tell us? Having them be able to communicate if they like the food we give them, when they&amp;rsquo;re not feeling well and when they want to be pet, would take out so much of the guess work. (Although hearing dogs constantly asking to have a ball thrown might get a bit old after a while). Researchers are looking into decoding animal languages and we are here for it!</description></item><item><title>3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work in what is called the Internationalization And Localization industry.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
When do we do this work for our clients? Generally when a client needs a managed service. This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays from VideoTranslator!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-hoidays-from-videotranslator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-hoidays-from-videotranslator/</guid><description>What a year it&amp;rsquo;s been! From our launch in May we would not have believed we&amp;rsquo;d come so far in such a short amount of time.
Thank You Thank you everyone for all your support! We want to wish you and yours a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year. We hope you have a brilliant 2020!
Everyone who engaged with us, others that offered feedback, and folks who made a purchasing decision - thank you very much.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: For the Love of Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-17-dec-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-17-dec-2019/</guid><description>Language. It's something we're passionate about here at Video Translator, we can't get enough of it. And, judging by the news that&amp;rsquo;s come out in the past week, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of folks out there who share our passion. We&amp;rsquo;re delving into language from all across the globe this week; NLP research engineers working with pidgin English, YouTube India is branching out into local and regional Indian languages, Navajo is getting it&amp;rsquo;s own version of one of the most popular (read: annoying for adults) songs amongst toddlers and we see the effects on the brain from being bilingual from an early age.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Exciting developments for Epilepsy patients, Amazon has added 22 new languages to Amazon Translate and has Microsoft given children the ability to speak to reindeer?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-10-dec-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-10-dec-2019/</guid><description>It seems like every week there are exciting new developments with artificial intelligence being used in the health, medicine and science fields; and that&amp;rsquo;s because, well, there is. There is often quite a negative attitude amongst the public in relation to AI, &amp;ldquo;they&amp;rsquo;re going to take our jobs!&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s the end of the human race!&amp;rdquo; But it&amp;rsquo;s not all doom and gloom. Really good, positive, and not to mention lifesaving advances in medicine, are taking place all with AI and proving that our new robot overlords are not planning on taking over the world just quite yet&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Changes In The Internationalization And Localization Industry</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/changes-in-the-internationalization-and-localization-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/changes-in-the-internationalization-and-localization-industry/</guid><description>Rev.com, a online transcription platform, got in trouble last month. It picked up a negative profile last month by none other than the New York Times.
Even worse was that Rev managed to become the poster child of gig-economy companies who mistreat workers. This led to a lot of negative media coverage which is probably not what Rev is looking to do.
What Set Off Media Focus This article by the NYT set of this series of events.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Hello baby! Machine learning helping to understand placental health, did Shakespeare have help? And advances in health and medicine thanks to AI.</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-26-nov-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-26-nov-2019/</guid><description>Considering it is something that keeps the human race going, maternal and placental health is still not properly understood, which proves extremely detrimental to the health of mother and baby during pregnancy. Thanks to a new development in AI technology, that will begin to change. We&amp;rsquo;re also looking at how educators in the US are frantically searching for a better solution to interpretations services that help communicate with non-English speaking families and we look at the leaps and bounds being made in medicine thanks to machine learning.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: AI to the rescue! Using machine learning for the greater good; advances in medicine, agriculture and saving lives, is there anything we can't do with the help of artificial intelligence?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-12-nov-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-12-nov-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another AI focused week and with so much going on in the world of Artificial Intelligence, can you blame us? The field of medicine and science have long been advocates of using AI for the greater good and it appears there are some incredible trail blazers helping to make that happen.
1. A Star Professor—And Her Radical, AI-Powered Plan To Discover New Drugs Using AI to discover new medicine One woman is using her incredible skills and mind to advance the way in which drugs can be discovered and created with the help of artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Foreign signs installed to save lives, when seeing isn't believing; learning about deepfake videos, content creators coming together to save the planet and hilarious movie translations</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-05-nov-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-05-nov-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s the start of a new month and news from around the globe keeps on rolling in. This week we&amp;rsquo;ve learnt the power of YouTube, its content creators and their followers and how they&amp;rsquo;re working together for the greater good. We also focus on the Western Australian Government&amp;rsquo;s foreign language road signs initiative that aims to save lives and we delve into the world of deepfake videos. Are they as dangerous as they seem?</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Google's latest Pixel 4 app impresses, praise for Nobel Prize winner and a feel-good video to brighten your week</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-29-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-29-oct-2019/</guid><description>Exciting news for content creators this week at Instagram&amp;rsquo;s IGTV releases features that will allow videos to viewed as a series. Google is releasing an on-device transcribing app that may be a game-changer, plus just because we loved it so; a video showing a deaf father signing to his newborn daughter, that has really hit us with all the feels.
1. Pixel 4’s live transcription goes up against “real-life” challenges Image courtesy of The Wall Street Journal Google is a releasing a new built in app in their Pixel 4 and honestly, it&amp;rsquo;s very impressive.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Travelling back in time with AI, learning the love of translation and why it is imperative to get more interpreters in courthouses to aid domestic violence cases</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-22-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-22-oct-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another big week in AI news, from assisting in search and rescue methods to aiding doctors in detecting brain bleeds, it&amp;rsquo;s being proven time and time again how Artificial Intelligence can help humanity in meaningful ways. We also see that AI is helping historians create a portal into the past of Europe and creating virtual worlds that we can experience. In other news, one woman is advocating for more support and resources for translators in domestic violence cases and one author and translator explains her love for language and translation.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Babies teaching us how best to teach AI, glasses made for translation and keeping an eye on our giant fishy friends with the help of Artificial Intelligence</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-15-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-15-oct-2019/</guid><description>More than just cute little stinkers, babies are exceptional learners, so good in fact that we&amp;rsquo;re trying to simulate their learning process to assist AI in becoming evermore smarter. Our first article details just how babies learn and what they&amp;rsquo;re doing to make AI do the same. Plus, machine learning is helping us prepare and respond to natural disasters and an app is now available to help content creators reach their target market, with the click of a button.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Open Captions for Deaf and Hard of Hearing People</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/importance-of-open-captions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/importance-of-open-captions/</guid><description>It comes as no surprise that for hard of hearing and deaf people, closed captions are a necessity for being able to watch TV, films and online videos. We&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned before the need for more captions and subtitles to be present in cinemas and as highlighted in this Washington Post article, &amp;ldquo;accessing online material&amp;hellip;can be a challenge for differently abled people.&amp;rdquo;
This is one of the reasons we believe it is so important to include open captions in online videos.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Translation devices changing the business game, machine learning aiding scientific research and the world's first ever AI concert</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-oct-2019/</guid><description>The art of translation has been a skilled required by humans for over 2000 years, we&amp;rsquo;ve got a few interesting articles that highlight just how important it is and one translator shares with us what she&amp;rsquo;s learnt after being in the business for 20 years. We&amp;rsquo;re also looking at how machine learning is aiding scientists in researching plants, AI writers writing as well as humans can, and we celebrate as Armenia hosts the first ever AI concert.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: AI is here to help; translation at the tip of your ears; and Google's ALBERT is receiving top ranks</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-01-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-01-oct-2019/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s been a lot going on with AI in particular this week. Read on to get up to date on some of the most interesting things coming out of the world of Artificial Intelligence. There&amp;rsquo;s also top ranking machine learning systems and earbuds that can translate languages as you&amp;rsquo;re hearing them.
1. Yes Bank creates &amp;lsquo;Yes Robot&amp;rsquo; using Microsoft Cognitive Services Yes Robot A bank in India has created AI assistant, &amp;lsquo;Yes Robot&amp;rsquo; to provide 24 hour customer service to its patrons.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: AI tools are transforming Indian healthcare, growth in the Translations Market and more</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-24-sept-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-24-sept-2019/</guid><description>Welcome to the Weekly Roundup!
Each week we put together a list of articles featuring some of the most interesting ideas and news in the field. This week we take a look at how AI tools are helping to transform Indian healthcare, machine learning is being used to create new music, plus much more.
Read on to find out what&amp;rsquo;s been going on in the past week.
1. Why one media buyer is embracing programmatic linear TV Linear television can be a tough nut to crack when it comes to advertising and brand reach, but Global director of media strategy at PHD Media, Nick Vernola believes new technology can hold the solution.</description></item><item><title>9 of China's Best Short Video Apps</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/9-of-chinas-best-short-video-apps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/9-of-chinas-best-short-video-apps/</guid><description>Short video makers are an up and coming category of apps that are really hitting the ground running in China. Short video clips (even less than a second long) have been gaining in popularity along with social platforms like Instagram and Snapchat, and especially in China with Wechat and Weibo. The social component to online video broadcasting has changed how we consume short videos, and what we expect from them.</description></item><item><title>Subtitling For The Win</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/subtitling-for-the-win/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/subtitling-for-the-win/</guid><description>It started with a Tweet, which was then picked up by the Guardian, re-Tweeted and the rest is history. The post got re-tweeted 70K+ times, and liked 74K+ times. That is clearly something which struck a cord. Why?
Who is using subtitles or captions, why are they using it, and how can you also use subtitles or captions. For a technical discussion on subtitles or captions, see this. This post is more about the value in subtitles or captions.</description></item><item><title>The Growing Pains Of Diversity And A Possible Solution</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-growing-pains-of-diversity-and-a-possible-solution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-growing-pains-of-diversity-and-a-possible-solution/</guid><description>This post is not really about diversity. It is about the granular challenges around governance in an increasingly complex world, and operational solutions which may work going forward.
We look at three events which took place in this week. What the problem is, and what a solution might be. These events are:
Trump Administration’s Deregulation Drive Begins to Impact Language Industry Sometimes Lost In Translation, With Dialects Context Is Key Translating verdicts will help all litigants Trump Administration’s Deregulation Drive Begins to Impact Language Industry US federal regulations have generally favored the language services industry.</description></item><item><title>How We Used SEO To Come Up With A New Name</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-we-used-seo-to-come-up-with-a-new-name/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-we-used-seo-to-come-up-with-a-new-name/</guid><description>Our original name was QBL Media, and our new name is videotranslator.ai. The original name did not really work, and was always a temporary name.
This post covers some of the context of where our platform came from, and what changes happened in the course of getting this app to market, including a pivot.
We used SEO to determine a new name. Read on to understand why this was done, how it was done, and what benefits we expect to get from the name change.</description></item><item><title>How To Use Auto Overlay To Simplify Transcription</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-auto-overlay-to-simplify-transcription/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-auto-overlay-to-simplify-transcription/</guid><description>We got this video from OSL Brokerage&amp;rsquo;s LinkedIn page. We are not suggesting that we have any relationship with OSL, and largely, we are using this content to demonstrate the process by which video content can be translated.
This specific video already has captions, so we don&amp;rsquo;t need these per se. However, we will be adding Chinese captions as an overlay, as opposed to captions.
The final output is shown below.</description></item><item><title>We Just Launched And We Need Luck</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-just-launched-and-we-need-luck/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-just-launched-and-we-need-luck/</guid><description>For the last 2 years or so, we have been working on a new platform which we think will be super useful for content creators. This includes marketers for exporters, tourism concerns, media shops and everyday folks looking to build brands and businesses using tools like YouTube and LinkedIn.
Just for some background, we are a tiny software company, and think of ourselves as basically an independent studio, trying to craft the best tools we can.</description></item><item><title>We Have An Explainer Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-have-an-explainer-video/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-have-an-explainer-video/</guid><description>We are a Sydney based, media focused technology platform provider, looking to make the world a more accessible place. Our primary value proposition is a transcription and translation platform, with a focus on audio and video content.
Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s translation platform (&amp;ldquo;the application&amp;rdquo;) is an Internet-enabled SaaS (Software as a Service) platform which assists content creators (&amp;ldquo;the client&amp;rdquo;) to engage with stakeholders (&amp;ldquo;the audience&amp;rdquo;) from different linguistic backgrounds. The application is used to convert hypermedia content from one language to another, using an Artificial Intelligence (AI) assisted process.</description></item><item><title>Multi-Lingual Forms... What Black Magic Is This???</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/multi-lingual-forms-what-black-magic-is-this/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/multi-lingual-forms-what-black-magic-is-this/</guid><description>We live in a modern world, which means working with colleagues, internal and external stakeholder, and clients from different backgrounds. For everyday interactions, this is fine, but every now and then, it can get messy.
Does this resonate with you? An important client in Asia needs something, and they are not happy. However, the operations person you are speaking to does not speak great English, and so an important deal has been bungled.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Manage Your Account</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-manage-your-account/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-manage-your-account/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s post we look at how to manage your account. This will cover Root and Management workspaces. The ordering reflects the navigation pane at the top right of the application. Please note, for more information covering how to add and remove languages specifically, please have a look at this post. Information about the Finance section will be covered in a later post.
This post is written to explain the use cases of account management, and why options are laid out as they are - if we have reached out to you for feedback, please feel free to come back with ideas on how you use/would like to use the interface.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year/</guid><description>We had a very good 2018 here at Video Translator. While a challenging year, the majority of the platform was built in 2018. Oddly, doing hard things well is enormously empowering, if a little scary. Important events in 2018 included:
Moved into Fishburners, our brilliant co-working space, in the new Sydney Start Up Hub. Brought on two fantastic developers, Vivek Kumar and Pranay Shah. Both these guys have been absolutely critical in getting our platform over the line.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Sign-Up</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-sign-up/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:05 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-sign-up/</guid><description>The below describes how to sign-up to the Video Translator application. Following sign-up, how to login to the platform is also covered.
Steps To sign-up for the application, please follow the below steps:
Please direct your browser to videotranslator.ai, and then click on the Sign Up button.
Please input your email address, and select languages. Your primary language is assumed to be English, and you will be able to select an additional 2 languages (additional languages are available within the application).</description></item></channel></rss>