<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Translation Services on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/translation-services/</link><description>Recent content in Translation Services on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:01 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/translation-services/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Implications Of AI Adoption In Our Tools</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-implications-of-ai-adoption-in-our-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-implications-of-ai-adoption-in-our-tools/</guid><description>AI is everywhere in the news these days. But something critical has changed recently.
In the near past, AI has gone from being super fancy to being, well... pedestrian.
Say what now?
Well - AI is becoming ordinary. And turning up in our office/productivity toolkits.
In recent days, Google has expanded its offering using AI, as has Microsoft, and so has Amazon.
What does this mean for how we work, and how can you use this trend to advantage your business?</description></item><item><title>How NSW Health Is Using Video Translation To Empower Occupational Therapists</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</guid><description>One major challenge in diverse societies is the provision of healthcare services.
In western Sydney, this problem is directly tackled by the South-West Sydney Local Health District, which sits under New South Wales Health.
Ok - so obviously this is complicated stuff. But how does video translation help?
If you don't speak good English, specifically business English, finding information is very hard. The doctor is the only resource who can help, but what happens when they don't speak your language?</description></item><item><title>Why YouTube Stopped Community Caption Contributions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</guid><description>Community captions are a function in YouTube. This function allows a YouTube content creator to crowd source captions for their video content.
YouTube is shutting this down. Here is how it will affect you!
Change To Community Contributions On YouTube Notice about an upcoming change to community contributions on YouTube Both creators and viewers have reported problems with the community contributions feature, including spam, abuse, and low quality submissions.</description></item><item><title>How Vyasa University Is Fighting Covid With Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</guid><description>Vivekananda Yoga Anusandhana Samsthana or VYASA is a registered charitable institution (1986) working to make Yoga a socially relevant field of study.
Based on the teachings of Swami Vivekananda, Vyasa University combines the four streams of Yoga with unity in their diversity, the key essence of Indian culture, applications of Yoga to bring health, harmony, peace the world over are now spread across the globe in nearly 30 countries.
Vyasa University: Using scientific research to bring Yoga into the modern world!</description></item><item><title>How QAChef Is Reaching Clients In A Tough Market</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</guid><description>The hospitality business is in a hard place right now because of Covid 19.
QAChef is a technology company which digitizes food safety compliance processes through a single handheld device, thus enabling unprecedented ingredient-to-customer food traceability and greater efficiency and productivity.
QAChef&amp;#39;s handheld device being used to measure temperature during cooking So QAChef is in a fantastic position, a ready for market product which enhances traceability across large scale food production - perfect given the focus on food safety and associated health implications in the wake of the Covid-19 pandemic.</description></item><item><title>How AI Dubbing Will Change Everything: Building A Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</guid><description>There is a very interesting piece of content we are looking at today. A team from IIIT-H (Indian Institute of Information Technology - Hyderabad) has build an AI which translates and lip-syncs a video from one language to another.
This originally came to our attention in this article from the folks at TNW. The paper this article is based on is here, and if you are interested in AI/Language you should absolutely have a look.</description></item><item><title>How AI Transcription Fails And What To Do About It</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</guid><description>AI Transcription has been all the rage recently. Several companies have been coming out with new products to meet this requirement.
What does it mean? Does it work? How to evaluate these products? We take a look and try to think behind the hype.
First we look at some of the incoming offerings. Then some issues with AI Transcription and Translation.
Incoming Offerings There is a very large number of AI products hitting the market place.</description></item><item><title>One Igbo Woman Trying To Save Her Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</guid><description>Oddly, its the feel-good stories which we think are the most important. This week we had a few stories come by which show much progress is being made in the popularity of regional languages.
Here at VideoTranslator we feel that most people are quite proud of where they come from - its totally natural.
Each one of us has a story of how we came to be, and the stories of those who came before are a vital part of any human identity.</description></item><item><title>How To Reach Gen Z Using AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we keep an eye on what everyone else is doing.
Well, we try to anyways. And one of the better resources out there is Social Media Today. This article, &amp;lsquo;What Gen Z is Watching Online - and What That Means for Marketers in 2020&amp;rsquo; is full of wonderful titbits about how to think about video.
How Gen Z Is Using YouTube The big takeaway from the article is that Vlogging and Informative Videos are the biggest draws.</description></item><item><title>Clients: Why You Make Me Blush!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:02 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we get lots of feedback from clients. Most of it is good, some of it not so much. Recently, as we have started to build out our retail client base it has become interesting.
The product challenge with retail is quite different from an enterprise offering or a managed service. Because the user is not being paid to use the product (or being told to by their manager) expectations for the product are totally different.</description></item><item><title>Speaking In The Mother Tongue: AI Indian Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</guid><description>We recently came across an article with the exciting news that the Indian government is planning on making its Internet content available in regional languages &amp;ldquo;to remove the language barrier among Indians.&amp;quot;
Currently websites are available in English and Hindi but that leaves out the remaining 20 regional languages that are spoken across the country.
&amp;ldquo;We need a method through which any Indian using his or her language should be able to converse with any user in any other Indian language without the impediment of English as a link language.</description></item><item><title>Accessibility: Why It Matters And How To Avoid Being Sued</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work with clients who are part of the healthcare ecosystem.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, voice over artists, or in this case, nurses/doctors. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing - we are technologists who are trying to service our clients to the best of our ability.
Every now and then a story turns up which brings a lot of our work into sharp focus.</description></item><item><title>On The Brink Of Extinction: Nearly Dead Languages And The Dedicated Linguists Bringing Them Back To Life</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</guid><description>Thousands of kilometres apart, and in incredibly different cultures; three linguists are doing their part to save the culture of their people through language.
Masahiro Yamada and Natsuko Nakagawa in Japan and Kenny Pheasant in the United States are all passionate about ensuring almost lost languages are preserved and continue to be taught; and a lot of it comes down to teaching the languages to children.
Linguists Work To Preserve Ryukyu Dialects Now Dying Out Image courtesy of Nobuaki Tanaka Professors at the National Institute for Japanese Language and Linguistics made an alarming discovery when they found that many dialects in the Okinawa Prefecture are on the verge of dying out.</description></item><item><title>Sign Languages: Their past, present and future</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/sign-languages-their-past-present-and-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/sign-languages-their-past-present-and-future/</guid><description>For something that is used by an estimated 70 million people worldwide, there is still a lot we don&amp;rsquo;t know when it comes to the origin of sign language - luckily research is being done to change that. Going from the past to the future, Google Translate is developing a way to translate sign language into speech and we are excited about the possibilities that this brings for, well, everyone!</description></item><item><title>Quick Transcribe: For When You Need To Get Transcription Done Quickly</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator.Ai, we work closely with the Internationalization And Localization industry. This industry has many different participants, and they use our technology in different ways.
As a software firm, the hardest thing is to really understand what our clients do and why they do these things. Sounds funny, but it is true.
We had a strong response to our previous article, 3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency, and a number of questions and suggestions.</description></item><item><title>Mr Sh*thole: What To Do When Your AI Misbehaves</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</guid><description>Today we look at a humorous articles which look at what happens when AI goes wrong. Here at video translator we like to keep abreast of the latest news in the intersection of Artificial Intelligence, Natural Language Programming, Human Languages and Culture.
Read on to find out how Facebook&amp;rsquo;s AI got in trouble, and why Oracle thinks replacing your manager with a robot is likely, and a good thing to boot!</description></item><item><title>What Arabic Voices are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</guid><description>Previously we&amp;rsquo;ve gone through the list of our English speaking AI and the different dialects they speak. You can see them all here.
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re looking at our Arabic speaking AI and the different dialects and voices available.
If you need a reminder as to how to select the appropriate AI language and dialect, check out our article here.
Now, on to the voices! We&amp;rsquo;ve used the phrase birds of a feather, flock together or الطيور على أشكالها تقع for our AI to say each time for the examples.</description></item><item><title>3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work in what is called the Internationalization And Localization industry.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
When do we do this work for our clients? Generally when a client needs a managed service. This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year 2020!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year-2020/</guid><description>Its the start of a new decade! This is a big deal, the only question is will this be the roaring 20&amp;rsquo;s all over again. Here at VideoTranslator we think it is going to be an exciting year.
Several amazing things happened last year, and this was mostly due to the kindness of strangers. Thank you very much to all the folks who took an interest in our work.
We started to get some traction, we found a niche where our tech was useful, and slowly slowly things started to come together.</description></item><item><title>An Old Language Is Young Again...</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/an-old-language-feels-young-again/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/an-old-language-feels-young-again/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we are big fans of the work of Tim Brookes. Recently, his work has included a kickstarter to create art work in traditional Nepalese script known as Ranjana.
We look at a language he shone some light on today. We also look at work Comcast is doing to support hearing impaired clients. This is quite exciting from an operational perspective.
Lastly we look at a recent write up from the Latin Post which looks at how to interface with commercial translation firms for your localisation and internationalization requirements.</description></item><item><title>60% Of The Content Produced By US YouTubers Is Watched In Other Countries</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/60-of-the-content-produced-by-us-youtubers-is-watched-in-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/60-of-the-content-produced-by-us-youtubers-is-watched-in-other-countries/</guid><description>Google produces all sorts of very interesting research. I mean, all kinds! One of the specific bits of intel which is well worth tracking is Think With Google.
Today we are going to look at a set of remarkable trend lines which point the way in which the world is heading.
We look at a 3 behavior and cultural shifts inside YouTube.
2 Behavioural And Cultural Shifts You should really read the article yourself, but the below was what we found super useful.</description></item><item><title>Changes In The Internationalization And Localization Industry</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/changes-in-the-internationalization-and-localization-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/changes-in-the-internationalization-and-localization-industry/</guid><description>Rev.com, a online transcription platform, got in trouble last month. It picked up a negative profile last month by none other than the New York Times.
Even worse was that Rev managed to become the poster child of gig-economy companies who mistreat workers. This led to a lot of negative media coverage which is probably not what Rev is looking to do.
What Set Off Media Focus This article by the NYT set of this series of events.</description></item><item><title>We Just Launched And We Need Luck</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-just-launched-and-we-need-luck/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-just-launched-and-we-need-luck/</guid><description>For the last 2 years or so, we have been working on a new platform which we think will be super useful for content creators. This includes marketers for exporters, tourism concerns, media shops and everyday folks looking to build brands and businesses using tools like YouTube and LinkedIn.
Just for some background, we are a tiny software company, and think of ourselves as basically an independent studio, trying to craft the best tools we can.</description></item></channel></rss>