<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Users on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/users/</link><description>Recent content in Users on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/users/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Latest News In The Translation Technology Industry</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/latest-news-in-the-translation-technology-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/latest-news-in-the-translation-technology-industry/</guid><description>The world has more than 7,000 languages. Although it may sound like a lot, the reality is that many of these languages are dying. To preserve a dying language and to combat the language barrier, many companies have made the best use out of the current technological advancements.
We have summed up 4 of the latest news in the translation technology industry in this blog post.
Latest News In The Translation Technology Industry Collage</description></item><item><title>8 Editor Video Singkat Terbaik Untuk Android Tahun 2021</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/8-editor-video-singkat-terbaik-android-2021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/8-editor-video-singkat-terbaik-android-2021/</guid><description>Hi, semuanya!
Kalian pernah nggak lagi scroll Instagram atau TikTok, eh, tiba-tiba udah lewat dua ajam aja! Kalau kalian pernah, kalian nggak sendirian, kok!
Akhir-akhir ini, video yang durasinya singkat itu emang lagi nge-trend banget. Kalian kedip dan tiba-tiba udah dua jam aja.
Nah, karena kalian udah lihat berbagaimacam video di media sosial, sekarang kalian juga pengen jadi content creator.
Tapi… mulai dari mana ya? Aplikasi apa yang bisa membantu kalian supaya bisa buat video-video nge-trend kayak influencer-influencer diluar sana?</description></item><item><title>The 8 Best Short Video Apps for Android 2021</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-8-best-short-video-apps-android-2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-8-best-short-video-apps-android-2021/</guid><description>If you have been guilty of spending 2 hours straight scrolling through Instagram or TikTok, well, you are not the only one!
These days, short videos are so addicting! You blinked and hours passed by. So, now you know that you’ve seen all these amazing videos, you also want to be a content creator.
But… where do you start? What apps should you use to create trending videos like those influencers?</description></item><item><title>9 of IOS Top Video Editing Apps 2021</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/top-performing-ios-video-editor-2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/top-performing-ios-video-editor-2021/</guid><description>Short videos are the hot trends these days. Everywhere you scroll on your social media, you will always be able to find these short videos.
So, what are the top video editor apps iOS have to offer for you in 2021 to make the next viral video?
Instagram
Video editing app number 1: Instagram
Instagram has 4.7 stars from its 1.3 million reviewers. This app remains number one on Apple&amp;rsquo;s photo and video chart.</description></item><item><title>The Importance Of Learning A Foreign Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-importance-of-learning-a-foreign-language/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-importance-of-learning-a-foreign-language/</guid><description>I was born in Indonesia, a country with over 250 million population scattered across its 17,000 islands. When I came to Australia four years ago, I noticed that most Australians with Indonesian background or mixed raced Indonesians do not know how to speak Indonesian.
Indonesia, the land with 17,000 islands
So, I began to question myself: how important it is to learn a foreign language? I came up with few answers…</description></item><item><title>One Igbo Woman Trying To Save Her Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-igbo-woman-trying-to-save-her-language/</guid><description>Oddly, its the feel-good stories which we think are the most important. This week we had a few stories come by which show much progress is being made in the popularity of regional languages.
Here at VideoTranslator we feel that most people are quite proud of where they come from - its totally natural.
Each one of us has a story of how we came to be, and the stories of those who came before are a vital part of any human identity.</description></item><item><title>How To Reach Gen Z Using AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-reach-gen-z-using-ai/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we keep an eye on what everyone else is doing.
Well, we try to anyways. And one of the better resources out there is Social Media Today. This article, &amp;lsquo;What Gen Z is Watching Online - and What That Means for Marketers in 2020&amp;rsquo; is full of wonderful titbits about how to think about video.
How Gen Z Is Using YouTube The big takeaway from the article is that Vlogging and Informative Videos are the biggest draws.</description></item><item><title>Clients: Why You Make Me Blush!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:02 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we get lots of feedback from clients. Most of it is good, some of it not so much. Recently, as we have started to build out our retail client base it has become interesting.
The product challenge with retail is quite different from an enterprise offering or a managed service. Because the user is not being paid to use the product (or being told to by their manager) expectations for the product are totally different.</description></item><item><title>Accessibility: Why It Matters And How To Avoid Being Sued</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work with clients who are part of the healthcare ecosystem.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, voice over artists, or in this case, nurses/doctors. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing - we are technologists who are trying to service our clients to the best of our ability.
Every now and then a story turns up which brings a lot of our work into sharp focus.</description></item><item><title>Quick Transcribe: For When You Need To Get Transcription Done Quickly</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/quick-transcribe-for-when-you-need-to-get-transcription-done-quickly/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator.Ai, we work closely with the Internationalization And Localization industry. This industry has many different participants, and they use our technology in different ways.
As a software firm, the hardest thing is to really understand what our clients do and why they do these things. Sounds funny, but it is true.
We had a strong response to our previous article, 3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency, and a number of questions and suggestions.</description></item><item><title>Mr Sh*thole: What To Do When Your AI Misbehaves</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</guid><description>Today we look at a humorous articles which look at what happens when AI goes wrong. Here at video translator we like to keep abreast of the latest news in the intersection of Artificial Intelligence, Natural Language Programming, Human Languages and Culture.
Read on to find out how Facebook&amp;rsquo;s AI got in trouble, and why Oracle thinks replacing your manager with a robot is likely, and a good thing to boot!</description></item><item><title>What Arabic Voices are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</guid><description>Previously we&amp;rsquo;ve gone through the list of our English speaking AI and the different dialects they speak. You can see them all here.
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re looking at our Arabic speaking AI and the different dialects and voices available.
If you need a reminder as to how to select the appropriate AI language and dialect, check out our article here.
Now, on to the voices! We&amp;rsquo;ve used the phrase birds of a feather, flock together or الطيور على أشكالها تقع for our AI to say each time for the examples.</description></item><item><title>3x Increase In Transcription Efficiency</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3x-increase-in-transcription-efficiency/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work in what is called the Internationalization And Localization industry.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
When do we do this work for our clients? Generally when a client needs a managed service. This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.</description></item><item><title>An Old Language Is Young Again...</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/an-old-language-feels-young-again/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/an-old-language-feels-young-again/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we are big fans of the work of Tim Brookes. Recently, his work has included a kickstarter to create art work in traditional Nepalese script known as Ranjana.
We look at a language he shone some light on today. We also look at work Comcast is doing to support hearing impaired clients. This is quite exciting from an operational perspective.
Lastly we look at a recent write up from the Latin Post which looks at how to interface with commercial translation firms for your localisation and internationalization requirements.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Manage Your Account</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-manage-your-account/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-manage-your-account/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s post we look at how to manage your account. This will cover Root and Management workspaces. The ordering reflects the navigation pane at the top right of the application. Please note, for more information covering how to add and remove languages specifically, please have a look at this post. Information about the Finance section will be covered in a later post.
This post is written to explain the use cases of account management, and why options are laid out as they are - if we have reached out to you for feedback, please feel free to come back with ideas on how you use/would like to use the interface.</description></item></channel></rss>