<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Happy New Year on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/happy-new-year/</link><description>Recent content in Happy New Year on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/happy-new-year/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What Team VideoTranslator Did In 2021</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-team-videotranslator-did-in-2021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-team-videotranslator-did-in-2021/</guid><description>The plan was to get this news item out prior to the end of the 2021. Unfortunately that did not work out.
So&amp;hellip; Happy New Year. Ok - we will do another post saying Happy New Year and listing out what we are looking forward to in 2022. But for the moment, we want to talk about 2021.
Thankfully, that&amp;rsquo;s a wrap on 2021! 2021 was a bit of a hard year for Team VideoTranslator.</description></item><item><title>Year In Review 2020</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/year-in-review-2020-may-you-live-in-interesting-times/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/year-in-review-2020-may-you-live-in-interesting-times/</guid><description>Happy New Year 2020 is over. Thankfully.
This might be tempting the fates just a bit, but really, 2021 has got to be better right!
Team VideoTranslator: Happy New Year
Jokes aside, the big learning from 2020 was to be more grateful. The strength shown by people worldwide was extraordinary, and we could not be more grateful for the kindness of strangers, friends, and family in what was a difficult time.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year 2020!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year-2020/</guid><description>Its the start of a new decade! This is a big deal, the only question is will this be the roaring 20&amp;rsquo;s all over again. Here at VideoTranslator we think it is going to be an exciting year.
Several amazing things happened last year, and this was mostly due to the kindness of strangers. Thank you very much to all the folks who took an interest in our work.
We started to get some traction, we found a niche where our tech was useful, and slowly slowly things started to come together.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays from VideoTranslator!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-hoidays-from-videotranslator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-hoidays-from-videotranslator/</guid><description>What a year it&amp;rsquo;s been! From our launch in May we would not have believed we&amp;rsquo;d come so far in such a short amount of time.
Thank You Thank you everyone for all your support! We want to wish you and yours a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year. We hope you have a brilliant 2020!
Everyone who engaged with us, others that offered feedback, and folks who made a purchasing decision - thank you very much.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year/</guid><description>We had a very good 2018 here at Video Translator. While a challenging year, the majority of the platform was built in 2018. Oddly, doing hard things well is enormously empowering, if a little scary. Important events in 2018 included:
Moved into Fishburners, our brilliant co-working space, in the new Sydney Start Up Hub. Brought on two fantastic developers, Vivek Kumar and Pranay Shah. Both these guys have been absolutely critical in getting our platform over the line.</description></item></channel></rss>