<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Artificial Intelligence on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/artificial-intelligence/</link><description>Recent content in Artificial Intelligence on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/artificial-intelligence/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Your AI Talking Back?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/is-your-ai-talking-back-the-cio-show/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/is-your-ai-talking-back-the-cio-show/</guid><description>In a very exciting turn of events, a Google engineer, Blake Lemoine, claimed that an AI he was working on had achieved sentience.
&amp;ldquo;If I didn’t know exactly what it was, which is this computer program we built recently, I’d think it was a 7-year-old, 8-year-old kid that happens to know physics,&amp;rdquo; the 41-year-old Lemoine told The Washington Post.
This was obviously quite a provocative claim, as ZeroHedge reported.
Google Engineer Placed On Leave After Insisting Company&amp;#39;s AI Is Sentient</description></item><item><title>How To Get To Pre-Product Market Fit For Startups</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-find-pre-product-market-fit-for-startups/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-find-pre-product-market-fit-for-startups/</guid><description>Getting to product-market fit is hard. Like, really really hard. In many ways, the journey of VideoTranslator has been around how to find product-market fit.
So why listen to us about product-market fit? Frankly, after working on it ourselves for several years, and helping many of our clients get to the same place, we know a few things about it.
Why Are We Talking About Pre-Product Marketing? This started over beers with one of our clients.</description></item><item><title>How To Use An AI Assurance Framework</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-an-ai-assurance-framework/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-an-ai-assurance-framework/</guid><description>Today we are going to be looking at AI Assurance Frameworks! Clearly, this is a fantastic topic that we are all super interested in :)
Ok - it&amp;rsquo;s not exactly riveting stuff, but it is important stuff!
What Is An AI Assurance Framework? The good folks over at the Department Of Customer Service have done really good work on this front. From their documentation:
&amp;ldquo;The AI Assurance Framework will help you design, build and use AI technology appropriately.</description></item><item><title>10 Tips Jitu Untuk Belajar Bahasa Baru</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/10-tips-jitu-untuk-belajar-bahasa-baru/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/10-tips-jitu-untuk-belajar-bahasa-baru/</guid><description>Belajar bahasa baru itu emang nggak mudah, tetapi nggak berarti harus sulit, kan?
Kalau kalian udah menyerah untuk belajar bahasa bari, kalian harus banget baca artikel ini!
Mari kita mulai!
Berikut adalah 10 tip untuk kalian yang mau belajar bahasa baru:
1. Cari Motivasi Cari motivasi untuk belajar bahasa baru
Menemukan motivasi adalah tip yang paling penting buat kalian yang mau belajar bahasa baru. Yang pastinya, kalian pasti pengen pengalaman belajar kalian itu menyenangkan dan mengasyikkan, bukannya malah membosankan dan melelahkan.</description></item><item><title>Berita Terbaru Di Industri Teknologi Terjemahan</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/berita-terbaru-di-industri-teknologi-terjemahan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/berita-terbaru-di-industri-teknologi-terjemahan/</guid><description>Saat ini, terdapat lebih dari 7,000 bahasa di dunia. Meskipun kedengarannya banyak, kenyataannya banyak dari bahasa-bahasa ini yang hampir punah. Oleh karena itu, saat ini banyak sekali perusahaan yang memanfaatkan kemajuan teknologi untuk melestarikan bahasa yang hampir punah dan untuk mengatasi kendala bahasa.
Kami sudah merangkum 4 berita terbaru di industri teknologi terjemahan dalam artikel kali ini.
Berita Terbaru Di Industri Teknologi Terjemahan
Yuk, kita cari tau!
1. Google Untuk Melestarikan Bahasa yang Terancam Punah Dengan Kecerdasan Buatan Google Arts &amp;amp; Culture adalah platform online berisi gambar dan video resolusi tinggi karya seni dan artefak budaya dari organisasi budaya di seluruh dunia.</description></item><item><title>Latest News In The Translation Technology Industry</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/latest-news-in-the-translation-technology-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/latest-news-in-the-translation-technology-industry/</guid><description>The world has more than 7,000 languages. Although it may sound like a lot, the reality is that many of these languages are dying. To preserve a dying language and to combat the language barrier, many companies have made the best use out of the current technological advancements.
We have summed up 4 of the latest news in the translation technology industry in this blog post.
Latest News In The Translation Technology Industry Collage</description></item><item><title>10 Tips That Actually Work If You Want To Learn A New Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/10-tips-to-learn-a-new-language/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/10-tips-to-learn-a-new-language/</guid><description>Learning a new language is not easy, but it does not mean that it should be hard.
If you have given up the idea of being bilingual (or trilingual? Maybe multilingual?), you should definitely read this article!
Let&amp;rsquo;s begin!
Here are 10 tips for you if you want to learn a new language:
1. Find your motivation Find your motivation
Finding your motivation is the most fundamental tip to learn a new language.</description></item><item><title>The Importance Of Learning A Foreign Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-importance-of-learning-a-foreign-language/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-importance-of-learning-a-foreign-language/</guid><description>I was born in Indonesia, a country with over 250 million population scattered across its 17,000 islands. When I came to Australia four years ago, I noticed that most Australians with Indonesian background or mixed raced Indonesians do not know how to speak Indonesian.
Indonesia, the land with 17,000 islands
So, I began to question myself: how important it is to learn a foreign language? I came up with few answers…</description></item><item><title>3 Alasan Kenapa Kalian Harus Mencoba Penerjemah Bertenaga Kecerdasan Buatan (AI-Powered Translator)</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3-alasan-untuk-mencoba-penerjemah-bertenaga-kecerdasan-buatan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3-alasan-untuk-mencoba-penerjemah-bertenaga-kecerdasan-buatan/</guid><description>Pada kesempatan kali ini, kita bakalan ngebahas 3 alasan kenapa kalian harus mencoba penerjemah bertenaga kecerdasan buatan.
Buat kalian yang nggak tau apa itu kecerdasan buatan atau artificial intelligence, yuk kita cari tau!
Sejarah Kecerdasan Buatan Percaya atau nggak, kecerdasan buatan dipopulerkan oleh cerita anak-anak yang berjudul The Wizard of Oz. Ceritanya dimulai dengan manusia kaleng dari Wizard of Oz yang bercita-cita untuk memiliki hati. Kemudian dilanjutkan oleh robot manusia yang menyamar sebagai Maria di Metropolis.</description></item><item><title>Why You Should Use AI Powered Translator?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-use-ai-powered-translator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-use-ai-powered-translator/</guid><description>In this article, we are going to give you 3 reasons why you should use AI-Powered translators.
To begin with, let us jump into the history of AI.
History of Artificial Intelligence Believe it or not, artificial intelligence was familiarized by a children’s story called The Wizard of Oz. It began with the “heartless” Tin man from the Wizard of Oz and continued with the humanoid robot that impersonated Maria in Metropolis.</description></item><item><title>What Is The Best Subtitling Software Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-is-the-best-subtitling-software-available/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-is-the-best-subtitling-software-available/</guid><description>Are you a content creator? Or Are you a court reporter looking for an easy way to caption lots of content? This blog post might be for you.
Having captions is very useful these days. Its really good for engagement, and its also really good for accessibility - specifically hearing impaired folk.
However, and there is no getting around this, it is painful to do.
Manual audio or video transcription takes ages.</description></item><item><title>How Safe Is AI Transcription: What You Need To Know</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-safe-is-ai-transcription-what-you-need-to-know/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-safe-is-ai-transcription-what-you-need-to-know/</guid><description>You are a content creator who uses AI.
But how safe is the AI you use, whether for transcription, translation or dubbing. Also some tips on how to use AI better in your journey into expanding your market.
There was a great article on this recently at How-To-Geek.
Ok - so why do you use AI? As a content creator you care about engagement. AI Transcription combined with Open Captions is fantastic for engagement.</description></item><item><title>Translate Your English Video Into Filipino And Chinese</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</guid><description>Business today relies on content creation. How do you expand your market? We show you how to add open captions for accessibility wins, and translate your video content into Tagalog and Chinese to expand your target client base!
Matija Squire is a LinkedIn coach, all round nice person plus a good friend. And she is doing something really cool!
We all know Covid-19 has distrupted all our lives. Some of us are lucky enough to be able to earn an income by working from home online.</description></item><item><title>How To Translate YouTube Videos And Dominate SEO</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</guid><description>The basic steps to translate a YouTube video are:
Download the video to your computer. Upload the video into an AI transcription service. Get the transcript in an .srt file. Translate the transcript using an AI translation service. Embed the translation into your video. You should only translate videos that you expect a good Return On Investment from - so you have a good feeling this video will work in a different language.</description></item><item><title>Clipping Chinese App: How To Translate Video Into Mandarin Chinese With AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</guid><description>One very common use case of video translator is as a Chinese clipping app. What is a Chinese clipping app?
This term is used by content creators to mean how to translate a video from English to Chinese, and they generally mean a short video for various social media channels.
In this blog post we are going to look at how to translate a small video from English to Mandarin (Simplified Chinese).</description></item><item><title>Fighting the Coronavirus and E. Coli with Machine Learning</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/fighting-the-coronavirus-and-e-coli-with-machine-learning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/fighting-the-coronavirus-and-e-coli-with-machine-learning/</guid><description>When it comes to combating superbugs and viruses, the human raced needs all the help it can get. Artificial Intelligence is being implemented to find treatments to fight bacteria that was formally resistant to all forms of antibiotics. China is also using AI to quickly determine if a person is showing symptoms of the coronavirus, which could be a great win against getting a handle on the respiratory disease.
Fighting The Coronavirus And E-Coli With Machine Learning</description></item><item><title>AI &amp; Wildlife Preservation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-and-wildlife-preservation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-and-wildlife-preservation/</guid><description>If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing most of us can agree on, it&amp;rsquo;s that wildlife preservation is important. The animals on this planet have been suffering a lot since we humans came on the scene. Luckily, there are amazing people out there trying to right the wrongs. Using Artificial Intelligence, researchers are able to continue this quest all the more and we&amp;rsquo;re looking into just how that&amp;rsquo;s being done.
How Artificial Intelligence Is Changing Wildlife Research Giraffe populations are rapidly declining but AI is here to help Researcher Jenna Stacy-Dawes and her team at San Diego Zoo&amp;rsquo;s Institute for Conservation Research are being assisted in their work in giraffe conservation with the AI software program, Wildbook.</description></item><item><title>Bleeding Edge AI: How A DeepMind Just Beat Team Liquid At StarCraft II</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-deepmind-just-beat-team-liquid-at-starcraft-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-deepmind-just-beat-team-liquid-at-starcraft-ii/</guid><description>If you didn&amp;rsquo;t catch it, last Thursday January 24, 2019 DeepMind&amp;rsquo;s new AI, AlphaStar beat a Team Liquid player Grzegorz Komincz, also known as MaNa in a professional game of StarCraft II.
What are we talking about? StarCraft II is a real-time strategy game by Blizzard Entertainment, which has become a staple of the eSports community. Professional play has been ongoing since the game&amp;rsquo;s initial release in 2010, following on the success of StartCraft and StarCraft: Brood Wars, both of which had substantial eSports fan bases.</description></item></channel></rss>