<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Transliteration on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/transliteration/</link><description>Recent content in Transliteration on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/transliteration/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What Arabic Voices are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</guid><description>Previously we&amp;rsquo;ve gone through the list of our English speaking AI and the different dialects they speak. You can see them all here.
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re looking at our Arabic speaking AI and the different dialects and voices available.
If you need a reminder as to how to select the appropriate AI language and dialect, check out our article here.
Now, on to the voices! We&amp;rsquo;ve used the phrase birds of a feather, flock together or الطيور على أشكالها تقع for our AI to say each time for the examples.</description></item><item><title>Extra! Extra! Read all about it!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/extra-extra-read-all-about-it/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/extra-extra-read-all-about-it/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of exciting developments at VideoTranslator, which means exciting things for you! This means that you&amp;rsquo;ll be hearing more from us going forward in the form of a weekly email.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t subscribed to our mailing list or signed up for a free trial yet, please do so here.
The email will be featuring the latest articles we&amp;rsquo;ve posted which will be like the following:
What English Dialects are Available?</description></item><item><title>What English Dialects are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-english-dialects-are-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-english-dialects-are-available/</guid><description>Did you know that our AI can speak in over 180 languages and more than 120 differing dialects and different genders? It&amp;rsquo;s true! That&amp;rsquo;s one smart robot ;)
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re focusing on English and the four different dialects that you can choose from when using our app.
For those that have you used the app before, you will notice that we have renamed the &amp;ldquo;voices&amp;rdquo;. Previously we had them named as EN-IN-P-M1, or UK-S4-M which didn&amp;rsquo;t make a lot of sense for those who were unfamiliar with the technology.</description></item><item><title>What Languages Are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-languages-are-available/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-languages-are-available/</guid><description>We look at the number of languages which you can use with your content. Remember, each languages is potentially a new market, and care needs to be taken to properly target your preferred leads.
There are two kinds of transcription, the first is Speech-To-Text Transcription, the second is a Text-To-Speech Transcription. In both cases, speech is involved, hence these are referred to as transcription AI&amp;rsquo;s. Similarly, with translation, what we are actually using is a Text-To-Text Translation AI.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/welcome-to-video-translator/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 11:16:52 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/welcome-to-video-translator/</guid><description>Welcome to the Video Translator. We are a Sydney based, media focused technology platform provider, looking to make the world a more accessible place. Our primary value proposition is a translation platform, with a focus on video translation.
Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s translation platform (&amp;ldquo;the application&amp;rdquo;) is an Internet-enabled SaaS (Software as a Service) platform which assists content creators (&amp;ldquo;the client&amp;rdquo;) to engage with stakeholders (&amp;ldquo;the audience&amp;rdquo;) from different linguistic backgrounds. The application is used to convert hypermedia content from one language to another, using an Artificial Intelligence (AI) assisted process.</description></item></channel></rss>