<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tamil on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/tags/tamil/</link><description>Recent content in Tamil on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/tags/tamil/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Vyasa University Is Fighting Covid With Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</guid><description>Vivekananda Yoga Anusandhana Samsthana or VYASA is a registered charitable institution (1986) working to make Yoga a socially relevant field of study.
Based on the teachings of Swami Vivekananda, Vyasa University combines the four streams of Yoga with unity in their diversity, the key essence of Indian culture, applications of Yoga to bring health, harmony, peace the world over are now spread across the globe in nearly 30 countries.
Vyasa University: Using scientific research to bring Yoga into the modern world!</description></item><item><title>Speaking In The Mother Tongue: AI Indian Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</guid><description>We recently came across an article with the exciting news that the Indian government is planning on making its Internet content available in regional languages &amp;ldquo;to remove the language barrier among Indians.&amp;quot;
Currently websites are available in English and Hindi but that leaves out the remaining 20 regional languages that are spoken across the country.
&amp;ldquo;We need a method through which any Indian using his or her language should be able to converse with any user in any other Indian language without the impediment of English as a link language.</description></item></channel></rss>