<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thai on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/tags/thai/</link><description>Recent content in Thai on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 23:00:00 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/tags/thai/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Step by Step Guide to Translating Your First Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-step-by-step-guide-to-translating-your-first-video/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-step-by-step-guide-to-translating-your-first-video/</guid><description>Having the ability to translate your video into a number of different languages and dialects puts your business a step ahead of the rest in means of reaching a larger audience and in turn, customers.
But getting your content translated and transcribed into another language seems expensive and time consuming, right?
Good news, friend. You&amp;rsquo;re wrong!
Dubbing and/or subtitling your video is a quick and easy process if you&amp;rsquo;re using our app and we hope that&amp;rsquo;s why you&amp;rsquo;re here&amp;hellip; to find out how to do it.</description></item><item><title>The Growing Pains Of Diversity And A Possible Solution</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-growing-pains-of-diversity-and-a-possible-solution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-growing-pains-of-diversity-and-a-possible-solution/</guid><description>This post is not really about diversity. It is about the granular challenges around governance in an increasingly complex world, and operational solutions which may work going forward.
We look at three events which took place in this week. What the problem is, and what a solution might be. These events are:
Trump Administration’s Deregulation Drive Begins to Impact Language Industry Sometimes Lost In Translation, With Dialects Context Is Key Translating verdicts will help all litigants Trump Administration’s Deregulation Drive Begins to Impact Language Industry US federal regulations have generally favored the language services industry.</description></item></channel></rss>