<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Management on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/management/</link><description>Recent content in Management on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/management/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Changes In The Internationalization And Localization Industry</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/changes-in-the-internationalization-and-localization-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/changes-in-the-internationalization-and-localization-industry/</guid><description>Rev.com, a online transcription platform, got in trouble last month. It picked up a negative profile last month by none other than the New York Times.
Even worse was that Rev managed to become the poster child of gig-economy companies who mistreat workers. This led to a lot of negative media coverage which is probably not what Rev is looking to do.
What Set Off Media Focus This article by the NYT set of this series of events.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Open Captions for Deaf and Hard of Hearing People</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/importance-of-open-captions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/importance-of-open-captions/</guid><description>It comes as no surprise that for hard of hearing and deaf people, closed captions are a necessity for being able to watch TV, films and online videos. We&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned before the need for more captions and subtitles to be present in cinemas and as highlighted in this Washington Post article, &amp;ldquo;accessing online material&amp;hellip;can be a challenge for differently abled people.&amp;rdquo;
This is one of the reasons we believe it is so important to include open captions in online videos.</description></item><item><title>We Just Launched And We Need Luck</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-just-launched-and-we-need-luck/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-just-launched-and-we-need-luck/</guid><description>For the last 2 years or so, we have been working on a new platform which we think will be super useful for content creators. This includes marketers for exporters, tourism concerns, media shops and everyday folks looking to build brands and businesses using tools like YouTube and LinkedIn.
Just for some background, we are a tiny software company, and think of ourselves as basically an independent studio, trying to craft the best tools we can.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Manage Your Account</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-manage-your-account/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-manage-your-account/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s post we look at how to manage your account. This will cover Root and Management workspaces. The ordering reflects the navigation pane at the top right of the application. Please note, for more information covering how to add and remove languages specifically, please have a look at this post. Information about the Finance section will be covered in a later post.
This post is written to explain the use cases of account management, and why options are laid out as they are - if we have reached out to you for feedback, please feel free to come back with ideas on how you use/would like to use the interface.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year/</guid><description>We had a very good 2018 here at Video Translator. While a challenging year, the majority of the platform was built in 2018. Oddly, doing hard things well is enormously empowering, if a little scary. Important events in 2018 included:
Moved into Fishburners, our brilliant co-working space, in the new Sydney Start Up Hub. Brought on two fantastic developers, Vivek Kumar and Pranay Shah. Both these guys have been absolutely critical in getting our platform over the line.</description></item></channel></rss>