<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Video translation on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/video-translation/</link><description>Recent content in Video translation on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/video-translation/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 TikTok Content Ideas</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/10-tiktok-content-ideas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/10-tiktok-content-ideas/</guid><description>We know that you&amp;rsquo;ve been guilty of spending hours and hours scrolling through your ForYou page on TikTok.
The microblogging app called Tik Tok is the trend these days. Most of the viral videos online come from this platform.
You know as well as we do that TikTok can bring you a lot of traction. So, you also want to make TikTok videos. However, you don’t know what contents you should post.</description></item><item><title>10 Tips That Actually Work If You Want To Learn A New Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/10-tips-to-learn-a-new-language/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/10-tips-to-learn-a-new-language/</guid><description>Learning a new language is not easy, but it does not mean that it should be hard.
If you have given up the idea of being bilingual (or trilingual? Maybe multilingual?), you should definitely read this article!
Let&amp;rsquo;s begin!
Here are 10 tips for you if you want to learn a new language:
1. Find your motivation Find your motivation
Finding your motivation is the most fundamental tip to learn a new language.</description></item><item><title>The Importance Of Learning A Foreign Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-importance-of-learning-a-foreign-language/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-importance-of-learning-a-foreign-language/</guid><description>I was born in Indonesia, a country with over 250 million population scattered across its 17,000 islands. When I came to Australia four years ago, I noticed that most Australians with Indonesian background or mixed raced Indonesians do not know how to speak Indonesian.
Indonesia, the land with 17,000 islands
So, I began to question myself: how important it is to learn a foreign language? I came up with few answers…</description></item><item><title>Leaving A Long-Lasting Legacy: Curating Your Family’s History</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/leaving-a-long-lasting-legacy-by-curating-your-familys-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/leaving-a-long-lasting-legacy-by-curating-your-familys-history/</guid><description>I believe everyone wants to leave a legacy.
Many people choose to pass on their homes, investments and possessions.
For Jeff Dormish, leaving a legacy means so much more than that. He does not just want to leave possessions; he wants to pass on his history.
For many Americans, most of their ancestors came from Europe in the great emigration wave before the First World War. Jeff Dormish’s ancestors also came from Europe, Slovenia, to be exact.</description></item><item><title>3 Alasan Kenapa Kalian Harus Mencoba Penerjemah Bertenaga Kecerdasan Buatan (AI-Powered Translator)</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3-alasan-untuk-mencoba-penerjemah-bertenaga-kecerdasan-buatan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/3-alasan-untuk-mencoba-penerjemah-bertenaga-kecerdasan-buatan/</guid><description>Pada kesempatan kali ini, kita bakalan ngebahas 3 alasan kenapa kalian harus mencoba penerjemah bertenaga kecerdasan buatan.
Buat kalian yang nggak tau apa itu kecerdasan buatan atau artificial intelligence, yuk kita cari tau!
Sejarah Kecerdasan Buatan Percaya atau nggak, kecerdasan buatan dipopulerkan oleh cerita anak-anak yang berjudul The Wizard of Oz. Ceritanya dimulai dengan manusia kaleng dari Wizard of Oz yang bercita-cita untuk memiliki hati. Kemudian dilanjutkan oleh robot manusia yang menyamar sebagai Maria di Metropolis.</description></item><item><title>How To Conveniently Translate Your Videos</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-conveniently-translate-your-videos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-conveniently-translate-your-videos/</guid><description>Many of you would have heard about translation. According to Kristen Malmkjær, translation is an activity that aims to convey meaning or meanings of a given linguistic discourse from one language to another.
What are the difficulties in translation? As a multilingual speaker, I have frequently asked to translate different languages. My family would ask me to translate files such as reports, articles and legal documents. However, translation also comes with its challenges.</description></item><item><title>Why Should You Translate Video Content: A Client Perspective</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-translate-video-content-a-client-perspective/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-translate-video-content-a-client-perspective/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we do a lot of work in the Internationalization And Localization industry.
But we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.
Sometimes however, the most useful thing we can do is just have a conversation.</description></item><item><title>The Implications Of AI Adoption In Our Tools</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-implications-of-ai-adoption-in-our-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-implications-of-ai-adoption-in-our-tools/</guid><description>AI is everywhere in the news these days. But something critical has changed recently.
In the near past, AI has gone from being super fancy to being, well... pedestrian.
Say what now?
Well - AI is becoming ordinary. And turning up in our office/productivity toolkits.
In recent days, Google has expanded its offering using AI, as has Microsoft, and so has Amazon.
What does this mean for how we work, and how can you use this trend to advantage your business?</description></item><item><title>How NSW Health Is Using Video Translation To Empower Occupational Therapists</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-nsw-heath-is-using-video-translation-to-empower-occupational-therapists/</guid><description>One major challenge in diverse societies is the provision of healthcare services.
In western Sydney, this problem is directly tackled by the South-West Sydney Local Health District, which sits under New South Wales Health.
Ok - so obviously this is complicated stuff. But how does video translation help?
If you don't speak good English, specifically business English, finding information is very hard. The doctor is the only resource who can help, but what happens when they don't speak your language?</description></item><item><title>Why YouTube Stopped Community Caption Contributions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</guid><description>Community captions are a function in YouTube. This function allows a YouTube content creator to crowd source captions for their video content.
YouTube is shutting this down. Here is how it will affect you!
Change To Community Contributions On YouTube Notice about an upcoming change to community contributions on YouTube Both creators and viewers have reported problems with the community contributions feature, including spam, abuse, and low quality submissions.</description></item><item><title>How Vyasa University Is Fighting Covid With Video Translation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-vyasa-university-is-fighting-covid-with-video-translation/</guid><description>Vivekananda Yoga Anusandhana Samsthana or VYASA is a registered charitable institution (1986) working to make Yoga a socially relevant field of study.
Based on the teachings of Swami Vivekananda, Vyasa University combines the four streams of Yoga with unity in their diversity, the key essence of Indian culture, applications of Yoga to bring health, harmony, peace the world over are now spread across the globe in nearly 30 countries.
Vyasa University: Using scientific research to bring Yoga into the modern world!</description></item><item><title>How QAChef Is Reaching Clients In A Tough Market</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</guid><description>The hospitality business is in a hard place right now because of Covid 19.
QAChef is a technology company which digitizes food safety compliance processes through a single handheld device, thus enabling unprecedented ingredient-to-customer food traceability and greater efficiency and productivity.
QAChef&amp;#39;s handheld device being used to measure temperature during cooking So QAChef is in a fantastic position, a ready for market product which enhances traceability across large scale food production - perfect given the focus on food safety and associated health implications in the wake of the Covid-19 pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Video Translation And Its Implications For FireTech</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</guid><description>A recent interview with FireTech Connect was really good fun, with Leigh Kelson hosting a free-wheeling discussion about crisis, technology and the future of AI in the internationalization and localization space.
FireTech Connect The FireTech 2020 program is an initiative of the Peregian Digital Hub, a leading technology incubator based in Noosa on Queensland&amp;rsquo;s Sunshine Coast.
FireTech Connect is funded by the Department of Industry, Science, Energy and Resources through the AusIndustry Entrepreneurs’ Programme; The Queensland State Government&amp;rsquo;s Advance Queensland Program; and Noosa Shire Council.</description></item><item><title>How Subtitling Can Boost ROI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</guid><description>Today we look at how to boost ROI or ROAS across your video production lifecycle, and how to make structural decisions which will pay off over a long time frame.
ROI or ROAS: Which One Should I Use? It&amp;rsquo;s actually a pretty messy question, but here are the basics.
ROI: Return on Investment Getting a definition is the starting point, and according to the smart folks at Investopia:
Return on Investment (ROI) is a performance measure used to evaluate the efficiency of an investment or compare the efficiency of a number of different investments.</description></item><item><title>A Little Positivity: To Brighten Your Day, Week And Month!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-little-positivity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/a-little-positivity/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m not going to sugarcoat it, this pandemic sucks big time and if you&amp;rsquo;re anything like me, you&amp;rsquo;re overwhelmed with the horrifying statistics and negative news that surrounds this whole thing.
So we&amp;rsquo;re focusing on the good news today. As Fred Rogers famously said, &amp;ldquo;When I was a boy and I would see scary things in the news, my mother would say to me, &amp;lsquo;Look for the helpers. You will always find people who are helping.</description></item><item><title>What Is The Best Subtitling Software Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-is-the-best-subtitling-software-available/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-is-the-best-subtitling-software-available/</guid><description>Are you a content creator? Or Are you a court reporter looking for an easy way to caption lots of content? This blog post might be for you.
Having captions is very useful these days. Its really good for engagement, and its also really good for accessibility - specifically hearing impaired folk.
However, and there is no getting around this, it is painful to do.
Manual audio or video transcription takes ages.</description></item><item><title>How Safe Is AI Transcription: What You Need To Know</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-safe-is-ai-transcription-what-you-need-to-know/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-safe-is-ai-transcription-what-you-need-to-know/</guid><description>You are a content creator who uses AI.
But how safe is the AI you use, whether for transcription, translation or dubbing. Also some tips on how to use AI better in your journey into expanding your market.
There was a great article on this recently at How-To-Geek.
Ok - so why do you use AI? As a content creator you care about engagement. AI Transcription combined with Open Captions is fantastic for engagement.</description></item><item><title>Translate Your English Video Into Filipino And Chinese</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</guid><description>Business today relies on content creation. How do you expand your market? We show you how to add open captions for accessibility wins, and translate your video content into Tagalog and Chinese to expand your target client base!
Matija Squire is a LinkedIn coach, all round nice person plus a good friend. And she is doing something really cool!
We all know Covid-19 has distrupted all our lives. Some of us are lucky enough to be able to earn an income by working from home online.</description></item><item><title>How To Translate YouTube Videos And Dominate SEO</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-translate-youtube-videos-and-dominate-seo/</guid><description>The basic steps to translate a YouTube video are:
Download the video to your computer. Upload the video into an AI transcription service. Get the transcript in an .srt file. Translate the transcript using an AI translation service. Embed the translation into your video. You should only translate videos that you expect a good Return On Investment from - so you have a good feeling this video will work in a different language.</description></item><item><title>Clipping Chinese App: How To Translate Video Into Mandarin Chinese With AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</guid><description>One very common use case of video translator is as a Chinese clipping app. What is a Chinese clipping app?
This term is used by content creators to mean how to translate a video from English to Chinese, and they generally mean a short video for various social media channels.
In this blog post we are going to look at how to translate a small video from English to Mandarin (Simplified Chinese).</description></item><item><title>Fighting the Coronavirus and E. Coli with Machine Learning</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/fighting-the-coronavirus-and-e-coli-with-machine-learning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/fighting-the-coronavirus-and-e-coli-with-machine-learning/</guid><description>When it comes to combating superbugs and viruses, the human raced needs all the help it can get. Artificial Intelligence is being implemented to find treatments to fight bacteria that was formally resistant to all forms of antibiotics. China is also using AI to quickly determine if a person is showing symptoms of the coronavirus, which could be a great win against getting a handle on the respiratory disease.
Fighting The Coronavirus And E-Coli With Machine Learning</description></item><item><title>How AI Dubbing Will Change Everything: Building A Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-dubbing-will-change-everything/</guid><description>There is a very interesting piece of content we are looking at today. A team from IIIT-H (Indian Institute of Information Technology - Hyderabad) has build an AI which translates and lip-syncs a video from one language to another.
This originally came to our attention in this article from the folks at TNW. The paper this article is based on is here, and if you are interested in AI/Language you should absolutely have a look.</description></item><item><title>How AI Transcription Fails And What To Do About It</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-ai-transcription-fails-and-what-to-do-about-it/</guid><description>AI Transcription has been all the rage recently. Several companies have been coming out with new products to meet this requirement.
What does it mean? Does it work? How to evaluate these products? We take a look and try to think behind the hype.
First we look at some of the incoming offerings. Then some issues with AI Transcription and Translation.
Incoming Offerings There is a very large number of AI products hitting the market place.</description></item><item><title>AI &amp; Wildlife Preservation</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-and-wildlife-preservation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-and-wildlife-preservation/</guid><description>If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing most of us can agree on, it&amp;rsquo;s that wildlife preservation is important. The animals on this planet have been suffering a lot since we humans came on the scene. Luckily, there are amazing people out there trying to right the wrongs. Using Artificial Intelligence, researchers are able to continue this quest all the more and we&amp;rsquo;re looking into just how that&amp;rsquo;s being done.
How Artificial Intelligence Is Changing Wildlife Research Giraffe populations are rapidly declining but AI is here to help Researcher Jenna Stacy-Dawes and her team at San Diego Zoo&amp;rsquo;s Institute for Conservation Research are being assisted in their work in giraffe conservation with the AI software program, Wildbook.</description></item><item><title>Speaking In The Mother Tongue: AI Indian Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/speaking-in-the-mother-tongue-ai-indian-languages/</guid><description>We recently came across an article with the exciting news that the Indian government is planning on making its Internet content available in regional languages &amp;ldquo;to remove the language barrier among Indians.&amp;quot;
Currently websites are available in English and Hindi but that leaves out the remaining 20 regional languages that are spoken across the country.
&amp;ldquo;We need a method through which any Indian using his or her language should be able to converse with any user in any other Indian language without the impediment of English as a link language.</description></item><item><title>On The Brink Of Extinction: Nearly Dead Languages And The Dedicated Linguists Bringing Them Back To Life</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</guid><description>Thousands of kilometres apart, and in incredibly different cultures; three linguists are doing their part to save the culture of their people through language.
Masahiro Yamada and Natsuko Nakagawa in Japan and Kenny Pheasant in the United States are all passionate about ensuring almost lost languages are preserved and continue to be taught; and a lot of it comes down to teaching the languages to children.
Linguists Work To Preserve Ryukyu Dialects Now Dying Out Image courtesy of Nobuaki Tanaka Professors at the National Institute for Japanese Language and Linguistics made an alarming discovery when they found that many dialects in the Okinawa Prefecture are on the verge of dying out.</description></item><item><title>One place, many languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-place-many-languages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-place-many-languages/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re talking language today and how diverse it can be even in the same country, or city! Germany is still a country divided when it comes to what a pancake should be called - maybe they should be called egg-cakes? Also Mandarin is now Melbourne and Sydney&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;most widely spoken community language.&amp;rdquo;
Language matters, it&amp;rsquo;s important culturally and on a deeper level to help us identify with ourselves and others.</description></item><item><title>Where are we heading with AI computing in the 2020s? And how human can they really become?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/where-are-we-heading-with-ai-computing-in-the-2020s-and-how-human-can-they-really-become/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/where-are-we-heading-with-ai-computing-in-the-2020s-and-how-human-can-they-really-become/</guid><description>We now well and truly know that Artificial Intelligence is here to stay (and in fact has been for quite some time), but what will become of it, and us, in the future? One author has some very interesting thoughts on how AI computing will reach beyond just recognising how to act like a human but rather see the world the way we do and have a form of common sense.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: January 2020</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-january-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-january-2020/</guid><description>There are a number of bug fixes and patches, which may affect your experience. In fact, we hope it will affect your experience for the better!
Images below are from our UAT environment. Please contact your relationship manager for more information or access.
Fixes include the below. If you have any questions please contact us at hello@videotranslator.ai.
Spaces In FileTemplate And FileItem Names Transcription Without Time-Coding Transcription Copy Function Edit/Exit Modals Removed/Modified Fixes To Locking Cosmetic Fixes To Billing January 2020: Spaces In FileTemplate And FileItem Names Previously, it was not possible to have spaces in fileTemplate and fileItem names.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year 2020!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year-2020/</guid><description>Its the start of a new decade! This is a big deal, the only question is will this be the roaring 20&amp;rsquo;s all over again. Here at VideoTranslator we think it is going to be an exciting year.
Several amazing things happened last year, and this was mostly due to the kindness of strangers. Thank you very much to all the folks who took an interest in our work.
We started to get some traction, we found a niche where our tech was useful, and slowly slowly things started to come together.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: September 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-september-2019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-september-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy month for us so far. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of new and exciting features we&amp;rsquo;re still developing so watch this space! In the meantime, there are a couple of updates and patches to tell you about.
Embedding Captions Previously, to embed captions onto your video it was possible to do so from the captions tab. This tab is now only used to make edits to the captions. To embed captions, it is now done by using the Audio Overlay tab.</description></item><item><title>What's Hot in Short Video Apps for iOS</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/whats-hot-in-short-video-apps-for-ios/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/whats-hot-in-short-video-apps-for-ios/</guid><description>With the ever increasing popularity of short video apps amongst iOS users, more and more developers are trying to get their apps to the top. This has resulted in a plethora of short video apps being created with different features based on the users needs and wants. We&amp;rsquo;ve taken a look at the top ranking short video apps in the Apple App Store (as of August 2019) to see what these apps for iPhone have to offer.</description></item><item><title>9 of China's Best Short Video Apps</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/9-of-chinas-best-short-video-apps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/9-of-chinas-best-short-video-apps/</guid><description>Short video makers are an up and coming category of apps that are really hitting the ground running in China. Short video clips (even less than a second long) have been gaining in popularity along with social platforms like Instagram and Snapchat, and especially in China with Wechat and Weibo. The social component to online video broadcasting has changed how we consume short videos, and what we expect from them.</description></item><item><title>How Video Transcription Works Explainer</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-video-transcription-works-explainer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-video-transcription-works-explainer/</guid><description>We have been working really hard making a number of changes to our underlying application. Specifically we have (i) added a new architecture to our video processing, (ii) added a few more languages, (iii) large number of changes to the look/feel of the product.
All in all, we felt it was time for a new explainer video which covered how to use the platform.
Here it is&amp;hellip; enjoy!
How To Transcribe A Video Using AI Explainer: How to Transcribe A Video Using AI</description></item><item><title>Subtitling For The Win</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/subtitling-for-the-win/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/subtitling-for-the-win/</guid><description>It started with a Tweet, which was then picked up by the Guardian, re-Tweeted and the rest is history. The post got re-tweeted 70K+ times, and liked 74K+ times. That is clearly something which struck a cord. Why?
Who is using subtitles or captions, why are they using it, and how can you also use subtitles or captions. For a technical discussion on subtitles or captions, see this. This post is more about the value in subtitles or captions.</description></item><item><title>Comparison Between Rev.com And VideoTranslator.ai</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/comparison-between-rev-dot-com-and-videotranslator-dot-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/comparison-between-rev-dot-com-and-videotranslator-dot-ai/</guid><description>These days, there are a large number of video editing tools available. The majority of these can add captions, or add subtitles, to your video. However, to do this we first need a transcript of the audio or video content.
Given the number of video transcription services out there, which one should you choose?
Before you take on the monotonous task of transcribing audio to text, read this blog post to see the major differences between two transcription platforms, rev.</description></item><item><title>Product Update: May 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/product-update-may-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/product-update-may-2019/</guid><description>We have been putting in for a number of grant applications in the innovation space. One of the applications needed a small video as part of the application process.
The video covers the basic use cases, and we added the captions to the asset.
May 2019: Product update Product Update: May 2019 (English)
Conclusion Please connect with us on LinkedIn, YouTube or Facebook for any comments, questions, or just to keep up to date with the work we do!</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: May 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-may-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-may-2019/</guid><description>There are a number of bug fixes and patches, which may affect your user experience. Fixes include (a) and upload bug, (b) a naming convention enhancement, (c) a UI timing bug, (d) UI help bug, and (e) UI folder bug.
May 2019: Upload Bug Previously, if you uploaded certain files, and exceeded certain file sizes, the application would error without notifying the user.
Specifically, on the operational side, we setup all client with file and size permissions at enrolment.</description></item><item><title>ऑस्ट्रेलियाई फैशन के माध्यम से एक यात्रा: अंग्रेजी से हिंदी में वीडियो प्रतिलेख और अनुवाद</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%91%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%88-%E0%A4%AB%E0%A5%88%E0%A4%B6%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A7%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A4%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/%E0%A4%91%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%9F%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%88-%E0%A4%AB%E0%A5%88%E0%A4%B6%E0%A4%A8-%E0%A4%95%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A7%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%AE-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%8F%E0%A4%95-%E0%A4%AF%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A4%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%BE-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%97%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%9C%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%87-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%B5%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%A1%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%AF%E0%A5%8B-%E0%A4%AA%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%B0%E0%A4%A4%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%B2%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%96-%E0%A4%94%E0%A4%B0-%E0%A4%85%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%81%E0%A4%B5%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%A6/</guid><description>ये वीडियो है म्यूजियम ऑफ एप्लाइड आर्ट्स एंड साइंसेज यूट्यूब चैनल। यह वीडियो म्यूजियम ऑफ एप्लाइड आर्ट्स एंड साइंसेज (मॉस) के परिधान और डिजाइन संग्रह के बारे में है।
परिधान संग्रह 18 वीं सदी से वर्तमान उदाहरण के टुकड़े को दर्शाता है। इन्हें मॉस के नए सेंटर फॉर फैशन में दिखाया गया है । कुल मिलाकर लगभग 30,000 अद्भुत टुकड़े हैं, जो मॉस, आशा करता हैं कि भविष्य की पीढ़ियों के फैशन डिजाइनरों को प्रभावित और प्रेरित करेंगे।</description></item><item><title>How To Use Auto Overlay To Simplify Transcription</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-auto-overlay-to-simplify-transcription/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-auto-overlay-to-simplify-transcription/</guid><description>We got this video from OSL Brokerage&amp;rsquo;s LinkedIn page. We are not suggesting that we have any relationship with OSL, and largely, we are using this content to demonstrate the process by which video content can be translated.
This specific video already has captions, so we don&amp;rsquo;t need these per se. However, we will be adding Chinese captions as an overlay, as opposed to captions.
The final output is shown below.</description></item><item><title>We Just Launched And We Need Luck</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-just-launched-and-we-need-luck/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-just-launched-and-we-need-luck/</guid><description>For the last 2 years or so, we have been working on a new platform which we think will be super useful for content creators. This includes marketers for exporters, tourism concerns, media shops and everyday folks looking to build brands and businesses using tools like YouTube and LinkedIn.
Just for some background, we are a tiny software company, and think of ourselves as basically an independent studio, trying to craft the best tools we can.</description></item><item><title>Bleeding Edge AI: How A DeepMind Just Beat Team Liquid At StarCraft II</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-deepmind-just-beat-team-liquid-at-starcraft-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-deepmind-just-beat-team-liquid-at-starcraft-ii/</guid><description>If you didn&amp;rsquo;t catch it, last Thursday January 24, 2019 DeepMind&amp;rsquo;s new AI, AlphaStar beat a Team Liquid player Grzegorz Komincz, also known as MaNa in a professional game of StarCraft II.
What are we talking about? StarCraft II is a real-time strategy game by Blizzard Entertainment, which has become a staple of the eSports community. Professional play has been ongoing since the game&amp;rsquo;s initial release in 2010, following on the success of StartCraft and StarCraft: Brood Wars, both of which had substantial eSports fan bases.</description></item></channel></rss>