<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Video Translation on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/video-translation/</link><description>Recent content in Video Translation on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/video-translation/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Video Translation And Its Implications For FireTech: A Conversation With Leigh Kelson</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</guid><description>A recent interview with FireTech Connect was really good fun, with Leigh Kelson hosting a free-wheeling discussion about crisis, technology and the future of AI in the internationalization and localization space.
FireTech Connect The FireTech 2020 program is an initiative of the Peregian Digital Hub, a leading technology incubator based in Noosa on Queensland&amp;rsquo;s Sunshine Coast.
FireTech Connect is funded by the Department of Industry, Science, Energy and Resources through the AusIndustry Entrepreneurs’ Programme; The Queensland State Government&amp;rsquo;s Advance Queensland Program; and Noosa Shire Council.</description></item><item><title>AI Internationalization: How Subtitling Can Boost ROI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</guid><description>Today we look at how to boost ROI or ROAS across your video production lifecycle, and how to make structural decisions which will pay off over a long time frame.
ROI or ROAS: Which One Should I Use? Its actually a pretty messy question, but here are the basics.
ROI: Return On Investment Getting a definition is the starting point, and according to the smart folks at Investopia:
Return on Investment (ROI) is a performance measure used to evaluate the efficiency of an investment or compare the efficiency of a number of different investments.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: January 2020</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-january-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-january-2020/</guid><description>There are a number of bug fixes and patches, which may affect your experience. In fact, we hope it will affect your experience for the better!
Images below are from our UAT environment. Please contact your relationship manager for more information or access.
Fixes include the below. If you have any questions please contact us at hello@videotranslator.ai.
Spaces In FileTemplate And FileItem Names Transcription Without Time-Coding Transcription Copy Function Edit/Exit Modals Removed/Modified Fixes To Locking Cosmetic Fixes To Billing January 2020: Spaces In FileTemplate And FileItem Names Previously, it was not possible to have spaces in fileTemplate and fileItem names.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: September 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-september-2019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-september-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy month for us so far. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of new and exciting features we&amp;rsquo;re still developing so watch this space! In the meantime, there are a couple of updates and patches to tell you about.
Embedding Captions Previously, to embed captions onto your video it was possible to do so from the captions tab. This tab is now only used to make edits to the captions. To embed captions, it is now done by using the Audio Overlay tab.</description></item><item><title>Product Update: May 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/product-update-may-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/product-update-may-2019/</guid><description>We have been putting in for a number of grant applications in the innovation space. One of the applications needed a small video as part of the application process.
The video covers the basic use cases, and we added the captions to the asset. Please note the Hindi version is a straight AI translation, and has not been optimised.
May 2019: Product update To view this video please enable JavaScript, and consider upgrading to a web browser that supports HTML5 video</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: May 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-may-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-may-2019/</guid><description>There are a number of bug fixes and patches, which may affect your user experience. Fixes include (a) and upload bug, (b) a naming convention enhancement, (c) a UI timing bug, (d) UI help bug, and (e) UI folder bug.
May 2019: Upload Bug Previously, if you uploaded certain files, and exceeded certain file sizes, the application would error without notifying the user.
Specifically, on the operational side, we setup all client with file and size permissions at enrolment.</description></item></channel></rss>