<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/video-translator/</link><description>Recent content on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/video-translator/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Merry Christmas 2020! Thank You From Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/merry-christmas-2020-thank-you-from-video-translator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/merry-christmas-2020-thank-you-from-video-translator/</guid><description>What a year it&amp;rsquo;s been! From getting locked down, to the great conjugation!
Obligatory Dancing Santa! 6e_nm65Qv9E
Merry Christmas 2020! Thank you for all the support!
Thank You Thank you everyone for all your support! We want to wish you and yours a `Merry Christmas`.
Everyone who engaged with us, others that offered feedback, and folks who made a purchasing decision - thank you very much.</description></item><item><title>The Girls and Women Revitalising Canada's Indigenous Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-girls-and-women-revitalising-canadas-indigenous-languages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-girls-and-women-revitalising-canadas-indigenous-languages/</guid><description>It was International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day this past Sunday 8 March and in honour of the day we&amp;rsquo;re looking at some incredible females who are doing all they can for their native languages.
The Girls and Women Revitalising Canada&amp;#39;s Indigenous Languages
Celebrating Indigenous Women Who Are Reclaiming and Revitalising Their Languages Image courtesy of Marion Konwanénhon Delaronde and Karihwiióstha Callie Montour In light of International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day which was this past Sunday, March 8, CBC News in Canada put together an article celebrating a number of Indigenous women and their plight to preserve and revitalise their traditional languages.</description></item><item><title>Sign Languages: Their past, present and future</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/sign-languages-their-past-present-and-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/sign-languages-their-past-present-and-future/</guid><description>For something that is used by an estimated 70 million people worldwide, there is still a lot we don&amp;rsquo;t know when it comes to the origin of sign language - luckily research is being done to change that. Going from the past to the future, Google Translate is developing a way to translate sign language into speech and we are excited about the possibilities that this brings for, well, everyone!</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: January 2020</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-january-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-january-2020/</guid><description>There are a number of bug fixes and patches, which may affect your experience. In fact, we hope it will affect your experience for the better!
Images below are from our UAT environment. Please contact your relationship manager for more information or access.
Fixes include the below. If you have any questions please contact us at hello@videotranslator.ai.
Spaces In FileTemplate And FileItem Names Transcription Without Time-Coding Transcription Copy Function Edit/Exit Modals Removed/Modified Fixes To Locking Cosmetic Fixes To Billing January 2020: Spaces In FileTemplate And FileItem Names Previously, it was not possible to have spaces in fileTemplate and fileItem names.</description></item><item><title>Real life Dr Dolittle: We are on our way to talking to the animals and AI may make happen sooner than you think!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-jan-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-jan-2020/</guid><description>Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be fantastic if we could understand what our pets were trying to tell us? Having them be able to communicate if they like the food we give them, when they&amp;rsquo;re not feeling well and when they want to be pet, would take out so much of the guess work. (Although hearing dogs constantly asking to have a ball thrown might get a bit old after a while). Researchers are looking into decoding animal languages and we are here for it!</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays from VideoTranslator!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-hoidays-from-videotranslator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-hoidays-from-videotranslator/</guid><description>What a year it&amp;rsquo;s been! From our launch in May we would not have believed we&amp;rsquo;d come so far in such a short amount of time.
Thank You Thank you everyone for all your support! We want to wish you and yours a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year. We hope you have a brilliant 2020!
Everyone who engaged with us, others that offered feedback, and folks who made a purchasing decision - thank you very much.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: For the Love of Language</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-17-dec-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-17-dec-2019/</guid><description>Language. It's something we're passionate about here at Video Translator, we can't get enough of it. And, judging by the news that&amp;rsquo;s come out in the past week, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of folks out there who share our passion. We&amp;rsquo;re delving into language from all across the globe this week; NLP research engineers working with pidgin English, YouTube India is branching out into local and regional Indian languages, Navajo is getting it&amp;rsquo;s own version of one of the most popular (read: annoying for adults) songs amongst toddlers and we see the effects on the brain from being bilingual from an early age.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Exciting developments for Epilepsy patients, Amazon has added 22 new languages to Amazon Translate and has Microsoft given children the ability to speak to reindeer?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-10-dec-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-10-dec-2019/</guid><description>It seems like every week there are exciting new developments with artificial intelligence being used in the health, medicine and science fields; and that&amp;rsquo;s because, well, there is. There is often quite a negative attitude amongst the public in relation to AI, &amp;ldquo;they&amp;rsquo;re going to take our jobs!&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s the end of the human race!&amp;rdquo; But it&amp;rsquo;s not all doom and gloom. Really good, positive, and not to mention lifesaving advances in medicine, are taking place all with AI and proving that our new robot overlords are not planning on taking over the world just quite yet&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>60% Of The Content Produced By US YouTubers Is Watched In Other Countries</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/60-of-the-content-produced-by-us-youtubers-is-watched-in-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/60-of-the-content-produced-by-us-youtubers-is-watched-in-other-countries/</guid><description>Google produces all sorts of very interesting research. I mean, all kinds! One of the specific bits of intel which is well worth tracking is Think With Google.
Today we are going to look at a set of remarkable trend lines which point the way in which the world is heading.
We look at a 3 behaviour and cultural shifts inside YouTube.
2 Behavioural And Cultural Shifts You should really read the article yourself, but the below was what we found super useful.</description></item><item><title>What A Hindi Speaking AI Sounds Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</guid><description>A few posts ago we transcribed an Indian English video using a Speech-To-Text Indian English transcription Artificial Intelligence (AI). Today we are going to take the same idea forward, and now going to translate the video into Hindi.
To recap, we used a sample clip from Rajya Sabha TV which as (a) transcribed using a speech-to-text AI, and (b) cleaned up by a human. We will now clean it up a little bit more, and then translate the content into Hindi.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Hello baby! Machine learning helping to understand placental health, did Shakespeare have help? And advances in health and medicine thanks to AI.</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-26-nov-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-26-nov-2019/</guid><description>Considering it is something that keeps the human race going, maternal and placental health is still not properly understood, which proves extremely detrimental to the health of mother and baby during pregnancy. Thanks to a new development in AI technology, that will begin to change. We&amp;rsquo;re also looking at how educators in the US are frantically searching for a better solution to interpretations services that help communicate with non-English speaking families and we look at the leaps and bounds being made in medicine thanks to machine learning.</description></item><item><title>Winning: We Won The JobsForNSW MVP Grant! Before, During And After...</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/winning-how-we-won-a-jobsfornsw-mvp-grant/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/winning-how-we-won-a-jobsfornsw-mvp-grant/</guid><description>DISCLAIMER: This blog post was updated after having a conversation with JobsForNSW. [3 Dec 2019]
Please check the JobsForNSW website for updates. The process covered below changes regularly and DO NOT rely on the below to be correct going forward. It was correct at time of publication, but talking to the JobsForNSW staff it is LIKELY to change pretty soon.
Earlier this year we put in an application for a Minimum Viable Product Grant from JobsForNSW, a NSW Government initiative.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: AI to the rescue! Using machine learning for the greater good; advances in medicine, agriculture and saving lives, is there anything we can't do with the help of artificial intelligence?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-12-nov-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-12-nov-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another AI focused week and with so much going on in the world of Artificial Intelligence, can you blame us? The field of medicine and science have long been advocates of using AI for the greater good and it appears there are some incredible trail blazers helping to make that happen.
1. A Star Professor—And Her Radical, AI-Powered Plan To Discover New Drugs Using AI to discover new medicine One woman is using her incredible skills and mind to advance the way in which drugs can be discovered and created with the help of artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Foreign signs installed to save lives, when seeing isn't believing; learning about deepfake videos, content creators coming together to save the planet and hilarious movie translations</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-05-nov-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-05-nov-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s the start of a new month and news from around the globe keeps on rolling in. This week we&amp;rsquo;ve learnt the power of YouTube, its content creators and their followers and how they&amp;rsquo;re working together for the greater good. We also focus on the Western Australian Government&amp;rsquo;s foreign language road signs initiative that aims to save lives and we delve into the world of deepfake videos. Are they as dangerous as they seem?</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Google's latest Pixel 4 app impresses, praise for Nobel Prize winner and a feel-good video to brighten your week</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-29-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-29-oct-2019/</guid><description>Exciting news for content creators this week at Instagram&amp;rsquo;s IGTV releases features that will allow videos to viewed as a series. Google is releasing an on-device transcribing app that may be a game-changer, plus just because we loved it so; a video showing a deaf father signing to his newborn daughter, that has really hit us with all the feels.
1. Pixel 4’s live transcription goes up against “real-life” challenges Image courtesy of The Wall Street Journal Google is a releasing a new built in app in their Pixel 4 and honestly, it&amp;rsquo;s very impressive.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Travelling back in time with AI, learning the love of translation and why it is imperative to get more interpreters in courthouses to aid domestic violence cases</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-22-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-22-oct-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another big week in AI news, from assisting in search and rescue methods to aiding doctors in detecting brain bleeds, it&amp;rsquo;s being proven time and time again how Artificial Intelligence can help humanity in meaningful ways. We also see that AI is helping historians create a portal into the past of Europe and creating virtual worlds that we can experience. In other news, one woman is advocating for more support and resources for translators in domestic violence cases and one author and translator explains her love for language and translation.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Babies teaching us how best to teach AI, glasses made for translation and keeping an eye on our giant fishy friends with the help of Artificial Intelligence</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-15-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-15-oct-2019/</guid><description>More than just cute little stinkers, babies are exceptional learners, so good in fact that we&amp;rsquo;re trying to simulate their learning process to assist AI in becoming evermore smarter. Our first article details just how babies learn and what they&amp;rsquo;re doing to make AI do the same. Plus, machine learning is helping us prepare and respond to natural disasters and an app is now available to help content creators reach their target market, with the click of a button.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Open Captions for Deaf and Hard of Hearing People</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/importance-of-open-captions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/importance-of-open-captions/</guid><description>It comes as no surprise that for hard of hearing and deaf people, closed captions are a necessity for being able to watch TV, films and online videos. We&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned before the need for more captions and subtitles to be present in cinemas and as highlighted in this Washington Post article, &amp;ldquo;accessing online material&amp;hellip;can be a challenge for differently abled people.&amp;rdquo;
This is one of the reasons we believe it is so important to include open captions in online videos.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: Translation devices changing the business game, machine learning aiding scientific research and the world's first ever AI concert</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-08-oct-2019/</guid><description>The art of translation has been a skilled required by humans for over 2000 years, we&amp;rsquo;ve got a few interesting articles that highlight just how important it is and one translator shares with us what she&amp;rsquo;s learnt after being in the business for 20 years. We&amp;rsquo;re also looking at how machine learning is aiding scientists in researching plants, AI writers writing as well as humans can, and we celebrate as Armenia hosts the first ever AI concert.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: AI is here to help; translation at the tip of your ears; and Google's ALBERT is receiving top ranks</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-01-oct-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-01-oct-2019/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s been a lot going on with AI in particular this week. Read on to get up to date on some of the most interesting things coming out of the world of Artificial Intelligence. There&amp;rsquo;s also top ranking machine learning systems and earbuds that can translate languages as you&amp;rsquo;re hearing them.
1. Yes Bank creates &amp;lsquo;Yes Robot&amp;rsquo; using Microsoft Cognitive Services Yes Robot A bank in India has created AI assistant, &amp;lsquo;Yes Robot&amp;rsquo; to provide 24 hour customer service to its patrons.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: September 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-september-2019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-september-2019/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy month for us so far. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of new and exciting features we&amp;rsquo;re still developing so watch this space! In the meantime, there are a couple of updates and patches to tell you about.
Embedding Captions Previously, to embed captions onto your video it was possible to do so from the captions tab. This tab is now only used to make edits to the captions. To embed captions, it is now done by using the Audio Overlay tab.</description></item><item><title>The Weekly Roundup: AI tools are transforming Indian healthcare, growth in the Translations Market and more</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-24-sept-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-weekly-roundup-24-sept-2019/</guid><description>Welcome to the Weekly Roundup!
Each week we put together a list of articles featuring some of the most interesting ideas and news in the field. This week we take a look at how AI tools are helping to transform Indian healthcare, machine learning is being used to create new music, plus much more.
Read on to find out what&amp;rsquo;s been going on in the past week.
1. Why one media buyer is embracing programmatic linear TV Linear television can be a tough nut to crack when it comes to advertising and brand reach, but Global director of media strategy at PHD Media, Nick Vernola believes new technology can hold the solution.</description></item><item><title>The 8 Best Short Video Apps for Android</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-8-best-short-video-apps-for-android/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-8-best-short-video-apps-for-android/</guid><description>Short video clips continue to gain in popularity along with social platforms like Instagram and Snapchap. As smartphone video technology has improved along with our access to video media online, there has been a growing need for short video apps on smartphones. TechloMedia recently published a report on trending social video apps. We’ve taken a look at these as well as the top performing video apps in the Google Play Store (as of August 2019).</description></item><item><title>Why Post Video To Social Media: 3 Tips</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-post-video-to-social-media-3-tips/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-post-video-to-social-media-3-tips/</guid><description>Several recent reports show that video content outperforms every other type of post on social media. In other words, using video content in social media marketing is a very good strategy. In this post we look at some numbers, and try to work out what this means for content creators and marketers.
Renderforest put together an insightful report on social video marketing. Here are some of their statistics:
100 million hours of video per day is watched on Facebook.</description></item><item><title>The Growing Pains Of Diversity And A Possible Solution</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-growing-pains-of-diversity-and-a-possible-solution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/the-growing-pains-of-diversity-and-a-possible-solution/</guid><description>This post is not really about diversity. It is about the granular challenges around governance in an increasingly complex world, and operational solutions which may work going forward.
We look at three events which took place in this week. What the problem is, and what a solution might be. These events are:
Trump Administration’s Deregulation Drive Begins to Impact Language Industry Sometimes Lost In Translation, With Dialects Context Is Key Translating verdicts will help all litigants Trump Administration’s Deregulation Drive Begins to Impact Language Industry US federal regulations have generally favored the language services industry.</description></item><item><title>How We Used SEO To Come Up With A New Name</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-we-used-seo-to-come-up-with-a-new-name/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-we-used-seo-to-come-up-with-a-new-name/</guid><description>Our original name was QBL Media, and our new name is videotranslator.ai. The original name did not really work, and was always a temporary name.
This post covers some of the context of where our platform came from, and what changes happened in the course of getting this app to market, including a pivot.
We used SEO to determine a new name. Read on to understand why this was done, how it was done, and what benefits we expect to get from the name change.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes: May 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-may-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/patch-notes-may-2019/</guid><description>There are a number of bug fixes and patches, which may affect your user experience. Fixes include (a) and upload bug, (b) a naming convention enhancement, (c) a UI timing bug, (d) UI help bug, and (e) UI folder bug.
May 2019: Upload Bug Previously, if you uploaded certain files, and exceeded certain file sizes, the application would error without notifying the user.
Specifically, on the operational side, we setup all client with file and size permissions at enrolment.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guide: Free Trial Registration</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-free-trial-registration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-free-trial-registration/</guid><description>Everyone likes to try before they buy. This post is a visual guide to how to sign up for the free trial, and logging into the Video Translator platform. This post covers:
Sign up for the free trial Select your preferred languages Verify your email address, and log into the application On reviewing this visual guide, you should be able to sign up to Video Translator platform for free, and transcribe and translate up to 20 minutes of video content.</description></item><item><title>We Have An Explainer Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-have-an-explainer-video/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/we-have-an-explainer-video/</guid><description>We are a Sydney based, media focused technology platform provider, looking to make the world a more accessible place. Our primary value proposition is a transcription and translation platform, with a focus on audio and video content.
Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s translation platform (&amp;ldquo;the application&amp;rdquo;) is an Internet-enabled SaaS (Software as a Service) platform which assists content creators (&amp;ldquo;the client&amp;rdquo;) to engage with stakeholders (&amp;ldquo;the audience&amp;rdquo;) from different linguistic backgrounds. The application is used to convert hypermedia content from one language to another, using an Artificial Intelligence (AI) assisted process.</description></item><item><title>How To Add A Forum To Your Website</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-add-a-forum-to-your-website/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-add-a-forum-to-your-website/</guid><description>Given we are getting super close to launch, there are a lot of conversations with prospects who are keen to use our product. We get many (welcome) questions from prospects/clients on how to use the platform. Additionally, because we are a new start up, we don't have great documentation. How to solve this problem with limited bandwidth?
The requirement is pretty simple, an easy way to communicate with prospects and clients, which stacks.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/happy-new-year/</guid><description>We had a very good 2018 here at Video Translator. While a challenging year, the majority of the platform was built in 2018. Oddly, doing hard things well is enormously empowering, if a little scary. Important events in 2018 included:
Moved into Fishburners, our brilliant co-working space, in the new Sydney Start Up Hub. Brought on two fantastic developers, Vivek Kumar and Pranay Shah. Both these guys have been absolutely critical in getting our platform over the line.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Add Languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-add-languages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-add-languages/</guid><description>We look at how to add languages for transcription, translation and transliteration.
That is, assume we have a video in English. We now need to translate into French and German. We need to add French and add German into our account, before the transcription or translation will work.
In brief, we assume that no additional languages were selected during the sign up process, and now we are looking to add additional languages to our account.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/welcome-to-video-translator/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 11:16:52 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/welcome-to-video-translator/</guid><description>Welcome to the Video Translator. We are a Sydney based, media focused technology platform provider, looking to make the world a more accessible place. Our primary value proposition is a translation platform, with a focus on video translation.
Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s translation platform (&amp;ldquo;the application&amp;rdquo;) is an Internet-enabled SaaS (Software as a Service) platform which assists content creators (&amp;ldquo;the client&amp;rdquo;) to engage with stakeholders (&amp;ldquo;the audience&amp;rdquo;) from different linguistic backgrounds. The application is used to convert hypermedia content from one language to another, using an Artificial Intelligence (AI) assisted process.</description></item></channel></rss>