<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>German on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/tags/german/</link><description>Recent content in German on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/tags/german/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>One place, many languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-place-many-languages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-place-many-languages/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re talking language today and how diverse it can be even in the same country, or city! Germany is still a country divided when it comes to what a pancake should be called - maybe they should be called egg-cakes? Also Mandarin is now Melbourne and Sydney&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;most widely spoken community language.&amp;rdquo;
Language matters, it&amp;rsquo;s important culturally and on a deeper level to help us identify with ourselves and others.</description></item><item><title>Samples From A Voice Over Robot: French, German and Dutch</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</guid><description>Following on from last week&amp;rsquo;s blog post, where we looked at different English dialects, we are going to do much the same today in Dutch, French and German.
Do you like the below examples? Let us know - we are super keen to hear what you think?
To try other languages (for FREE!) sign up to the free trial and give it a go!
Steps First, as per our usual create a new item using the English language template.</description></item><item><title>English German Video Translation (What is a Babybündel?)</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/english-to-german-video-translation-what-is-a-babyb%C3%BCndel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/english-to-german-video-translation-what-is-a-babyb%C3%BCndel/</guid><description>Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here. What we are going to do today is transcribe content to a different language, and use a practical example to demonstrate the technology.
We will be using this video, from the team at NSWHealth. The video is a simple, but effective solution for young mothers, where NSWHealth provide a useful box of household items aimed at first time mothers.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guides: How To Translate A Video without Sound</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-translate-a-video-without-sound/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tutorial-how-to-translate-a-video-without-sound/</guid><description>We look at how to translate video content. Translation is the communication of the meaning of a source-language text by means of an equivalent target-language text1. In brief, we will (i) upload a video, (ii) add text, (iii) translate the video text, (iv) download a translated video.
Steps We need a sample video to work with, and will use the Big Bunny video from Sample Video&amp;rsquo;s.
To view this video please enable JavaScript, and consider upgrading to a web browser that supports HTML5 video</description></item></channel></rss>