<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Right to left on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/right-to-left/</link><description>Recent content in Right to left on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/right-to-left/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cara Menambahkan Subtitle Ke Video YouTube, Facebook dan LinkedIn</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tambah-subtitle-youtube-facebook-linkedin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tambah-subtitle-youtube-facebook-linkedin/</guid><description>Hello semuanya!
Kembali lagi bersama Video Translator dimana kami akan memberikan tips and tricks tentang dunia media dan terjemahan.
Di artikel sebelumnya, kami sudah membahas cara agar kalian bisa membuat file SRT.
Kali ini, kami akan membahas gimana caranya kalian bisa menambahkan subtitle ke video kalian di YouTube, Facebook maupun LinkedIn.
Ayo, kita mulai!
Menambahkan Subtitle Ke YouTube Kalian pernah nggak lagi nonton video YouTube di tempat umum dan suara videonya nggak kedengeran gara-gara suara di sekitar kalian lebih kenceng dari pada suara videonya?</description></item><item><title>How To Transcribe English Into Hebrew: ChangePlan</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-english-into-hebrew-changeplan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-english-into-hebrew-changeplan/</guid><description>Video Translator&amp;rsquo;s platform provides a client with the ability to transcribe and translate content to/from a number of languages, as discussed here. Today, we will be using the video translation platform on a video from our friends at ChangePlan. We will do the following:
Transcribe ChangePlan&amp;rsquo;s video using Australian English. Fix up spelling/grammar in our captions. Translate ChangePlan&amp;rsquo;s video from English -&amp;gt; Hebrew. If you are looking to replicate this process, please note, after the translation step, it is highly recommended that you have a Hebrew qualified subject-matter expert finesse the captions.</description></item></channel></rss>