<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Audio on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/audio/</link><description>Recent content in Audio on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/audio/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What Arabic Voices are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</guid><description>Previously we&amp;rsquo;ve gone through the list of our English speaking AI and the different dialects they speak. You can see them all here.
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re looking at our Arabic speaking AI and the different dialects and voices available.
If you need a reminder as to how to select the appropriate AI language and dialect, check out our article here.
Now, on to the voices! We&amp;rsquo;ve used the phrase birds of a feather, flock together or الطيور على أشكالها تقع for our AI to say each time for the examples.</description></item><item><title>What A Hindi Speaking AI Sounds Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</guid><description>A few posts ago we transcribed an Indian English video using a Speech-To-Text Indian English transcription Artificial Intelligence (AI). Today we are going to take the same idea forward, and now going to translate the video into Hindi.
To recap, we used a sample clip from Rajya Sabha TV which as (a) transcribed using a speech-to-text AI, and (b) cleaned up by a human. We will now clean it up a little bit more, and then translate the content into Hindi.</description></item><item><title>Samples From A Voice Over Robot: French, German and Dutch</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</guid><description>Following on from last week&amp;rsquo;s blog post, where we looked at different English dialects, we are going to do much the same today in Dutch, French and German.
Do you like the below examples? Let us know - we are super keen to hear what you think?
To try other languages (for FREE!) sign up to the free trial and give it a go!
Steps First, as per our usual create a new item using the English language template.</description></item><item><title>AI Dubbing: What Different Dialects Of English Sound Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</guid><description>Today we are going to look AI dubbing and look at a few different samples of what an AI can sound like in English. We are going to do something pretty simple, we will use the quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog for our seed text.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what this sentence is, quoting from Wikipedia, &amp;ldquo;The quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog&amp;rdquo; is an English-language pangram—a sentence that contains all of the letters of the alphabet.</description></item><item><title>AI Transcription, Translation And Dubbing: How To Think About Accuracy</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-transcription-translation-and-dubbing-how-to-think-about-accuracy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-transcription-translation-and-dubbing-how-to-think-about-accuracy/</guid><description>We get a number of questions around AI Accuracy, and depending on the context, the question can refer to a number of things.
Wanted to put down a note describing the various iterations of what Accuracy in Artificial Intelligence refers to, and where it is going from my point of view.
Is the AI accurate? Is AI accurate when it comes to Transcription? Is AI accurate when it comes to Translation?</description></item><item><title>Text-To-Speech: AI Dubbing And What You Can Do With It</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/text-to-speech-ai-dubbing-and-what-you-can-do-with-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/text-to-speech-ai-dubbing-and-what-you-can-do-with-it/</guid><description>Today we are going to look AI dubbing and its various use cases. If you are wondering, is my content suitable for AI dubbing, or AI localisation? In simple terms:
What is dubbing or dub localisation? Should I use a human, or a machine for my dubbing? How do I use a video translator to dub my video? Rules of thumb, or heuristics, to achieve a superior outcome with AI dubbing?</description></item><item><title>Visual Guide: Audio To Text</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-audio-to-text/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-audio-to-text/</guid><description>This post covers how to transcribe audio content. We will use a podcast as our sample audio content, and assume you are on a free trial. This post covers:
Sign into the application. Create an audio specific template. Create a new item, with our audio specific template as parent. Upload our podcast, and then use an Artificial Intelligence (AI) to transcribe our content. On reviewing this visual guide, you will be able to upload your own audio content, and transcribe using an AI.</description></item></channel></rss>