<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Audio on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/audio/</link><description>Recent content in Audio on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/audio/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cara Menambahkan Musik Ke Video (Premiere Pro, iMovie, Canva)</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/cara-menambahkan-musik-ke-video/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/cara-menambahkan-musik-ke-video/</guid><description>Video merupakan salah satu cara paling menarik untuk menjangkau orang-orang saat ini, baik sebagai bentuk konten promosi untuk perusahaan atau sebagai outlet kreatif. Namun, meskipun visual biasanya menjadi fokus utama video, musik juga memainkan peran integral.
Salah satu komponen yang sering diabaikan adalah penggunaan latar musik. Seringkali, yang membuat video Youtube menonjol adalah pilihan latar musik yang tepat dari genre dan periode yang berbeda.
Pada artikel ini, kami akan membahas tentang bagaimana kalian bisa menambahkan musik ke video menggunakan Adobe Premiere Pro, iMovie, dan Canva.</description></item><item><title>How To Add Music To Your Video (Premiere Pro, iMovie, Canva)</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/add-music-to-your-video/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/add-music-to-your-video/</guid><description>Video is one of the most engaging ways to reach people today, whether as a form of promotional content for a company or as a creative outlet. However, while visuals are usually the primary focus of a video, music plays an integral role in its engagement.
One component that is often overlooked is the use of background music. Often, what makes Youtube videos stand out is the correct choice of background music from different genres and periods.</description></item><item><title>4 Cara Mudah Mengubah Video Menjadi MP3</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/4-cara-mudah-mengubah-video-menjadi-mp3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/4-cara-mudah-mengubah-video-menjadi-mp3/</guid><description>Akhir-akhir ini, kita sering banget nih ngeliat artis-artis pada ngebuat podcast. Misalnya, Deddy Corbuzier dan anaknya Azka.
Kalau kalian lihat, hasil podcast Deddy di YouTube kan berupa video. Terus, gimana dong caranya kita bisa ngedengerin podcast tersebut hanya berupa audio? Ya caranya dengan mengubah video tersebut jadi MP3.
Sepuluh tahun yang lalu, proses mengubah video menjadi MP3 itu lumaya ribet. Cuman, karena berbagai macam kemajuan teknologi, proses ini sekarang udah mudah banget loh!</description></item><item><title>4 Easy Ways To Convert Your Video To Mp3</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/4-easy-ways-to-convert-your-video-to-mp3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/4-easy-ways-to-convert-your-video-to-mp3/</guid><description>With the popularity of podcasts, there is now a higher demand for MP4 to MP3 conversion.
The good news is, converting your videos to MP3 is so much easier today than it was 10 years ago. There are many different ways to do this, and you can do it in few simple steps!
But before we begin&amp;hellip; let&amp;rsquo;s tackle the biggest question: is it legal?
Is Converting A Video To MP3 Legal?</description></item><item><title>Multiple Ways To Transcribe Your Audio</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/multiple-ways-to-transcribe-your-audio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/multiple-ways-to-transcribe-your-audio/</guid><description>Whether you&amp;rsquo;re attending a meeting or having a sudden burst of inspiration, having a transcription can be very helpful.
The thing with transcribing audio is that&amp;hellip; it is such a pain to do one. If you have transcribed audios, you know how long it takes to transcribe a 5-minute conversation, let alone an hour-long meeting. You are stuck in the endless cycle of playing and pausing the audio.
Does transcribing have to be that hard?</description></item><item><title>Berbagai Cara Untuk Menghilangkan Suara Bising/Noise Di Audio Atau Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/menghilangkan-suara-bising-atau-noise/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/menghilangkan-suara-bising-atau-noise/</guid><description>Kita semua tahu betapa menyebalkannya ketika harus mendengarkan video/audio yang memiliki banyak sekali suara berisik.
Orang-orang yang tugasnya setiap hari melakukan transkripsi ucapan-ke-teks pasti tahu banget rasanya.
Kualitas suara dari audio atau video kalian itu sangat mempengaruhi proses transkripsi, apalagi kalau hal yang harus kalian salin adalah materi yang sangat penting, seperti kasus hukum.
Kalau audio kalian dipenuhi dengan suara bising, bukan hanya mesin yang dilengkapi dengan tenaga kecerdasan buatan yang akan kesulitan untuk menyalin tulisan, tetapi juga sulit untuk manusia.</description></item><item><title>Different Ways To Reduce Audio Background Noise</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/reduce-background-noise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/reduce-background-noise/</guid><description>We all know how annoying it can be to listen to noisy audio.
Professionals who do speech-to-text transcription on a daily basis sure can relate to this matter.
Your audio quality matters when you are doing the transcription process, especially if what you are trying to transcribe is an important matter, such as a legal case.
If your audio is filled with loud background noises, not only that it will be hard for the AI to automatically transcribe your audio but also for a human to manually transcribe it.</description></item><item><title>What Arabic Voices are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</guid><description>Previously we&amp;rsquo;ve gone through the list of our English speaking AI and the different dialects they speak. You can see them all here.
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re looking at our Arabic speaking AI and the different dialects and voices available.
If you need a reminder as to how to select the appropriate AI language and dialect, check out our article here.
Now, on to the voices! We&amp;rsquo;ve used the phrase birds of a feather, flock together or الطيور على أشكالها تقع for our AI to say each time for the examples.</description></item><item><title>What A Hindi Speaking AI Sounds Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-a-hindi-speaking-ai-sounds-like/</guid><description>A few posts ago we transcribed an Indian English video using a Speech-To-Text Indian English transcription Artificial Intelligence (AI). Today we are going to take the same idea forward, and now going to translate the video into Hindi.
To recap, we used a sample clip from Rajya Sabha TV which as (a) transcribed using a speech-to-text AI, and (b) cleaned up by a human. We will now clean it up a little bit more, and then translate the content into Hindi.</description></item><item><title>Samples From A Voice Over Robot: French, German and Dutch</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/samples-from-a-voice-over-robot-french-german-and-dutch/</guid><description>Following on from last week&amp;rsquo;s blog post, where we looked at different English dialects, we are going to do much the same today in Dutch, French and German.
Do you like the below examples? Let us know - we are super keen to hear what you think?
To try other languages (for FREE!) sign up to the free trial and give it a go!
Steps First, as per our usual create a new item using the English language template.</description></item><item><title>AI Dubbing: What Different Dialects Of English Sound Like</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-dubbing-what-different-dialects-of-english-sound-like/</guid><description>Today we are going to look AI dubbing and look at a few different samples of what an AI can sound like in English. We are going to do something pretty simple, we will use the quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog for our seed text.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what this sentence is, quoting from Wikipedia, &amp;ldquo;The quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog&amp;rdquo; is an English-language pangram—a sentence that contains all of the letters of the alphabet.</description></item><item><title>AI Transcription, Translation And Dubbing: How To Think About Accuracy</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-transcription-translation-and-dubbing-how-to-think-about-accuracy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-transcription-translation-and-dubbing-how-to-think-about-accuracy/</guid><description>We get a number of questions around AI Accuracy, and depending on the context, the question can refer to a number of things.
Wanted to put down a note describing the various iterations of what Accuracy in Artificial Intelligence refers to, and where it is going from my point of view.
Is the AI accurate? Is AI accurate when it comes to Transcription? Is AI accurate when it comes to Translation?</description></item><item><title>Text-To-Speech: AI Dubbing And What You Can Do With It</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/text-to-speech-ai-dubbing-and-what-you-can-do-with-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/text-to-speech-ai-dubbing-and-what-you-can-do-with-it/</guid><description>Today we are going to look AI dubbing and its various use cases. If you are wondering, is my content suitable for AI dubbing, or AI localisation? In simple terms:
What is dubbing or dub localisation? Should I use a human, or a machine for my dubbing? How do I use a video translator to dub my video? Rules of thumb, or heuristics, to achieve a superior outcome with AI dubbing?</description></item><item><title>Visual Guide: Audio To Text</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-audio-to-text/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-audio-to-text/</guid><description>This post covers how to transcribe audio content. We will use a podcast as our sample audio content, and assume you are on a free trial. This post covers:
Sign into the application. Create an audio specific template. Create a new item, with our audio specific template as parent. Upload our podcast, and then use an Artificial Intelligence (AI) to transcribe our content. On reviewing this visual guide, you will be able to upload your own audio content, and transcribe using an AI.</description></item></channel></rss>