<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chinese on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/tags/chinese/</link><description>Recent content in Chinese on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/tags/chinese/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How QAChef Is Reaching Clients In A Tough Market</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-qachef-is-reaching-clients-in-a-tough-market/</guid><description>The hospitality business is in a hard place right now because of Covid 19.
QAChef is a technology company which digitizes food safety compliance processes through a single handheld device, thus enabling unprecedented ingredient-to-customer food traceability and greater efficiency and productivity.
QAChef&amp;#39;s handheld device being used to measure temperature during cooking So QAChef is in a fantastic position, a ready for market product which enhances traceability across large scale food production - perfect given the focus on food safety and associated health implications in the wake of the Covid-19 pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Translate Your English Video Into Filipino And Chinese</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/translate-your-english-video-to-filipino-and-chinese/</guid><description>Business today relies on content creation. How do you expand your market? We show you how to add open captions for accessibility wins, and translate your video content into Tagalog and Chinese to expand your target client base!
Matija Squire is a LinkedIn coach, all round nice person plus a good friend. And she is doing something really cool!
We all know Covid-19 has distrupted all our lives. Some of us are lucky enough to be able to earn an income by working from home online.</description></item><item><title>Clipping Chinese App: How To Translate Video Into Mandarin Chinese With AI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clipping-chinese-app-how-to-translate-video-into-mandarin-chinese-with-ai/</guid><description>One very common use case of video translator is as a Chinese clipping app. What is a Chinese clipping app?
This term is used by content creators to mean how to translate a video from English to Chinese, and they generally mean a short video for various social media channels.
In this blog post we are going to look at how to translate a small video from English to Mandarin (Simplified Chinese).</description></item><item><title>Mr Sh*thole: What To Do When Your AI Misbehaves</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mr-shithole-what-to-do-when-your-ai-misbehaves/</guid><description>Today we look at a humorous articles which look at what happens when AI goes wrong. Here at video translator we like to keep abreast of the latest news in the intersection of Artificial Intelligence, Natural Language Programming, Human Languages and Culture.
Read on to find out how Facebook&amp;rsquo;s AI got in trouble, and why Oracle thinks replacing your manager with a robot is likely, and a good thing to boot!</description></item><item><title>One place, many languages</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-place-many-languages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/one-place-many-languages/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re talking language today and how diverse it can be even in the same country, or city! Germany is still a country divided when it comes to what a pancake should be called - maybe they should be called egg-cakes? Also Mandarin is now Melbourne and Sydney&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;most widely spoken community language.&amp;rdquo;
Language matters, it&amp;rsquo;s important culturally and on a deeper level to help us identify with ourselves and others.</description></item><item><title>9 of China's Best Short Video Apps</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/9-of-chinas-best-short-video-apps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/9-of-chinas-best-short-video-apps/</guid><description>Short video makers are an up and coming category of apps that are really hitting the ground running in China. Short video clips (even less than a second long) have been gaining in popularity along with social platforms like Instagram and Snapchat, and especially in China with Wechat and Weibo. The social component to online video broadcasting has changed how we consume short videos, and what we expect from them.</description></item><item><title>Visual Guide: Free Trial Registration</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-free-trial-registration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/visual-guide-free-trial-registration/</guid><description>Everyone likes to try before they buy. This post is a visual guide to how to sign up for the free trial, and logging into the Video Translator platform. This post covers:
Sign up for the free trial Select your preferred languages Verify your email address, and log into the application On reviewing this visual guide, you should be able to sign up to Video Translator platform for free, and transcribe and translate up to 20 minutes of video content.</description></item><item><title>How To Use Auto Overlay To Simplify Transcription</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-auto-overlay-to-simplify-transcription/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-use-auto-overlay-to-simplify-transcription/</guid><description>We got this video from OSL Brokerage&amp;rsquo;s LinkedIn page. We are not suggesting that we have any relationship with OSL, and largely, we are using this content to demonstrate the process by which video content can be translated.
This specific video already has captions, so we don&amp;rsquo;t need these per se. However, we will be adding Chinese captions as an overlay, as opposed to captions.
The final output is shown below.</description></item><item><title>How To Transcribe Lots of Different Accents Accurately</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-lots-of-different-accents-accurately/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-transcribe-lots-of-different-accents-accurately/</guid><description>Today, we will look at how to transcribe many different accents correctly. First off, what does this question even mean in terms of AI?
The video we are working with is from Institute for Communication in Health Care (ICH) at the Australian National University (ANU).
Looking at the ICH&amp;rsquo;s mission statement, &amp;ldquo;The ICH’s mission is to build an international, collaborative research and training hub in healthcare communication to improve patient safety and quality of healthcare practice around the world&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;</description></item></channel></rss>