<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Subtitles on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/subtitles/</link><description>Recent content in Subtitles on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/subtitles/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Berbagai Cara Untuk Menghilangkan Suara Bising/Noise Di Audio Atau Video</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/menghilangkan-suara-bising-atau-noise/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/menghilangkan-suara-bising-atau-noise/</guid><description>Kita semua tahu betapa menyebalkannya waktu kita ngedengerin video/audio yang memiliki banyak sekali suara berisik.
Orang-orang yang tugasnya melakukan transkripsi ucapan-ke-teks setiap hari pasti tahu banget rasanya.
Kualitas suara dari audio atau video kalian itu sangat mempengaruhi proses transkripsi, apalagi kalau hal yang harus kalian salin adalah materi yang sangat penting, seperti kasus legal.
Kalau audio kalian dipenuhi dengan suara bising, bukan hanya mesin yang dilengkapi dengan tenaga kecerdasan buatan yang akan kesulitan untuk menyalin tulisan, tetapi juga sulit untuk manusia.</description></item><item><title>Different Ways To Reduce Audio Background Noise</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/reduce-background-noise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/reduce-background-noise/</guid><description>We all know how annoying it can be to listen to noisy audio.
Professionals who do speech-to-text transcription on a daily basis sure can relate to this matter.
Your audio quality matters when you are doing the transcription process, especially if what you are trying to transcribe is an important matter, such as a legal case.
If your audio is filled with loud background noises, not only that it will be hard for the AI to automatically transcribe your audio but also for a human to manually transcribe it.</description></item><item><title>Cara Menambahkan Subtitle Ke Video YouTube, Facebook dan LinkedIn</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tambah-subtitle-youtube-facebook-linkedin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/tambah-subtitle-youtube-facebook-linkedin/</guid><description>Hello semuanya!
Kembali lagi bersama Video Translator dimana kami akan memberikan tips and tricks tentang dunia media dan terjemahan.
Di artikel sebelumnya, kami sudah membahas cara agar kalian bisa membuat file SRT.
Kali ini, kami akan membahas gimana caranya kalian bisa menambahkan subtitle ke video kalian di YouTube, Facebook maupun LinkedIn.
Ayo, kita mulai!
Menambahkan Subtitle Ke YouTube Kalian pernah nggak lagi nonton video YouTube di tempat umum dan suara videonya nggak kedengeran gara-gara suara di sekitar kalian lebih kenceng dari pada suara videonya?</description></item><item><title>How To Add Subtitles To YouTube, Facebook and LinkedIn Videos</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-add-subtitle-youtube-facebook-linkedin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-add-subtitle-youtube-facebook-linkedin/</guid><description>Hello lovely people!
Welcome back to VideoTranslator support where we will be telling you the tips and tricks regarding the media and translation world.
In the previous post, we have written about how you can create, import, and edit SRT files.
This time, we will be explaining how you can add subtitles to your YouTube, Facebook, and LinkedIn video.
So, without further ado, let&amp;rsquo;s begin!
Adding Subtitles To YouTube Videos Have you ever been on noisy public transport rides and struggled to watch your favorite YouTuber&amp;rsquo;s video?</description></item><item><title>Cara Mengimpor Dan Mengedit File SRT Ke Adobe Premiere Pro</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mengedit-dan-mengimpor-file-srt-ke-premiere-pro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/mengedit-dan-mengimpor-file-srt-ke-premiere-pro/</guid><description>Halo, semuanya!
Kembali lagi bersama Video Translator dimana kami akan memberikan tips and tricks tentang dunia media dan terjemahan.
Kali ini, kami akan membahas cara agar kalian bisa mengimpor dan mengedit file SRT ke Adobe Premiere Pro.
Sebelum mulai, yuk kita cari tahu apa sih file SRT&amp;hellip;
Apa Itu SRT? SRT adalah file teks biasa yang berisi informasi penting mengenai subtitle, termasuk kode waktu awal dan akhir teks kalian untuk memastikan subtitle kalian cocok dengan audio kalian, dan nomor urut subtitle.</description></item><item><title>How To Import And Edit SRT File To Adobe Premiere Pro</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/import-and-edit-srt-file-to-adobe-premiere-pro-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/import-and-edit-srt-file-to-adobe-premiere-pro-/</guid><description>Hello, fam!
Welcome back again to VideoTranslator support where we will be telling you the tips and tricks regarding the media and translation world.
This time, we will be explaining how you can import and edit SRT files to Adobe Premiere Pro.
Before we begin, let&amp;rsquo;s explain what an SRT file is first&amp;hellip;
What Is SRT? SRT is a plain-text file that contains critical information regarding subtitles, including the start and end timecodes of your text to ensure your subtitles match your audio, and the sequential number of subtitles.</description></item><item><title>Reviewing Splice Video Editor on iPhone</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/reviewing-splice-video-editor-on-iphone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/reviewing-splice-video-editor-on-iphone/</guid><description>Hello, fam!
A few weeks back, we have just released an article about the 9 of iOS top video editing apps.
One of the apps that we mentioned in that article is Splice.
So, today, we are going to give you our honest review of the video editing app Splice!
What Is Splice Splice is a free video editing app from the creators of GoPro.
The app claims that it will allow users to:</description></item><item><title>Leaving A Long-Lasting Legacy: Curating Your Family’s History</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/leaving-a-long-lasting-legacy-by-curating-your-familys-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/leaving-a-long-lasting-legacy-by-curating-your-familys-history/</guid><description>I believe everyone wants to leave a legacy.
Many people choose to pass on their homes, investments and possessions.
For Jeff Dormish, leaving a legacy means so much more than that. He does not just want to leave possessions; he wants to pass on his history.
For many Americans, most of their ancestors came from Europe in the great emigration wave before the First World War. Jeff Dormish’s ancestors also came from Europe, Slovenia, to be exact.</description></item><item><title>How To Conveniently Translate Your Videos</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-conveniently-translate-your-videos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-to-conveniently-translate-your-videos/</guid><description>Many of you would have heard about translation. According to Kristen Malmkjær, translation is an activity that aims to convey meaning or meanings of a given linguistic discourse from one language to another.
What are the difficulties in translation? As a multilingual speaker, I have frequently asked to translate different languages. My family would ask me to translate files such as reports, articles and legal documents. However, translation also comes with its challenges.</description></item><item><title>Why Should You Translate Video Content: A Client Perspective</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-translate-video-content-a-client-perspective/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-you-should-translate-video-content-a-client-perspective/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator we do a lot of work in the Internationalization And Localization industry.
But we are not transcribers, translators, or voice over artists. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing.
This happens when a client is looking to try out tech and/or better understand the value proposition, or has their own reasons for us to provide this service.
Sometimes however, the most useful thing we can do is just have a conversation.</description></item><item><title>Video Translation And Its Implications For FireTech</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</guid><description>A recent interview with FireTech Connect was really good fun, with Leigh Kelson hosting a free-wheeling discussion about crisis, technology and the future of AI in the internationalization and localization space.
FireTech Connect The FireTech 2020 program is an initiative of the Peregian Digital Hub, a leading technology incubator based in Noosa on Queensland&amp;rsquo;s Sunshine Coast.
FireTech Connect is funded by the Department of Industry, Science, Energy and Resources through the AusIndustry Entrepreneurs’ Programme; The Queensland State Government&amp;rsquo;s Advance Queensland Program; and Noosa Shire Council.</description></item><item><title>How Subtitling Can Boost ROI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 23:00:01 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</guid><description>Today we look at how to boost ROI or ROAS across your video production lifecycle, and how to make structural decisions which will pay off over a long time frame.
ROI or ROAS: Which One Should I Use? It&amp;rsquo;s actually a pretty messy question, but here are the basics.
ROI: Return on Investment Getting a definition is the starting point, and according to the smart folks at Investopia:
Return on Investment (ROI) is a performance measure used to evaluate the efficiency of an investment or compare the efficiency of a number of different investments.</description></item><item><title>Clients: Why You Make Me Blush!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:02 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we get lots of feedback from clients. Most of it is good, some of it not so much. Recently, as we have started to build out our retail client base it has become interesting.
The product challenge with retail is quite different from an enterprise offering or a managed service. Because the user is not being paid to use the product (or being told to by their manager) expectations for the product are totally different.</description></item><item><title>Accessibility: Why It Matters And How To Avoid Being Sued</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work with clients who are part of the healthcare ecosystem.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, voice over artists, or in this case, nurses/doctors. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing - we are technologists who are trying to service our clients to the best of our ability.
Every now and then a story turns up which brings a lot of our work into sharp focus.</description></item><item><title>What Arabic Voices are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</guid><description>Previously we&amp;rsquo;ve gone through the list of our English speaking AI and the different dialects they speak. You can see them all here.
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re looking at our Arabic speaking AI and the different dialects and voices available.
If you need a reminder as to how to select the appropriate AI language and dialect, check out our article here.
Now, on to the voices! We&amp;rsquo;ve used the phrase birds of a feather, flock together or الطيور على أشكالها تقع for our AI to say each time for the examples.</description></item><item><title>Open Captions: Enhancements November 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/open-captions-enhancements-november-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/open-captions-enhancements-november-2019/</guid><description>Working with a prospect, we added a number of enhancements to our open captions workflow. If you are interested in what open captions are and what its use cases are please have a look at this blog post.
Very simply open captions are generally used as an accessibility tool focused on people who have hearing impairments. More recently due to the rise of streaming services, open captions have been making a come back.</description></item><item><title>Transcribing Indian English: A Simple Guide To Using AI To Speed Up Transcription And Add Open Captions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcribing-indian-english-a-simple-guide-to-using-ai-to-speed-up-transcription-and-add-open-captions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcribing-indian-english-a-simple-guide-to-using-ai-to-speed-up-transcription-and-add-open-captions/</guid><description>Today we are going to look at how to transcribe Indian English. Firstly of course, what is Indian English, and what does it sound like? How many such dialects exist? Have a look.
Now that we know what Indian English sounds like, we are going to use a short clip from Rajya Sabha TV, an Indian government content creator. We use our AI to transcribe this clip.
Lastly, we add an Auto-Overlay so that we can show you the video.</description></item><item><title>How Do I Make Subtitles And Closed Captions?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-do-i-make-subtitles-and-closed-captions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-do-i-make-subtitles-and-closed-captions/</guid><description>Many clients ask how us about subtitles. Generally, this is the first question a prospect asks us about our platform. In practise, they mean a few different things.
We want subtitles for our audio/video content. We have subtitles, but want to make changes to the timing. We want to embed our subtitles into our video file, for use in Social Media. Let us look at these questions in detail.</description></item></channel></rss>