<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Subtitles on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/categories/subtitles/</link><description>Recent content in Subtitles on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/categories/subtitles/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Video Translation And Its Implications For FireTech</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/video-translation-and-its-implications-for-firetech/</guid><description>A recent interview with FireTech Connect was really good fun, with Leigh Kelson hosting a free-wheeling discussion about crisis, technology and the future of AI in the internationalization and localization space.
FireTech Connect The FireTech 2020 program is an initiative of the Peregian Digital Hub, a leading technology incubator based in Noosa on Queensland&amp;rsquo;s Sunshine Coast.
FireTech Connect is funded by the Department of Industry, Science, Energy and Resources through the AusIndustry Entrepreneurs’ Programme; The Queensland State Government&amp;rsquo;s Advance Queensland Program; and Noosa Shire Council.</description></item><item><title>How Subtitling Can Boost ROI</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/ai-internationalization-how-subtitling-can-boost-roi/</guid><description>Today we look at how to boost ROI or ROAS across your video production lifecycle, and how to make structural decisions which will pay off over a long time frame.
ROI or ROAS: Which One Should I Use? It&amp;rsquo;s actually a pretty messy question, but here are the basics.
ROI: Return on Investment Getting a definition is the starting point, and according to the smart folks at Investopia:
Return on Investment (ROI) is a performance measure used to evaluate the efficiency of an investment or compare the efficiency of a number of different investments.</description></item><item><title>Clients: Why You Make Me Blush!</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:02 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/clients-why-you-make-me-blush/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we get lots of feedback from clients. Most of it is good, some of it not so much. Recently, as we have started to build out our retail client base it has become interesting.
The product challenge with retail is quite different from an enterprise offering or a managed service. Because the user is not being paid to use the product (or being told to by their manager) expectations for the product are totally different.</description></item><item><title>Accessibility: Why It Matters And How To Avoid Being Sued</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/accessibility-why-it-matters-and-how-to-avoid-being-sued/</guid><description>At VideoTranslator, we do a lot of work with clients who are part of the healthcare ecosystem.
That being said, we are not transcribers, translators, voice over artists, or in this case, nurses/doctors. We use AI to do transcription, translation and synthetic (AI) dubbing - we are technologists who are trying to service our clients to the best of our ability.
Every now and then a story turns up which brings a lot of our work into sharp focus.</description></item><item><title>What Arabic Voices are Available?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/what-arabic-voices-are-available/</guid><description>Previously we&amp;rsquo;ve gone through the list of our English speaking AI and the different dialects they speak. You can see them all here.
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re looking at our Arabic speaking AI and the different dialects and voices available.
If you need a reminder as to how to select the appropriate AI language and dialect, check out our article here.
Now, on to the voices! We&amp;rsquo;ve used the phrase birds of a feather, flock together or الطيور على أشكالها تقع for our AI to say each time for the examples.</description></item><item><title>Open Captions: Enhancements November 2019</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/open-captions-enhancements-november-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/open-captions-enhancements-november-2019/</guid><description>Working with a prospect, we added a number of enhancements to our open captions workflow. If you are interested in what open captions are and what its use cases are please have a look at this blog post.
Very simply open captions are generally used as an accessibility tool focused on people who have hearing impairments. More recently due to the rise of streaming services, open captions have been making a come back.</description></item><item><title>Transcribing Indian English: A Simple Guide To Using AI To Speed Up Transcription And Add Open Captions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcribing-indian-english-a-simple-guide-to-using-ai-to-speed-up-transcription-and-add-open-captions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/transcribing-indian-english-a-simple-guide-to-using-ai-to-speed-up-transcription-and-add-open-captions/</guid><description>Today we are going to look at how to transcribe Indian English. Firstly of course, what is Indian English, and what does it sound like? How many such dialects exist? Have a look.
Now that we know what Indian English sounds like, we are going to use a short clip from Rajya Sabha TV, an Indian government content creator. We use our AI to transcribe this clip.
Lastly, we add an Auto-Overlay so that we can show you the video.</description></item><item><title>How Do I Make Subtitles And Closed Captions?</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-do-i-make-subtitles-and-closed-captions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/how-do-i-make-subtitles-and-closed-captions/</guid><description>Many clients ask how us about subtitles. Generally, this is the first question a prospect asks us about our platform. In practise, they mean a few different things.
We want subtitles for our audio/video content. We have subtitles, but want to make changes to the timing. We want to embed our subtitles into our video file, for use in Social Media. Let us look at these questions in detail.</description></item></channel></rss>