<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Japanese on Video Translator</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/tags/japanese/</link><description>Recent content in Japanese on Video Translator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://videotranslator.ai/tags/japanese/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why YouTube Stopped Community Caption Contributions</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:01 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/why-youtube-stopped-community-caption-contributions/</guid><description>Community captions are a function in YouTube. This function allows a YouTube content creator to crowd source captions for their video content.
YouTube is shutting this down. Here is how it will affect you!
Change To Community Contributions On YouTube Notice about an upcoming change to community contributions on YouTube Both creators and viewers have reported problems with the community contributions feature, including spam, abuse, and low quality submissions.</description></item><item><title>On The Brink Of Extinction: Nearly Dead Languages And The Dedicated Linguists Bringing Them Back To Life</title><link>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://videotranslator.ai/news/on-the-brink-of-extinction/</guid><description>Thousands of kilometres apart, and in incredibly different cultures; three linguists are doing their part to save the culture of their people through language.
Masahiro Yamada and Natsuko Nakagawa in Japan and Kenny Pheasant in the United States are all passionate about ensuring almost lost languages are preserved and continue to be taught; and a lot of it comes down to teaching the languages to children.
Linguists Work To Preserve Ryukyu Dialects Now Dying Out Image courtesy of Nobuaki Tanaka Professors at the National Institute for Japanese Language and Linguistics made an alarming discovery when they found that many dialects in the Okinawa Prefecture are on the verge of dying out.</description></item></channel></rss>